[{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d92c"},"rt":20329,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":99164,"subject":"CKQ8J","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610ab372d62539f535d9731b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d92d"},"rt":10998,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":110239,"subject":"CKQ8J","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610ab372d62539f535d9731b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A A U E H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d92e"},"rt":27116,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":137438,"subject":"CKQ8J","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610ab372d62539f535d9731b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d92f"},"rt":11853,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":149353,"subject":"CKQ8J","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610ab372d62539f535d9731b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d930"},"rt":78477,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":227893,"subject":"CKQ8J","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610ab372d62539f535d9731b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"3U U 03 PMI 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d932"},"rt":9453,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":244621,"subject":"CKQ8J","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610ab372d62539f535d9731b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d933"},"rt":16619,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":261302,"subject":"CKQ8J","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610ab372d62539f535d9731b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F B F B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d934"},"rt":104123,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":365489,"subject":"CKQ8J","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610ab372d62539f535d9731b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d935"},"rt":32392,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":398045,"subject":"CKQ8J","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610ab372d62539f535d9731b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d936"},"rt":40289,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":438397,"subject":"CKQ8J","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610ab372d62539f535d9731b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d937"},"rt":6941,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":445423,"subject":"CKQ8J","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610ab372d62539f535d9731b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d938"},"rt":14875,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":460396,"subject":"CKQ8J","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610ab372d62539f535d9731b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"2C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d939"},"rt":30128,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":490577,"subject":"CKQ8J","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610ab372d62539f535d9731b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d93a"},"rt":30624,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":521279,"subject":"CKQ8J","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610ab372d62539f535d9731b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"11 AM12 PMX B O 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d93b"},"rt":97850,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":619209,"subject":"CKQ8J","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610ab372d62539f535d9731b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"I M X X O O M M B O O B B F 3M B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d94c"},"rt":6606,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":46164,"subject":"82VVD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5f4fab801ed01f08bff0257e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d94d"},"rt":6397,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":52612,"subject":"82VVD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5f4fab801ed01f08bff0257e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d94e"},"rt":12629,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":65291,"subject":"82VVD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5f4fab801ed01f08bff0257e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"2C A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d94f"},"rt":53536,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":118877,"subject":"82VVD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5f4fab801ed01f08bff0257e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"11 AM04 PM01 PM04 PME E E 01 PMZ 04 PM04 PMD D J D 04 PMU "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d950"},"rt":35248,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":154185,"subject":"82VVD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5f4fab801ed01f08bff0257e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d952"},"rt":6276,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":165431,"subject":"82VVD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5f4fab801ed01f08bff0257e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"11 AM02 PME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d953"},"rt":7787,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":173272,"subject":"82VVD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5f4fab801ed01f08bff0257e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"10 AMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d954"},"rt":27611,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":200950,"subject":"82VVD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5f4fab801ed01f08bff0257e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"1B B B E G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d955"},"rt":17802,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":218808,"subject":"82VVD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5f4fab801ed01f08bff0257e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J I 09 AM09 AMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d956"},"rt":16199,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":235050,"subject":"82VVD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5f4fab801ed01f08bff0257e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B B F F O Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d957"},"rt":5240,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":240357,"subject":"82VVD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5f4fab801ed01f08bff0257e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"02 PM03 PM02 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d958"},"rt":3852,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":244266,"subject":"82VVD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5f4fab801ed01f08bff0257e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d959"},"rt":16964,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":261288,"subject":"82VVD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5f4fab801ed01f08bff0257e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"M Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d95a"},"rt":8797,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":270148,"subject":"82VVD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5f4fab801ed01f08bff0257e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM06 PMO "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d95b"},"rt":19722,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":289914,"subject":"82VVD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5f4fab801ed01f08bff0257e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"01 PM02 PMX X 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d96c"},"rt":15650,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":83597,"subject":"5J3H6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"60771d9212cc298408c03c96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11103A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d96d"},"rt":12993,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":96638,"subject":"5J3H6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"60771d9212cc298408c03c96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A E E 10"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d96e"},"rt":65705,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":162389,"subject":"5J3H6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"60771d9212cc298408c03c96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C 10 AM03 PM02 PM01 PM10 AM12 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d96f"},"rt":66726,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":229260,"subject":"5J3H6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"60771d9212cc298408c03c96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C C A A Z 02 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d970"},"rt":160380,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":389813,"subject":"5J3H6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"60771d9212cc298408c03c96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I A A A I I A A 11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM06 PM05 PMJ J X J I I 11 AMO O 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM05 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d972"},"rt":9618,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":406548,"subject":"5J3H6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"60771d9212cc298408c03c96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d973"},"rt":75435,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":482058,"subject":"5J3H6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"60771d9212cc298408c03c96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C J J M M B B G G H H Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d974"},"rt":57335,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":539589,"subject":"5J3H6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"60771d9212cc298408c03c96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d975"},"rt":115306,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":654963,"subject":"5J3H6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"60771d9212cc298408c03c96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"X B H H G 10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d976"},"rt":53191,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":708377,"subject":"5J3H6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"60771d9212cc298408c03c96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"F B B B F F F B 12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d977"},"rt":9470,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":717937,"subject":"5J3H6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"60771d9212cc298408c03c96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PM01 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d978"},"rt":12028,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":730012,"subject":"5J3H6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"60771d9212cc298408c03c96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d979"},"rt":47795,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":777899,"subject":"5J3H6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"60771d9212cc298408c03c96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z 04 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d97a"},"rt":32102,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":810070,"subject":"5J3H6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"60771d9212cc298408c03c96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d97b"},"rt":74170,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":884316,"subject":"5J3H6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"60771d9212cc298408c03c96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"12 PM10 AM01 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM11 AM11 AMI 02 PMI 10 AM11 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PMM 01 PMM B B 12 PM01 PM2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d98c"},"rt":22857,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":64547,"subject":"M6Y4Z","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AMC C C C C C C 11 AMZ F C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d98d"},"rt":12826,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":77457,"subject":"M6Y4Z","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"5O D D K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d98e"},"rt":20107,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":97626,"subject":"M6Y4Z","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,J","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d98f"},"rt":12147,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":109835,"subject":"M6Y4Z","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"01 PM02 PM10 AM11 AM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d990"},"rt":29301,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":139198,"subject":"M6Y4Z","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d992"},"rt":14749,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":176183,"subject":"M6Y4Z","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,H","hovered":"09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d993"},"rt":26546,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":202798,"subject":"M6Y4Z","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"J F X J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d994"},"rt":48623,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":251484,"subject":"M6Y4Z","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"1B M B B F F L C G X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d995"},"rt":27431,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":278977,"subject":"M6Y4Z","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,O","hovered":"F X J J M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d996"},"rt":6423,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":285494,"subject":"M6Y4Z","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d997"},"rt":13944,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":299498,"subject":"M6Y4Z","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"04 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d998"},"rt":11115,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":310676,"subject":"M6Y4Z","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d999"},"rt":32109,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":342849,"subject":"M6Y4Z","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":"Z F F N N N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d99a"},"rt":28081,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":370993,"subject":"M6Y4Z","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM03 PMX 03 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d99b"},"rt":18997,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":390101,"subject":"M6Y4Z","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62eec1ce0ae04f6129df1e94","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PMZ F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9ac"},"rt":26424,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":97594,"subject":"F7Q5V","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62bdfe451d380bec13a4a864","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9ad"},"rt":15461,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":113166,"subject":"F7Q5V","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62bdfe451d380bec13a4a864","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9ae"},"rt":10682,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":123958,"subject":"F7Q5V","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62bdfe451d380bec13a4a864","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9af"},"rt":39522,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":163582,"subject":"F7Q5V","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62bdfe451d380bec13a4a864","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,U","hovered":"04 PMU 1004 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9b0"},"rt":49602,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":213280,"subject":"F7Q5V","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62bdfe451d380bec13a4a864","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9b2"},"rt":7968,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":226806,"subject":"F7Q5V","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62bdfe451d380bec13a4a864","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9b3"},"rt":10590,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":237495,"subject":"F7Q5V","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62bdfe451d380bec13a4a864","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9b4"},"rt":29679,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":267278,"subject":"F7Q5V","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62bdfe451d380bec13a4a864","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"3F B 3B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9b5"},"rt":39510,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":306891,"subject":"F7Q5V","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62bdfe451d380bec13a4a864","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,K,P","hovered":"J J D D P "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9b6"},"rt":39166,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":346158,"subject":"F7Q5V","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62bdfe451d380bec13a4a864","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B F B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9b7"},"rt":33548,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":379811,"subject":"F7Q5V","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62bdfe451d380bec13a4a864","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"E P K K K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9b8"},"rt":27589,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":407505,"subject":"F7Q5V","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62bdfe451d380bec13a4a864","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,J,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9b9"},"rt":20935,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":428546,"subject":"F7Q5V","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62bdfe451d380bec13a4a864","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9ba"},"rt":15333,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":443984,"subject":"F7Q5V","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62bdfe451d380bec13a4a864","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"O J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9bb"},"rt":22494,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":466581,"subject":"F7Q5V","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62bdfe451d380bec13a4a864","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9cc"},"rt":20515,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":92541,"subject":"V82NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60ff10899697dd7bdbdac10f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"08 AM10 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9cd"},"rt":8143,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":100823,"subject":"V82NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60ff10899697dd7bdbdac10f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"C K 12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9ce"},"rt":20731,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":121639,"subject":"V82NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60ff10899697dd7bdbdac10f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A 10 AM11 AMC 11 AMC C 11 AM11 AMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9cf"},"rt":6331,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":128058,"subject":"V82NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60ff10899697dd7bdbdac10f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"A 02 PM04 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9d0"},"rt":64451,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":192593,"subject":"V82NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60ff10899697dd7bdbdac10f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"7I 12 PMZ Z Z Z A Z Z Z 12 PM12 PMZ 12 PMZ Z Z 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9d2"},"rt":5269,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":202491,"subject":"V82NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60ff10899697dd7bdbdac10f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9d3"},"rt":29763,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":232361,"subject":"V82NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60ff10899697dd7bdbdac10f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"08 AMI J J J J J A A M X O O X X 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9d4"},"rt":44800,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":277299,"subject":"V82NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60ff10899697dd7bdbdac10f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"08 AM09 AMB E J J J E F 10 AMF F B B 10 AMF G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9d5"},"rt":19934,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":297318,"subject":"V82NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60ff10899697dd7bdbdac10f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"08 AMI J J 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9d6"},"rt":6276,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":303780,"subject":"V82NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60ff10899697dd7bdbdac10f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"M M F F F 02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9d7"},"rt":10070,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":313937,"subject":"V82NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60ff10899697dd7bdbdac10f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PM01 PM12 PMM M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9d8"},"rt":6872,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":320903,"subject":"V82NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60ff10899697dd7bdbdac10f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9d9"},"rt":11475,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":332460,"subject":"V82NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60ff10899697dd7bdbdac10f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"M F Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9da"},"rt":9309,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":341912,"subject":"V82NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60ff10899697dd7bdbdac10f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"4X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9db"},"rt":12441,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":354436,"subject":"V82NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60ff10899697dd7bdbdac10f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9ec"},"rt":18169,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":97656,"subject":"REWC9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6111f29123e474c8788b6df3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMA A C 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9ed"},"rt":11140,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":108850,"subject":"REWC9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6111f29123e474c8788b6df3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"K E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9ee"},"rt":20874,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":129784,"subject":"REWC9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6111f29123e474c8788b6df3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9ef"},"rt":37964,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":167791,"subject":"REWC9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6111f29123e474c8788b6df3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"308 PM05 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9f0"},"rt":45069,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":212916,"subject":"REWC9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6111f29123e474c8788b6df3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9f2"},"rt":16905,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":248057,"subject":"REWC9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6111f29123e474c8788b6df3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9f3"},"rt":36246,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":284349,"subject":"REWC9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6111f29123e474c8788b6df3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9f4"},"rt":101243,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":385652,"subject":"REWC9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6111f29123e474c8788b6df3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9f5"},"rt":43474,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":429304,"subject":"REWC9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6111f29123e474c8788b6df3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"X B J B J 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9f6"},"rt":9774,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":439132,"subject":"REWC9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6111f29123e474c8788b6df3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9f7"},"rt":11589,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":450774,"subject":"REWC9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6111f29123e474c8788b6df3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"11 AM12 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9f8"},"rt":9084,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":459915,"subject":"REWC9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6111f29123e474c8788b6df3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9f9"},"rt":29419,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":489391,"subject":"REWC9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6111f29123e474c8788b6df3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":"4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9fa"},"rt":36355,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":525807,"subject":"REWC9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6111f29123e474c8788b6df3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":6,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,H,L,N,P,Z","hovered":"11 AM03 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972d9fb"},"rt":19189,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":545048,"subject":"REWC9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6111f29123e474c8788b6df3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PM02 PM02 PMX X 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da0c"},"rt":16135,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":37460,"subject":"GN4BR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,O,I","hovered":"09 AMA 10 AM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da0d"},"rt":7570,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":45160,"subject":"GN4BR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da0e"},"rt":14694,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":59966,"subject":"GN4BR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C A A C C C C C C C C C C C A A Z Z Z Z C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da0f"},"rt":34888,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":94976,"subject":"GN4BR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"F C C Z A A A Z 06 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da10"},"rt":14660,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":109762,"subject":"GN4BR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da12"},"rt":18940,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":131052,"subject":"GN4BR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"09 AM11"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da13"},"rt":20927,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":152098,"subject":"GN4BR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"C C J F I I I F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da14"},"rt":35984,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":188204,"subject":"GN4BR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"12 PMM M M J J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da15"},"rt":4341,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":192686,"subject":"GN4BR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da16"},"rt":5956,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":198760,"subject":"GN4BR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da17"},"rt":9788,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":208670,"subject":"GN4BR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PMB B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da18"},"rt":15879,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":224671,"subject":"GN4BR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"01 PM02 PM03 PM12 PM01 PMF F F B B F F B F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da19"},"rt":17527,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":242320,"subject":"GN4BR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M,X","hovered":"Z Z Z O O O X X X X 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da1a"},"rt":10500,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":252938,"subject":"GN4BR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,O","hovered":"12 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM03 PMO O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da1b"},"rt":3171,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":256225,"subject":"GN4BR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da2c"},"rt":13021,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":68790,"subject":"R1T02","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeeb4903c80f200013af2ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A A 2A A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da2d"},"rt":7595,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":76429,"subject":"R1T02","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeeb4903c80f200013af2ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da2e"},"rt":10801,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":87269,"subject":"R1T02","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeeb4903c80f200013af2ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C A Z 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da2f"},"rt":18834,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":106149,"subject":"R1T02","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeeb4903c80f200013af2ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"04 PMK O O K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da30"},"rt":49356,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":155541,"subject":"R1T02","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeeb4903c80f200013af2ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"I I 12 PMI I I O O I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da32"},"rt":6957,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":164688,"subject":"R1T02","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeeb4903c80f200013af2ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da33"},"rt":11497,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":176221,"subject":"R1T02","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeeb4903c80f200013af2ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da34"},"rt":13852,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":190108,"subject":"R1T02","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeeb4903c80f200013af2ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da35"},"rt":7591,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":197732,"subject":"R1T02","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeeb4903c80f200013af2ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da36"},"rt":23181,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":220947,"subject":"R1T02","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeeb4903c80f200013af2ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F F F 04 PMX 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da37"},"rt":5917,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":226907,"subject":"R1T02","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeeb4903c80f200013af2ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da38"},"rt":5063,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":232003,"subject":"R1T02","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeeb4903c80f200013af2ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da39"},"rt":44332,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":276371,"subject":"R1T02","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeeb4903c80f200013af2ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,O","hovered":"O Z O X M B F O Z Z Z O O C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da3a"},"rt":25125,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":301532,"subject":"R1T02","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeeb4903c80f200013af2ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"E X X X 04 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da3b"},"rt":20475,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":322044,"subject":"R1T02","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeeb4903c80f200013af2ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da4c"},"rt":43919,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":109564,"subject":"OOXNY","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5d229433f9b71c00010853ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"5511 AMA 12 PM11 AM02 PM03 PM6O A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da4d"},"rt":7095,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":116748,"subject":"OOXNY","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5d229433f9b71c00010853ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da4e"},"rt":6925,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":123760,"subject":"OOXNY","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5d229433f9b71c00010853ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"F Z C C 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da4f"},"rt":15998,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":139844,"subject":"OOXNY","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5d229433f9b71c00010853ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,H","hovered":"011 AM12 PM01 PM04 PM04 PM04 PME D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da50"},"rt":23739,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":163674,"subject":"OOXNY","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5d229433f9b71c00010853ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I I I I I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da52"},"rt":96116,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":268188,"subject":"OOXNY","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5d229433f9b71c00010853ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"10 AMI 10 AM09 AM09 AM10 AM09 AM10 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM01 PMA A 04 PMZ Z 04 PMO C G G A A 12 PM12 PMB B F 10 AM10 AM10 AM10 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM08 PM07 PM12 PME E G J 10 AM11 AMM M C 04 PM03 PM02 PM09 AM08 AM10 AMM 06 PM06 PMM X X M M M M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da53"},"rt":12738,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":281172,"subject":"OOXNY","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5d229433f9b71c00010853ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L","hovered":"I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da54"},"rt":111740,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":392998,"subject":"OOXNY","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5d229433f9b71c00010853ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I B B A 10 AMK K C 1103 PMB B B 11 AM11 AM12 PM10 AM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da55"},"rt":10367,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":403688,"subject":"OOXNY","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5d229433f9b71c00010853ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"X X B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da56"},"rt":11207,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":414982,"subject":"OOXNY","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5d229433f9b71c00010853ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da57"},"rt":6957,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":422037,"subject":"OOXNY","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5d229433f9b71c00010853ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM01 PM12 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da58"},"rt":8900,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":431029,"subject":"OOXNY","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5d229433f9b71c00010853ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da59"},"rt":12930,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":444049,"subject":"OOXNY","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5d229433f9b71c00010853ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L","hovered":"01 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da5a"},"rt":10398,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":454535,"subject":"OOXNY","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5d229433f9b71c00010853ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"04 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMO J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da5b"},"rt":17138,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":471762,"subject":"OOXNY","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5d229433f9b71c00010853ed","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"101 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da6c"},"rt":26085,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":118071,"subject":"44H3S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"J J X X X X 1210 AM11 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da6d"},"rt":9034,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":127252,"subject":"44H3S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"D I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da6e"},"rt":39491,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":166870,"subject":"44H3S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C C C C C C 2C C C C C 24310 AM10 AMC C C 10 AMC A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da6f"},"rt":8836,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":175821,"subject":"44H3S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da70"},"rt":7660,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":183597,"subject":"44H3S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da72"},"rt":7891,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":200094,"subject":"44H3S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da73"},"rt":26397,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":226615,"subject":"44H3S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"5F B B B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da74"},"rt":49749,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":276477,"subject":"44H3S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"E A E B B B B B M M M M M M M M M M M M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da75"},"rt":11711,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":288324,"subject":"44H3S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"2J J J J M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da76"},"rt":43644,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":332077,"subject":"44H3S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"Z F F B B F B B B B I B B B B F B 12 PMF 03 PM04 PMZ Z C C 11 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da77"},"rt":10375,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":342570,"subject":"44H3S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da78"},"rt":4487,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":347177,"subject":"44H3S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da79"},"rt":9206,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":356613,"subject":"44H3S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,O","hovered":"Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da7a"},"rt":35849,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":392575,"subject":"44H3S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"02 PM01 PM10 AM10 AM11 AM03 PMM M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da7b"},"rt":4115,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":396808,"subject":"44H3S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5aeab6e39e185a0001b9e272","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da8c"},"rt":296567,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":351913,"subject":"QXSGR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5f517f5efe32293c4b0fbdb0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"209 AM08 AM09 AM11 AMI 6A F F F 11 AM11 AM11 AMC 10 AM10 AMC 11 AMZ F 09 AM08 AM11 AM11 AMF F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da8d"},"rt":23282,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":375594,"subject":"QXSGR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5f517f5efe32293c4b0fbdb0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"12 PMD 12 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da8e"},"rt":8675,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":384380,"subject":"QXSGR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5f517f5efe32293c4b0fbdb0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"10 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da8f"},"rt":33624,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":418106,"subject":"QXSGR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5f517f5efe32293c4b0fbdb0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"05 PM04 PMH 05 PM04 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da90"},"rt":19910,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":438126,"subject":"QXSGR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5f517f5efe32293c4b0fbdb0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"H J I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da92"},"rt":17656,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":460563,"subject":"QXSGR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5f517f5efe32293c4b0fbdb0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"D 04 PM10 AME C C G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da93"},"rt":35587,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":496262,"subject":"QXSGR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5f517f5efe32293c4b0fbdb0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"C F B B B F F X X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da94"},"rt":38914,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":535285,"subject":"QXSGR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5f517f5efe32293c4b0fbdb0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da95"},"rt":26481,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":561881,"subject":"QXSGR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5f517f5efe32293c4b0fbdb0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"10 AM10 AMJ J J I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da96"},"rt":12009,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":574001,"subject":"QXSGR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5f517f5efe32293c4b0fbdb0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da97"},"rt":27197,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":601312,"subject":"QXSGR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5f517f5efe32293c4b0fbdb0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"01 PM12 PM10 AM12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da98"},"rt":9330,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":610753,"subject":"QXSGR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5f517f5efe32293c4b0fbdb0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da99"},"rt":9871,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":620732,"subject":"QXSGR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5f517f5efe32293c4b0fbdb0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"10 AM02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da9a"},"rt":11663,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":632500,"subject":"QXSGR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5f517f5efe32293c4b0fbdb0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"112 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972da9b"},"rt":14478,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":647090,"subject":"QXSGR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5f517f5efe32293c4b0fbdb0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"01 PM02 PM02 PMX I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972daac"},"rt":12982,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":48872,"subject":"UESF5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60d13c261171b69977e81f9b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972daad"},"rt":12160,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":61063,"subject":"UESF5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60d13c261171b69977e81f9b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"01 PMD J E E 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972daae"},"rt":28823,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":89917,"subject":"UESF5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60d13c261171b69977e81f9b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,J","hovered":"02 PM01 PM12 PMC C C 11 AM10 AM09 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972daaf"},"rt":27388,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":117335,"subject":"UESF5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60d13c261171b69977e81f9b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PMU U 03 PM10 AMC C 02 PM08 PM07 PM06 PM05 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dab0"},"rt":12246,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":129611,"subject":"UESF5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60d13c261171b69977e81f9b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C I 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dab2"},"rt":8983,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":144831,"subject":"UESF5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60d13c261171b69977e81f9b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dab3"},"rt":18665,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":163526,"subject":"UESF5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60d13c261171b69977e81f9b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"6F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dab4"},"rt":12902,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":176491,"subject":"UESF5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60d13c261171b69977e81f9b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dab5"},"rt":12970,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":189490,"subject":"UESF5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60d13c261171b69977e81f9b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"P L J J A A A 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dab6"},"rt":11012,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":200535,"subject":"UESF5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60d13c261171b69977e81f9b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"F F 06 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dab7"},"rt":10985,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":211571,"subject":"UESF5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60d13c261171b69977e81f9b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"06 PM05 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dab8"},"rt":10184,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":221811,"subject":"UESF5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60d13c261171b69977e81f9b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dab9"},"rt":21438,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":243303,"subject":"UESF5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60d13c261171b69977e81f9b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":"Z Z 05 PM04 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972daba"},"rt":108932,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":352298,"subject":"UESF5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60d13c261171b69977e81f9b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"03 PM03 PM05 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMM M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dabb"},"rt":12308,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":364706,"subject":"UESF5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60d13c261171b69977e81f9b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"02 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dacc"},"rt":44938,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":139669,"subject":"D46SH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100b6365a3b961d941f7071","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"08 AM08 AM09 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMA 11 AMC C Z F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dacd"},"rt":17688,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":157652,"subject":"D46SH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100b6365a3b961d941f7071","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,K","hovered":"K 12 PMA Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dace"},"rt":46235,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":203959,"subject":"D46SH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100b6365a3b961d941f7071","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A C C A 08 AMC 11 AM09 AMC 11 AMF 11 AM01 PMC 11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dacf"},"rt":34311,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":238338,"subject":"D46SH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100b6365a3b961d941f7071","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"H H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dad0"},"rt":92725,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":331148,"subject":"D46SH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100b6365a3b961d941f7071","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"O O O C C 09 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM11 AMA A 02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dad2"},"rt":19318,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":354441,"subject":"D46SH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100b6365a3b961d941f7071","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dad3"},"rt":42894,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":397406,"subject":"D46SH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100b6365a3b961d941f7071","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F 06 PMX X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dad4"},"rt":214661,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":612151,"subject":"D46SH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100b6365a3b961d941f7071","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"L G 5B 10 AMB B B B G G G O C H C J J B X X B C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dad5"},"rt":85548,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":698042,"subject":"D46SH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100b6365a3b961d941f7071","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"10 AM10 AM3208 AMI J I J 08 AMJ 11 AM33J J J E F 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dad6"},"rt":15633,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":713949,"subject":"D46SH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100b6365a3b961d941f7071","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"I 02 PM02 PMF E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dad7"},"rt":17309,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":731327,"subject":"D46SH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100b6365a3b961d941f7071","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"311 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dad8"},"rt":10680,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":742080,"subject":"D46SH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100b6365a3b961d941f7071","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"1F 10 AMF G A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dad9"},"rt":24792,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":766939,"subject":"D46SH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100b6365a3b961d941f7071","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X Z N 06 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dada"},"rt":16119,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":783128,"subject":"D46SH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100b6365a3b961d941f7071","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PM03 PM03 PMX X X X X X X 03 PMX B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dadb"},"rt":35742,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":818948,"subject":"D46SH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100b6365a3b961d941f7071","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"M 11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PMX X X X X 01 PM02 PMK K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972daec"},"rt":48267,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":184483,"subject":"64SNN","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62ceb98594c924be25e1db41","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM12 PM11 AMA A A A 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972daed"},"rt":11069,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":195630,"subject":"64SNN","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62ceb98594c924be25e1db41","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972daee"},"rt":14534,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":210241,"subject":"64SNN","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62ceb98594c924be25e1db41","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C 12 PM12 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972daef"},"rt":83628,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":293933,"subject":"64SNN","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62ceb98594c924be25e1db41","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"01 PMZ U F 11 AMA 04 PM01 PMZ U U U F 01 PM01 PMO O O O 02 PM01 PMH H 01 PM01 PMH 12 PM12 PMZ 11 AMA A F F F F H H 09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972daf0"},"rt":185473,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":479808,"subject":"64SNN","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62ceb98594c924be25e1db41","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"10I I 12 PMA A A C C X 02 PM02 PMB B 02 PM12 PMZ O 911X I I 710 AM11 AM12 PM12 PMZ 7I 11 AMI I O O O 12 PM03 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972daf2"},"rt":8863,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":494311,"subject":"64SNN","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62ceb98594c924be25e1db41","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972daf3"},"rt":20475,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":514859,"subject":"64SNN","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62ceb98594c924be25e1db41","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4F B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972daf4"},"rt":28047,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":543050,"subject":"64SNN","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62ceb98594c924be25e1db41","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J 5E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972daf5"},"rt":18608,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":561731,"subject":"64SNN","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62ceb98594c924be25e1db41","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972daf6"},"rt":64225,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":626122,"subject":"64SNN","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62ceb98594c924be25e1db41","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"M B F 05 PM05 PM04 PMF F Z 04 PMI 01 PM01 PM01 PM12 PMB B F B M M 01 PM01 PM02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972daf7"},"rt":8006,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":634630,"subject":"64SNN","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62ceb98594c924be25e1db41","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972daf8"},"rt":12257,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":646960,"subject":"64SNN","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62ceb98594c924be25e1db41","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"6F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972daf9"},"rt":26068,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":673100,"subject":"64SNN","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62ceb98594c924be25e1db41","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"H Z Z 04 PMZ Z F B O 04 PM01 PM12 PMB B X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dafa"},"rt":78714,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":751931,"subject":"64SNN","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62ceb98594c924be25e1db41","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM02 PMB B 02 PM11 AM10 AM10 AMJ J 10 AM09 AM09 AM08 AME 11 AM03 PMF E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dafb"},"rt":101076,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":853522,"subject":"64SNN","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62ceb98594c924be25e1db41","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"11 AMB 02 PM04 PMZ Z O 01 PM01 PM02 PMX X J J J J E G G 5G E F 3I B F F B B O O B O O G A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db0c"},"rt":22081,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":131347,"subject":"E0GFS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A 11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db0d"},"rt":11201,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":142650,"subject":"E0GFS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"01 PMD "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db0e"},"rt":7857,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":150620,"subject":"E0GFS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db0f"},"rt":14028,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":164760,"subject":"E0GFS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db10"},"rt":16039,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":180908,"subject":"E0GFS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db12"},"rt":64834,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":249636,"subject":"E0GFS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.75,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":9,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,H,K,L,N,O,P,Z,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db13"},"rt":74552,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":324493,"subject":"E0GFS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db14"},"rt":43631,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":368430,"subject":"E0GFS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I,J","hovered":"02 PM03 PM4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db15"},"rt":10888,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":379419,"subject":"E0GFS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMJ J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db16"},"rt":12398,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":391920,"subject":"E0GFS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db17"},"rt":12782,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":404805,"subject":"E0GFS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M 12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db18"},"rt":8945,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":413849,"subject":"E0GFS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"5F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db19"},"rt":41940,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":455908,"subject":"E0GFS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"O N Z L L F J J C Z Z Z Z Z H H Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db1a"},"rt":18626,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":474633,"subject":"E0GFS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db1b"},"rt":7033,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":481765,"subject":"E0GFS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db2c"},"rt":9132,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":76300,"subject":"M0RB1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5cc8039e3ef93000171c96b8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db2d"},"rt":7727,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":84114,"subject":"M0RB1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5cc8039e3ef93000171c96b8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"08 AM08 AM4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db2e"},"rt":10500,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":94698,"subject":"M0RB1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5cc8039e3ef93000171c96b8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db2f"},"rt":15647,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":110444,"subject":"M0RB1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5cc8039e3ef93000171c96b8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,H","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db30"},"rt":54384,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":164915,"subject":"M0RB1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5cc8039e3ef93000171c96b8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"C 67I I O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db32"},"rt":53544,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":221915,"subject":"M0RB1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5cc8039e3ef93000171c96b8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"A A G G 05 PM06 PM07 PM08 PMA A A G G G C C F O G G J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db33"},"rt":22333,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":244354,"subject":"M0RB1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5cc8039e3ef93000171c96b8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db34"},"rt":86915,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":331354,"subject":"M0RB1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5cc8039e3ef93000171c96b8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db35"},"rt":19588,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":351235,"subject":"M0RB1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5cc8039e3ef93000171c96b8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db36"},"rt":30213,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":381578,"subject":"M0RB1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5cc8039e3ef93000171c96b8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db37"},"rt":7854,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":389538,"subject":"M0RB1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5cc8039e3ef93000171c96b8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db38"},"rt":6923,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":396546,"subject":"M0RB1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5cc8039e3ef93000171c96b8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db39"},"rt":26773,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":423418,"subject":"M0RB1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5cc8039e3ef93000171c96b8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db3a"},"rt":20066,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":443570,"subject":"M0RB1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5cc8039e3ef93000171c96b8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db3b"},"rt":18398,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":462123,"subject":"M0RB1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5cc8039e3ef93000171c96b8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db4c"},"rt":12816,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":39828,"subject":"LJ5PP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db4d"},"rt":8703,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":48630,"subject":"LJ5PP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db4e"},"rt":5941,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":54674,"subject":"LJ5PP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db4f"},"rt":13022,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":67802,"subject":"LJ5PP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"04 PME E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db50"},"rt":13789,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":81690,"subject":"LJ5PP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"I O 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db52"},"rt":38168,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":123075,"subject":"LJ5PP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":6,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,H,L,N,P,Z","hovered":"08 PM08 PM07 PM08 PM07 PM07 PM06 PM06 PM05 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db53"},"rt":18523,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":141699,"subject":"LJ5PP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":"3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db54"},"rt":37342,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":179297,"subject":"LJ5PP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B X X E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db55"},"rt":17792,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":197188,"subject":"LJ5PP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"F J J J J I E I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db56"},"rt":13931,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":211223,"subject":"LJ5PP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db57"},"rt":9938,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":221259,"subject":"LJ5PP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"02 PM01 PM12 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db58"},"rt":10471,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":231836,"subject":"LJ5PP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db59"},"rt":50663,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":282597,"subject":"LJ5PP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"J B Z Z Z O X X B B B B B B F Z F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db5a"},"rt":39071,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":321770,"subject":"LJ5PP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"O 03 PMF B B B I X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db5b"},"rt":31315,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":353198,"subject":"LJ5PP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62e4b6f21f7c164777c6eb67","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,C","hovered":"01 PM02 PMX X X F C C I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db6c"},"rt":17444,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":98800,"subject":"K780A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6112dccad39227e361c13866","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"01 PM12 PMA 11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db6d"},"rt":8940,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":107797,"subject":"K780A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6112dccad39227e361c13866","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db6e"},"rt":28910,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":136756,"subject":"K780A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6112dccad39227e361c13866","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"A A A 01 PMZ C C 10 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db6f"},"rt":15538,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":152341,"subject":"K780A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6112dccad39227e361c13866","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"08 AM09 AM11 AM04 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db70"},"rt":92479,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":244877,"subject":"K780A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6112dccad39227e361c13866","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db72"},"rt":6636,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":257469,"subject":"K780A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6112dccad39227e361c13866","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db73"},"rt":17421,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":274942,"subject":"K780A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6112dccad39227e361c13866","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db74"},"rt":39953,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":314946,"subject":"K780A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6112dccad39227e361c13866","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db75"},"rt":40332,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":355327,"subject":"K780A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6112dccad39227e361c13866","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"10 AMB B O H N 09 AMJ I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db76"},"rt":50573,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":405949,"subject":"K780A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6112dccad39227e361c13866","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"F F 04 PM04 PMB J X X 04 PM04 PMF F E E E 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db77"},"rt":9530,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":415546,"subject":"K780A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6112dccad39227e361c13866","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"02 PM01 PM12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db78"},"rt":10077,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":425670,"subject":"K780A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6112dccad39227e361c13866","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db79"},"rt":39391,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":465108,"subject":"K780A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6112dccad39227e361c13866","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"J 01 PM12K H C Z Z N X M J N O Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db7a"},"rt":26900,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":492061,"subject":"K780A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6112dccad39227e361c13866","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"01 PM02 PM03 PMB E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db7b"},"rt":50008,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":542117,"subject":"K780A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6112dccad39227e361c13866","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM02 PM02 PM12 PMM M M M M I B F F E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db8c"},"rt":9518,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":70831,"subject":"2FYOZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"629e633c82ed7bd84fce0f9a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"X C Z Z A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db8d"},"rt":6571,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":77440,"subject":"2FYOZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"629e633c82ed7bd84fce0f9a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db8e"},"rt":64079,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":141554,"subject":"2FYOZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"629e633c82ed7bd84fce0f9a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM08 PMD X 11 AM10 AMC A B A A A U 12 PM2Z B 346C O O H 10 AM09 AMU B X X X X G A C C 11 AMA 09 AM08 AM07 PM08 PMX A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db8f"},"rt":6638,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":148326,"subject":"2FYOZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"629e633c82ed7bd84fce0f9a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"02 PM03 PM05 PM04 PM04 PMK H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db90"},"rt":23927,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":172288,"subject":"2FYOZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"629e633c82ed7bd84fce0f9a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db92"},"rt":10346,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":186700,"subject":"2FYOZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"629e633c82ed7bd84fce0f9a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E 02 PMX X E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db93"},"rt":17832,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":204569,"subject":"2FYOZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"629e633c82ed7bd84fce0f9a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"1C C B B 10 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db94"},"rt":44789,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":249393,"subject":"2FYOZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"629e633c82ed7bd84fce0f9a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"3C M B B B B B 03 PME E E M F F E E B 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db95"},"rt":17087,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":266517,"subject":"2FYOZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"629e633c82ed7bd84fce0f9a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"Z Z J I 0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db96"},"rt":6797,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":273350,"subject":"2FYOZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"629e633c82ed7bd84fce0f9a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"3B B M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db97"},"rt":6380,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":279765,"subject":"2FYOZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"629e633c82ed7bd84fce0f9a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"P P 02 PM01 PM12 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db98"},"rt":4586,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":284391,"subject":"2FYOZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"629e633c82ed7bd84fce0f9a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"08 AM09 AMF F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db99"},"rt":21656,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":306083,"subject":"2FYOZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"629e633c82ed7bd84fce0f9a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G,O","hovered":"1X Z Z 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db9a"},"rt":6484,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":312609,"subject":"2FYOZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"629e633c82ed7bd84fce0f9a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"12 PM06 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972db9b"},"rt":18349,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":330995,"subject":"2FYOZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"629e633c82ed7bd84fce0f9a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"12 PMO O 03 PM02 PMX X X 11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbac"},"rt":16372,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":82437,"subject":"76BPO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM11 AMA 10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbad"},"rt":12603,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":95156,"subject":"76BPO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbae"},"rt":25114,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":120388,"subject":"76BPO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"09 AMC C C C C C C 12 PM12 PMZ Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbaf"},"rt":41503,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":162014,"subject":"76BPO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,U","hovered":"03 PM03 PMZ Z A F 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbb0"},"rt":59427,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":221579,"subject":"76BPO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"09 AMI I 77I I I I 11 AM11 AMO 12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbb2"},"rt":12045,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":242101,"subject":"76BPO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbb3"},"rt":14884,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":257159,"subject":"76BPO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbb4"},"rt":92207,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":349507,"subject":"76BPO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.3333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":4,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,J,M,N","hovered":"11 AMB B 08 AM6E L 5E G F F B B M J J J M M N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbb5"},"rt":37013,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":387071,"subject":"76BPO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"2F J J M I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbb6"},"rt":59944,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":447252,"subject":"76BPO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"O N F F F F F F F F F F 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbb7"},"rt":11889,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":459276,"subject":"76BPO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbb8"},"rt":11152,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":470557,"subject":"76BPO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"08 AMB F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbb9"},"rt":58114,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":528934,"subject":"76BPO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"02 PM03 PMO O Z Z Z Z Z Z 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbba"},"rt":18327,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":547439,"subject":"76BPO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbbb"},"rt":49372,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":597005,"subject":"76BPO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"J M M M M 02 PM02 PMM M 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbcc"},"rt":11994,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":62140,"subject":"9BLWS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5e27727328b7b698b037ee6c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbcd"},"rt":7418,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":69675,"subject":"9BLWS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5e27727328b7b698b037ee6c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"Z E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbce"},"rt":92037,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":161812,"subject":"9BLWS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5e27727328b7b698b037ee6c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM01 PMC C C 10 AMZ 06 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMA U C O O O C C C C O O C 09 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbcf"},"rt":15364,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":177497,"subject":"9BLWS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5e27727328b7b698b037ee6c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbd0"},"rt":45928,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":223532,"subject":"9BLWS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5e27727328b7b698b037ee6c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"4I O O I O 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbd2"},"rt":29900,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":259538,"subject":"9BLWS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5e27727328b7b698b037ee6c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F,I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbd3"},"rt":14963,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":274604,"subject":"9BLWS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5e27727328b7b698b037ee6c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbd4"},"rt":26135,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":300844,"subject":"9BLWS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5e27727328b7b698b037ee6c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbd5"},"rt":19034,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":319979,"subject":"9BLWS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5e27727328b7b698b037ee6c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbd6"},"rt":10212,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":330293,"subject":"9BLWS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5e27727328b7b698b037ee6c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbd7"},"rt":6915,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":337305,"subject":"9BLWS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5e27727328b7b698b037ee6c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbd8"},"rt":6185,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":343589,"subject":"9BLWS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5e27727328b7b698b037ee6c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbd9"},"rt":13186,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":356877,"subject":"9BLWS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5e27727328b7b698b037ee6c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L,P","hovered":"F B Z Z H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbda"},"rt":7882,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":364863,"subject":"9BLWS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5e27727328b7b698b037ee6c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbdb"},"rt":12909,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":377882,"subject":"9BLWS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5e27727328b7b698b037ee6c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,X","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbec"},"rt":5744,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":23633,"subject":"HSJBQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbed"},"rt":12475,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":36234,"subject":"HSJBQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"12 PMD "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbee"},"rt":16569,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":52932,"subject":"HSJBQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"10 AMC C C C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbef"},"rt":41478,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":94680,"subject":"HSJBQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,U","hovered":"02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbf0"},"rt":83220,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":178025,"subject":"HSJBQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"08 AMI I O I O O 12 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM12 PM03 PMO Z I H H 10"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbf2"},"rt":8649,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":188991,"subject":"HSJBQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbf3"},"rt":30495,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":219713,"subject":"HSJBQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbf4"},"rt":41390,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":261224,"subject":"HSJBQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":"09 AMG G G G G M M M N N N N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbf5"},"rt":35581,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":297016,"subject":"HSJBQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbf6"},"rt":34105,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":331348,"subject":"HSJBQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"10 AMF F F F F F M M X X 10 AM01 PMX X 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbf7"},"rt":12715,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":344290,"subject":"HSJBQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbf8"},"rt":7177,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":351675,"subject":"HSJBQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"08 AM10 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbf9"},"rt":30288,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":382102,"subject":"HSJBQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"10 AML Z Z 09 AMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbfa"},"rt":31801,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":414140,"subject":"HSJBQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"M O X X M M B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dbfb"},"rt":31868,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":446144,"subject":"HSJBQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62cb2fda77bec729c86fbbba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"10 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM11 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc0c"},"rt":65349,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":315459,"subject":"9470X","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5dc50289718e6d39756e99f9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"10 AM03 PM10 AM3208 AM08 AM08 AM0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc0d"},"rt":20206,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":335978,"subject":"9470X","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5dc50289718e6d39756e99f9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"1Z U K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc0e"},"rt":38371,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":374440,"subject":"9470X","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5dc50289718e6d39756e99f9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM11 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc0f"},"rt":13744,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":388280,"subject":"9470X","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5dc50289718e6d39756e99f9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"C C 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc10"},"rt":27383,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":415752,"subject":"9470X","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5dc50289718e6d39756e99f9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"09 AM2C A F 609 AM10 AMA A O I 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc12"},"rt":10845,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":446433,"subject":"9470X","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5dc50289718e6d39756e99f9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AM0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc13"},"rt":62130,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":508652,"subject":"9470X","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5dc50289718e6d39756e99f9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F 08 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc14"},"rt":68189,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":577105,"subject":"9470X","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5dc50289718e6d39756e99f9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"Z G J F F F F F C G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc15"},"rt":78056,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":655407,"subject":"9470X","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5dc50289718e6d39756e99f9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"Z O B B J J J J I I I I E B 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc16"},"rt":12816,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":668461,"subject":"9470X","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5dc50289718e6d39756e99f9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc17"},"rt":25790,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":694350,"subject":"9470X","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5dc50289718e6d39756e99f9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM01 PML L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc18"},"rt":8589,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":703029,"subject":"9470X","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5dc50289718e6d39756e99f9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"4B F F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc19"},"rt":26572,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":729692,"subject":"9470X","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5dc50289718e6d39756e99f9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"I I Z Z 12 PM01 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc1a"},"rt":18092,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":747876,"subject":"9470X","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5dc50289718e6d39756e99f9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"008 AM09 AM10 AM04 PM03 PMX 12 PM01 PM03 PM02 PMM X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc1b"},"rt":28435,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":776412,"subject":"9470X","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5dc50289718e6d39756e99f9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"01 PM02 PMX B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc2c"},"rt":5735,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":21150,"subject":"PR840","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc2d"},"rt":6187,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":27425,"subject":"PR840","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc2e"},"rt":10651,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":38160,"subject":"PR840","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"10 AMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc2f"},"rt":24304,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":62551,"subject":"PR840","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"01 PM01 PMO O 12 PMF H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc30"},"rt":20613,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":83268,"subject":"PR840","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"Z I I H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc32"},"rt":7456,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":91763,"subject":"PR840","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc33"},"rt":10783,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":102631,"subject":"PR840","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"2E B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc34"},"rt":17153,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":119867,"subject":"PR840","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc35"},"rt":6777,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":126729,"subject":"PR840","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc36"},"rt":7515,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":134334,"subject":"PR840","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc37"},"rt":6773,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":141191,"subject":"PR840","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc38"},"rt":7215,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":148489,"subject":"PR840","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc39"},"rt":12085,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":160662,"subject":"PR840","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"6Z Z Z 04 PM04 PMF F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc3a"},"rt":26307,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":187052,"subject":"PR840","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM03 PMX C G G G G G G B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc3b"},"rt":19619,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":206757,"subject":"PR840","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"F 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc4c"},"rt":11010,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":71286,"subject":"GUQ7E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5bc9f8b677740000016a08b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"09 AMA 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc4d"},"rt":32311,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":103712,"subject":"GUQ7E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5bc9f8b677740000016a08b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G D D C K E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc4e"},"rt":17728,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":121547,"subject":"GUQ7E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5bc9f8b677740000016a08b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"A C 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc4f"},"rt":41014,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":162703,"subject":"GUQ7E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5bc9f8b677740000016a08b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C A A 405 PM04 PMU 2U U F U F Z Z 12 PMZ K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc50"},"rt":147318,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":310140,"subject":"GUQ7E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5bc9f8b677740000016a08b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"0Z Z C C C 10 AMO O O O O A 02 PMC A A F O O O O I I A A I O O 2H E H O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc52"},"rt":8949,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":324587,"subject":"GUQ7E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5bc9f8b677740000016a08b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc53"},"rt":20368,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":345065,"subject":"GUQ7E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5bc9f8b677740000016a08b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B B B F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc54"},"rt":57101,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":402277,"subject":"GUQ7E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5bc9f8b677740000016a08b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PMX X X X X B B E G F Z B J A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc55"},"rt":13223,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":415565,"subject":"GUQ7E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5bc9f8b677740000016a08b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J 2I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc56"},"rt":21265,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":436894,"subject":"GUQ7E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5bc9f8b677740000016a08b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"M F Z Z Z M X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc57"},"rt":7147,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":444099,"subject":"GUQ7E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5bc9f8b677740000016a08b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PM12 PMM M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc58"},"rt":7983,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":452211,"subject":"GUQ7E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5bc9f8b677740000016a08b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc59"},"rt":31561,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":483831,"subject":"GUQ7E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5bc9f8b677740000016a08b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"Z Z C C G E E G F F F H C B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc5a"},"rt":58616,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":542507,"subject":"GUQ7E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5bc9f8b677740000016a08b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"07 PM06 PM05 PM06 PM04 PM03 PMF O O M M X X O O I B O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc5b"},"rt":107992,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":650560,"subject":"GUQ7E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5bc9f8b677740000016a08b5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"101 PM02 PMM X X C B O B 5B M E G X E G B B A J B B B B B B B B F X 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc6c"},"rt":34255,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":351275,"subject":"6JC9F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61230b14a3bcb65c585dfdaa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc6d"},"rt":19943,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":371871,"subject":"6JC9F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61230b14a3bcb65c585dfdaa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc6e"},"rt":59457,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":431672,"subject":"6JC9F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61230b14a3bcb65c585dfdaa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc6f"},"rt":42571,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":474597,"subject":"6JC9F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61230b14a3bcb65c585dfdaa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc70"},"rt":30630,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":505751,"subject":"6JC9F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61230b14a3bcb65c585dfdaa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"6O I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc72"},"rt":15891,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":535664,"subject":"6JC9F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61230b14a3bcb65c585dfdaa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc73"},"rt":20401,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":556456,"subject":"6JC9F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61230b14a3bcb65c585dfdaa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc74"},"rt":22374,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":579235,"subject":"6JC9F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61230b14a3bcb65c585dfdaa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc75"},"rt":68201,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":647775,"subject":"6JC9F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61230b14a3bcb65c585dfdaa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I 4B B B B I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc76"},"rt":23081,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":671555,"subject":"6JC9F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61230b14a3bcb65c585dfdaa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"F F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc77"},"rt":16790,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":688738,"subject":"6JC9F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61230b14a3bcb65c585dfdaa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"09 AM12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc78"},"rt":13374,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":702355,"subject":"6JC9F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61230b14a3bcb65c585dfdaa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc79"},"rt":35550,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":738505,"subject":"6JC9F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61230b14a3bcb65c585dfdaa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"O O X M M Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc7a"},"rt":42054,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":780959,"subject":"6JC9F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61230b14a3bcb65c585dfdaa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc7b"},"rt":26192,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":807546,"subject":"6JC9F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61230b14a3bcb65c585dfdaa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"10 AM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc8c"},"rt":13666,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":57832,"subject":"YD7QB","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PM11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc8d"},"rt":8714,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":66638,"subject":"YD7QB","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc8e"},"rt":18225,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":84945,"subject":"YD7QB","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"2C C A C C A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc8f"},"rt":29992,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":115022,"subject":"YD7QB","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"Z 03 PM02 PM01 PMK K U U U U F F F H H H 01 PMH H H O O 11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc90"},"rt":67010,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":182113,"subject":"YD7QB","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"I 12 PM11 AM12 PM04 PMU U K K H H J F 11 AM11 AMH H F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc92"},"rt":5465,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":190667,"subject":"YD7QB","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc93"},"rt":14676,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":205428,"subject":"YD7QB","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc94"},"rt":25531,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":231052,"subject":"YD7QB","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"H O B B X X E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc95"},"rt":10982,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":242119,"subject":"YD7QB","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc96"},"rt":35412,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":277616,"subject":"YD7QB","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"I B F F B B B F F F C B B B F F E M M X X O O 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc97"},"rt":68418,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":346116,"subject":"YD7QB","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.08333333333333337,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":11,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,C,D,G,H,K,L,M,N,O,P,Z,X","hovered":"203 PM12 PM01 PMM M 12 PM12 PMM 12 PMM M O X X L L P P L H B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc98"},"rt":4752,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":351101,"subject":"YD7QB","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc99"},"rt":11703,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":362891,"subject":"YD7QB","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc9a"},"rt":20030,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":383017,"subject":"YD7QB","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"04 PM03 PMX X C O F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dc9b"},"rt":22080,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":405188,"subject":"YD7QB","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"610b1ad30daed5064d31c2c3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PM01 PMM M B B F 6E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcac"},"rt":43030,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":112436,"subject":"XMCRU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"6101cad0b59a684dcf97be1c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcad"},"rt":70013,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":182575,"subject":"XMCRU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"6101cad0b59a684dcf97be1c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"04 PMG G E E 12 PMD D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcae"},"rt":21488,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":204399,"subject":"XMCRU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"6101cad0b59a684dcf97be1c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,K","hovered":"C O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcaf"},"rt":20078,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":224593,"subject":"XMCRU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"6101cad0b59a684dcf97be1c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,E","hovered":"04 PME E E D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcb0"},"rt":325467,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":550174,"subject":"XMCRU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"6101cad0b59a684dcf97be1c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"I U 03 PMI J H H H J I I F F I I I F F F J O C C C C C C O I I H I I I I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcb2"},"rt":29153,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":585718,"subject":"XMCRU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"6101cad0b59a684dcf97be1c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcb3"},"rt":20886,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":606720,"subject":"XMCRU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"6101cad0b59a684dcf97be1c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"05 PMF I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcb4"},"rt":175846,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":782681,"subject":"XMCRU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"6101cad0b59a684dcf97be1c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"12 PMM F J J A A A E E P L L H H Z Z N N N X J J X O Z Z 4M E G J X E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcb5"},"rt":72364,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":855468,"subject":"XMCRU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"6101cad0b59a684dcf97be1c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"1I B I I E G J I I 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcb6"},"rt":34397,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":890199,"subject":"XMCRU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"6101cad0b59a684dcf97be1c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"H H F F F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcb7"},"rt":27336,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":917660,"subject":"XMCRU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"6101cad0b59a684dcf97be1c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcb8"},"rt":7031,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":924805,"subject":"XMCRU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"6101cad0b59a684dcf97be1c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcb9"},"rt":100817,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1025736,"subject":"XMCRU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"6101cad0b59a684dcf97be1c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"05 PMZ Z Z X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcba"},"rt":12047,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1038111,"subject":"XMCRU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"6101cad0b59a684dcf97be1c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcbb"},"rt":25947,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1064173,"subject":"XMCRU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"6101cad0b59a684dcf97be1c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dccc"},"rt":34001,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":124897,"subject":"QRHO8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62b14dff6abbc73f0f5f090c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"1A 11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dccd"},"rt":8752,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":133760,"subject":"QRHO8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62b14dff6abbc73f0f5f090c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"H 8"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcce"},"rt":37026,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":170897,"subject":"QRHO8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62b14dff6abbc73f0f5f090c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"109 AM10 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dccf"},"rt":73618,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":244547,"subject":"QRHO8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62b14dff6abbc73f0f5f090c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"U F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcd0"},"rt":81338,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":326161,"subject":"QRHO8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62b14dff6abbc73f0f5f090c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"A I Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcd2"},"rt":16034,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":346258,"subject":"QRHO8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62b14dff6abbc73f0f5f090c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcd3"},"rt":15631,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":362001,"subject":"QRHO8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62b14dff6abbc73f0f5f090c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcd4"},"rt":45425,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":407410,"subject":"QRHO8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62b14dff6abbc73f0f5f090c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcd5"},"rt":32734,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":440249,"subject":"QRHO8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62b14dff6abbc73f0f5f090c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I I I 2J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcd6"},"rt":92025,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":532206,"subject":"QRHO8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62b14dff6abbc73f0f5f090c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"11 AMB F F X M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcd7"},"rt":8413,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":540939,"subject":"QRHO8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62b14dff6abbc73f0f5f090c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcd8"},"rt":12997,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":554049,"subject":"QRHO8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62b14dff6abbc73f0f5f090c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcd9"},"rt":45779,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":599942,"subject":"QRHO8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62b14dff6abbc73f0f5f090c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z O X X X B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcda"},"rt":28701,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":628827,"subject":"QRHO8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62b14dff6abbc73f0f5f090c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"J X X 11 AM10 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcdb"},"rt":31641,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":660584,"subject":"QRHO8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62b14dff6abbc73f0f5f090c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"3I X M X X M B B F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcec"},"rt":17204,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":108692,"subject":"EMS03","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"59c0a297c458e800017b5499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dced"},"rt":14040,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":122888,"subject":"EMS03","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"59c0a297c458e800017b5499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcee"},"rt":64249,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":187289,"subject":"EMS03","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"59c0a297c458e800017b5499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C A F F F F C C C A Z 10 AM11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcef"},"rt":54142,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":241858,"subject":"EMS03","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"59c0a297c458e800017b5499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"01 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PMU F F F O O O I F A A 03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcf0"},"rt":95684,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":337705,"subject":"EMS03","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"59c0a297c458e800017b5499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"5I I I 11 AM12 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM03 PMO 11 AM12 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcf2"},"rt":15115,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":360188,"subject":"EMS03","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"59c0a297c458e800017b5499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"46E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcf3"},"rt":25734,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":386086,"subject":"EMS03","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"59c0a297c458e800017b5499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B 01 PM02 PMM F F F Z F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcf4"},"rt":69764,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":456019,"subject":"EMS03","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"59c0a297c458e800017b5499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"7E 11 AM05 PME F F F O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcf5"},"rt":38147,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":494596,"subject":"EMS03","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"59c0a297c458e800017b5499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B F 6B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcf6"},"rt":62362,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":557110,"subject":"EMS03","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"59c0a297c458e800017b5499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"F C F 04 PM04 PM10 AMJ B E 05 PMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcf7"},"rt":42261,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":599814,"subject":"EMS03","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"59c0a297c458e800017b5499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"3J 108 AM09 AMJ J I M 01 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMM M B B B B F I N D N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcf8"},"rt":20531,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":620515,"subject":"EMS03","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"59c0a297c458e800017b5499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"C F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcf9"},"rt":62057,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":682727,"subject":"EMS03","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"59c0a297c458e800017b5499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"X Z Z Z Z Z Z Z X O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcfa"},"rt":47457,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":730605,"subject":"EMS03","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"59c0a297c458e800017b5499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"M 03 PMX 03 PMF F F X E C C F B B M M M X O O O J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dcfb"},"rt":41677,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":772465,"subject":"EMS03","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"59c0a297c458e800017b5499","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PMX X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd0c"},"rt":7011,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":41066,"subject":"EJ13F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd0d"},"rt":11352,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":52547,"subject":"EJ13F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd0e"},"rt":11644,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":64304,"subject":"EJ13F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"10 AMC A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd0f"},"rt":44266,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":108669,"subject":"EJ13F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"04 PMU 04 PM10 AM02 PM03 PM02 PMF O F U U O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd10"},"rt":61106,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":169880,"subject":"EJ13F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I I O O 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PMU 02 PM03 PM12 PMO 12 PM01 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd12"},"rt":9062,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":182077,"subject":"EJ13F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd13"},"rt":21124,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":203327,"subject":"EJ13F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd14"},"rt":25733,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":229160,"subject":"EJ13F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E F X E J J E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd15"},"rt":14576,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":243855,"subject":"EJ13F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I J J J I 10 AMM B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd16"},"rt":44606,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":288558,"subject":"EJ13F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F F B B X X X 04 PMO C F F B 12 PM12 PMF F B B B B B J M M O 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd17"},"rt":11211,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":299868,"subject":"EJ13F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd18"},"rt":6282,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":306247,"subject":"EJ13F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd19"},"rt":29578,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":335922,"subject":"EJ13F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z 04 PMZ X X B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd1a"},"rt":25830,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":361850,"subject":"EJ13F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"X M M X 03 PM03 PMB J J E 11 AM0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd1b"},"rt":49635,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":411580,"subject":"EJ13F","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"610842d3e4ba6eb0276f4a89","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"03 PM02 PMX X X X B B B F B F I I J E 12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PME 6C C C 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd2c"},"rt":19439,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":312989,"subject":"DCKVC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100f11d098c8c861e11cb9f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"4K A A A A A A C C 10 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd2d"},"rt":10991,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":324097,"subject":"DCKVC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100f11d098c8c861e11cb9f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5D D D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd2e"},"rt":11947,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":336151,"subject":"DCKVC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100f11d098c8c861e11cb9f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C 02 PM01 PMC C A A Z 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd2f"},"rt":33962,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":370216,"subject":"DCKVC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100f11d098c8c861e11cb9f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"04 PM04 PM04 PMU Z Z K K K K F A A F F F 01 PMF F U K K K 03 PM03 PMA O 12 PM11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd30"},"rt":64389,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":434716,"subject":"DCKVC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100f11d098c8c861e11cb9f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"201 PMI I O I O I I I I 05 PM03 PMZ F F F F F F O O O O F 01 PMF U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd32"},"rt":158388,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":599577,"subject":"DCKVC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100f11d098c8c861e11cb9f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"J E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd33"},"rt":13523,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":613392,"subject":"DCKVC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100f11d098c8c861e11cb9f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F B F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd34"},"rt":412009,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1025586,"subject":"DCKVC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100f11d098c8c861e11cb9f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"3G B B A A G G B B B B 08 PM08 AME E 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd35"},"rt":155827,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1181702,"subject":"DCKVC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100f11d098c8c861e11cb9f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"Z B X L J J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd36"},"rt":9104,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1191093,"subject":"DCKVC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100f11d098c8c861e11cb9f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"Z X B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd37"},"rt":280434,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1471633,"subject":"DCKVC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100f11d098c8c861e11cb9f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM06 PMB 511C B F M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd38"},"rt":3363,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1475288,"subject":"DCKVC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100f11d098c8c861e11cb9f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd39"},"rt":15627,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1491018,"subject":"DCKVC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100f11d098c8c861e11cb9f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd3a"},"rt":16083,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1507205,"subject":"DCKVC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100f11d098c8c861e11cb9f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B J X 12 PMB 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd3b"},"rt":29593,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1536901,"subject":"DCKVC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"6100f11d098c8c861e11cb9f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X X C F F F E E E 11 AM11 AMG "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd4c"},"rt":26517,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":122689,"subject":"B4AM3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"574ce0a57fd0ec000db73aa6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,O,I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd4d"},"rt":13741,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":136646,"subject":"B4AM3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"574ce0a57fd0ec000db73aa6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd4e"},"rt":25068,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":161940,"subject":"B4AM3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"574ce0a57fd0ec000db73aa6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd4f"},"rt":9075,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":171125,"subject":"B4AM3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"574ce0a57fd0ec000db73aa6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd50"},"rt":47445,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":218848,"subject":"B4AM3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"574ce0a57fd0ec000db73aa6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,H","hovered":"O O 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd52"},"rt":9543,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":239706,"subject":"B4AM3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"574ce0a57fd0ec000db73aa6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd53"},"rt":17451,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":257267,"subject":"B4AM3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"574ce0a57fd0ec000db73aa6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd54"},"rt":53141,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":310514,"subject":"B4AM3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"574ce0a57fd0ec000db73aa6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"I E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd55"},"rt":20052,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":330844,"subject":"B4AM3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"574ce0a57fd0ec000db73aa6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd56"},"rt":16322,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":347275,"subject":"B4AM3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"574ce0a57fd0ec000db73aa6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd57"},"rt":12766,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":360267,"subject":"B4AM3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"574ce0a57fd0ec000db73aa6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd58"},"rt":4711,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":365213,"subject":"B4AM3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"574ce0a57fd0ec000db73aa6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd59"},"rt":20132,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":385567,"subject":"B4AM3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"574ce0a57fd0ec000db73aa6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd5a"},"rt":25813,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":411484,"subject":"B4AM3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"574ce0a57fd0ec000db73aa6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd5b"},"rt":47050,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":458645,"subject":"B4AM3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"574ce0a57fd0ec000db73aa6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd6c"},"rt":45571,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":192714,"subject":"BWJ8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5dd4767b32288646716dc98a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMA 110 AM11 AM11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd6d"},"rt":53896,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":246651,"subject":"BWJ8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5dd4767b32288646716dc98a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"11 AMK K D D D E E F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd6e"},"rt":18260,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":264959,"subject":"BWJ8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5dd4767b32288646716dc98a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd6f"},"rt":25822,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":290820,"subject":"BWJ8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5dd4767b32288646716dc98a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PME E E I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd70"},"rt":25911,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":316785,"subject":"BWJ8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5dd4767b32288646716dc98a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"I I O O 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd72"},"rt":30110,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":357993,"subject":"BWJ8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5dd4767b32288646716dc98a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"05 PM01 PMI E 12E E E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd73"},"rt":51932,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":410237,"subject":"BWJ8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5dd4767b32288646716dc98a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"I B B B B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd74"},"rt":90678,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":500985,"subject":"BWJ8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5dd4767b32288646716dc98a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd75"},"rt":75473,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":576816,"subject":"BWJ8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5dd4767b32288646716dc98a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd76"},"rt":68494,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":646681,"subject":"BWJ8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5dd4767b32288646716dc98a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"P","hovered":"11 AM12 PMM F F 9B B F F Z Z Z L L P Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd77"},"rt":16868,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":664231,"subject":"BWJ8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5dd4767b32288646716dc98a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd78"},"rt":12222,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":676495,"subject":"BWJ8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5dd4767b32288646716dc98a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd79"},"rt":131675,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":808237,"subject":"BWJ8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5dd4767b32288646716dc98a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L,P","hovered":"I O O Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd7a"},"rt":21881,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":830967,"subject":"BWJ8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5dd4767b32288646716dc98a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,O","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PMO "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd7b"},"rt":50912,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":881919,"subject":"BWJ8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"5dd4767b32288646716dc98a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,K","hovered":"02 PMX X X X X X O 02 PMC C 11"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd8c"},"rt":13960,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":191443,"subject":"66H6K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61138937023e260faf9d04b4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"09 AM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd8d"},"rt":11155,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":202699,"subject":"66H6K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61138937023e260faf9d04b4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"C A E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd8e"},"rt":41093,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":243887,"subject":"66H6K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61138937023e260faf9d04b4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"C C A C C C C C K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd8f"},"rt":94163,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":338416,"subject":"66H6K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61138937023e260faf9d04b4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"A D D D K E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd90"},"rt":64638,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":403254,"subject":"66H6K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61138937023e260faf9d04b4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd92"},"rt":75191,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":492483,"subject":"66H6K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61138937023e260faf9d04b4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G,H","hovered":"F F C O 04 PM9H Z N 06 PMC O G C C O C O O X O M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd93"},"rt":32826,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":525530,"subject":"66H6K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61138937023e260faf9d04b4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"5B G M B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd94"},"rt":36937,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":562554,"subject":"66H6K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61138937023e260faf9d04b4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"3B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd95"},"rt":66347,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":628984,"subject":"66H6K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61138937023e260faf9d04b4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"C H H E I I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd96"},"rt":19527,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":649008,"subject":"66H6K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61138937023e260faf9d04b4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G G F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd97"},"rt":6082,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":655185,"subject":"66H6K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61138937023e260faf9d04b4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd98"},"rt":7522,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":662804,"subject":"66H6K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61138937023e260faf9d04b4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd99"},"rt":132860,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":795763,"subject":"66H6K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61138937023e260faf9d04b4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G","hovered":"C G Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd9a"},"rt":7165,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":803188,"subject":"66H6K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61138937023e260faf9d04b4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dd9b"},"rt":73812,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":877094,"subject":"66H6K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"61138937023e260faf9d04b4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G,M","hovered":"710M M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddac"},"rt":15961,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":173829,"subject":"W0BU0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60b9af795939f976cb74232a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"Z 08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddad"},"rt":11595,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":185502,"subject":"W0BU0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60b9af795939f976cb74232a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddae"},"rt":185620,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":371197,"subject":"W0BU0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60b9af795939f976cb74232a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A A 08 AM09 AMA X 08 AM08 AMC 09 AM09 AMC C A Z Z C A F 11 AM08 AM08 AM09 AMC C C 11 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddaf"},"rt":56376,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":427752,"subject":"W0BU0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60b9af795939f976cb74232a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"12 PM01 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM08 AM04 PM09 AMA K 05 PM04 PMH H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddb0"},"rt":29868,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":457726,"subject":"W0BU0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60b9af795939f976cb74232a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"Z 04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM01 PMK O O 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddb2"},"rt":15578,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":491746,"subject":"W0BU0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60b9af795939f976cb74232a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"09 AM08 AME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddb3"},"rt":41594,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":533423,"subject":"W0BU0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60b9af795939f976cb74232a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"5F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddb4"},"rt":121861,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":655366,"subject":"W0BU0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60b9af795939f976cb74232a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B 3F B B F E E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddb5"},"rt":44414,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":699971,"subject":"W0BU0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60b9af795939f976cb74232a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J J J J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddb6"},"rt":214793,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":914842,"subject":"W0BU0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60b9af795939f976cb74232a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X F F 04 PMO X X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddb7"},"rt":24140,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":939232,"subject":"W0BU0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60b9af795939f976cb74232a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"11 AM11 AM12 PMB F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddb8"},"rt":23381,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":962698,"subject":"W0BU0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60b9af795939f976cb74232a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"08 AM11 AM01 PMF B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddb9"},"rt":46168,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1008946,"subject":"W0BU0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60b9af795939f976cb74232a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"H Z Z Z O X M B B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddba"},"rt":18640,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1027664,"subject":"W0BU0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60b9af795939f976cb74232a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddbb"},"rt":212034,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1239787,"subject":"W0BU0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"60b9af795939f976cb74232a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X X B B F 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddcc"},"rt":23784,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":203717,"subject":"TCJCD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"579a4c6a82f7f90001ee9d92","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"J I J 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddcd"},"rt":12825,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":216781,"subject":"TCJCD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"579a4c6a82f7f90001ee9d92","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddce"},"rt":27210,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":244188,"subject":"TCJCD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"579a4c6a82f7f90001ee9d92","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,U,B","hovered":"G G F C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddcf"},"rt":40795,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":285182,"subject":"TCJCD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"579a4c6a82f7f90001ee9d92","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"44E E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddd0"},"rt":184610,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":470020,"subject":"TCJCD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"579a4c6a82f7f90001ee9d92","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C I O I O O O H I I O O O O I I O O U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddd2"},"rt":9741,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":490233,"subject":"TCJCD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"579a4c6a82f7f90001ee9d92","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddd3"},"rt":15960,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":506509,"subject":"TCJCD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"579a4c6a82f7f90001ee9d92","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddd4"},"rt":65990,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":572750,"subject":"TCJCD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"579a4c6a82f7f90001ee9d92","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"X X F J E J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddd5"},"rt":28324,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":601317,"subject":"TCJCD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"579a4c6a82f7f90001ee9d92","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddd6"},"rt":59902,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":661402,"subject":"TCJCD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"579a4c6a82f7f90001ee9d92","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddd7"},"rt":13357,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":674874,"subject":"TCJCD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"579a4c6a82f7f90001ee9d92","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"E 01 PM12 PMM B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddd8"},"rt":11318,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":686266,"subject":"TCJCD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"579a4c6a82f7f90001ee9d92","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"X X B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddd9"},"rt":88256,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":774616,"subject":"TCJCD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"579a4c6a82f7f90001ee9d92","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"O Z Z F Z E B B B O 03 PMX X J 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddda"},"rt":28357,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":803214,"subject":"TCJCD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"579a4c6a82f7f90001ee9d92","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B B B B B B O 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dddb"},"rt":82381,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":885698,"subject":"TCJCD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"579a4c6a82f7f90001ee9d92","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"X X 6E G 702 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddec"},"rt":21341,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":97990,"subject":"VULTG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5e59ee3a2bff541fcf05d86e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMA 11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dded"},"rt":25955,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":124064,"subject":"VULTG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5e59ee3a2bff541fcf05d86e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E 04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddee"},"rt":24470,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":148656,"subject":"VULTG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5e59ee3a2bff541fcf05d86e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"4C A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddef"},"rt":37530,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":186312,"subject":"VULTG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5e59ee3a2bff541fcf05d86e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C Z U Z Z F F O O F F 01 PM12 PMZ Z A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddf0"},"rt":71123,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":257561,"subject":"VULTG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5e59ee3a2bff541fcf05d86e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddf2"},"rt":10461,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":274841,"subject":"VULTG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5e59ee3a2bff541fcf05d86e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddf3"},"rt":19473,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":294444,"subject":"VULTG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5e59ee3a2bff541fcf05d86e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddf4"},"rt":44414,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":338976,"subject":"VULTG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5e59ee3a2bff541fcf05d86e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"08 AMB B E E I 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddf5"},"rt":12370,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":351466,"subject":"VULTG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5e59ee3a2bff541fcf05d86e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddf6"},"rt":46084,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":397667,"subject":"VULTG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5e59ee3a2bff541fcf05d86e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddf7"},"rt":10007,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":407792,"subject":"VULTG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5e59ee3a2bff541fcf05d86e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddf8"},"rt":12168,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":420174,"subject":"VULTG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5e59ee3a2bff541fcf05d86e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddf9"},"rt":23299,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":443722,"subject":"VULTG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5e59ee3a2bff541fcf05d86e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddfa"},"rt":31644,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":475501,"subject":"VULTG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5e59ee3a2bff541fcf05d86e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"08 AM03 PMX B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ddfb"},"rt":70355,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":545977,"subject":"VULTG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"5e59ee3a2bff541fcf05d86e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de0c"},"rt":11414,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":132107,"subject":"4T6NO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"57813c9d275be60001357faa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"110 AMF F 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de0d"},"rt":11790,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":144010,"subject":"4T6NO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"57813c9d275be60001357faa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"2C A K D K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de0e"},"rt":49661,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":193726,"subject":"4T6NO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"57813c9d275be60001357faa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"4F A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de0f"},"rt":116083,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":309861,"subject":"4T6NO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"57813c9d275be60001357faa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"03 PM04 PMA A F H K O O K F F G B U G G H E C A A 09 AM08 AM102 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de10"},"rt":92799,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":403335,"subject":"4T6NO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"57813c9d275be60001357faa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"C A U F A C A K F F O I I E K C 3C A U I K C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de12"},"rt":6744,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":416099,"subject":"4T6NO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"57813c9d275be60001357faa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de13"},"rt":22338,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":438507,"subject":"4T6NO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"57813c9d275be60001357faa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F B B B B 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de14"},"rt":26691,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":465281,"subject":"4T6NO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"57813c9d275be60001357faa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"6E J 2E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de15"},"rt":24370,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":489787,"subject":"4T6NO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"57813c9d275be60001357faa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"2J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de16"},"rt":91029,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":580872,"subject":"4T6NO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"57813c9d275be60001357faa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"4C F Z Z Z B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de17"},"rt":10066,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":591506,"subject":"4T6NO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"57813c9d275be60001357faa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de18"},"rt":11259,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":602883,"subject":"4T6NO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"57813c9d275be60001357faa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"G H Z O B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de19"},"rt":31057,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":634074,"subject":"4T6NO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"57813c9d275be60001357faa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"3M O Z 4Z Z Z G C 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de1a"},"rt":34436,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":668629,"subject":"4T6NO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"57813c9d275be60001357faa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"01 PM12 PM01 PM4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de1b"},"rt":62835,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":731628,"subject":"4T6NO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"63058a8765a9341fb889e9f8","sona_id":"57813c9d275be60001357faa","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,G","hovered":"4M 10114B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de2c"},"rt":34467,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":118901,"subject":"4G5CC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62fd86ae7c7fbcb2c2d31583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AM11 AM1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de2d"},"rt":21230,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":140189,"subject":"4G5CC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62fd86ae7c7fbcb2c2d31583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A E O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de2e"},"rt":37642,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":177890,"subject":"4G5CC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62fd86ae7c7fbcb2c2d31583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"O A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de2f"},"rt":53767,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":231721,"subject":"4G5CC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62fd86ae7c7fbcb2c2d31583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"02 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de30"},"rt":138441,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":370222,"subject":"4G5CC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62fd86ae7c7fbcb2c2d31583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"2I I I O O I U Z H U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de32"},"rt":11892,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":387405,"subject":"4G5CC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62fd86ae7c7fbcb2c2d31583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de33"},"rt":30304,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":417805,"subject":"4G5CC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62fd86ae7c7fbcb2c2d31583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4B B 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de34"},"rt":53812,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":471702,"subject":"4G5CC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62fd86ae7c7fbcb2c2d31583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"6X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de35"},"rt":15984,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":487746,"subject":"4G5CC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62fd86ae7c7fbcb2c2d31583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"F O O O X J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de36"},"rt":33765,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":521569,"subject":"4G5CC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62fd86ae7c7fbcb2c2d31583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"H H O O F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de37"},"rt":9926,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":531558,"subject":"4G5CC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62fd86ae7c7fbcb2c2d31583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"211 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de38"},"rt":8658,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":540314,"subject":"4G5CC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62fd86ae7c7fbcb2c2d31583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de39"},"rt":52046,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":592415,"subject":"4G5CC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62fd86ae7c7fbcb2c2d31583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"O O O Z Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de3a"},"rt":37993,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":630472,"subject":"4G5CC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62fd86ae7c7fbcb2c2d31583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"08 AM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de3b"},"rt":56198,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":686730,"subject":"4G5CC","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"630585f90861b070751c521d","sona_id":"62fd86ae7c7fbcb2c2d31583","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"01 PM02 PMJ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de4c"},"rt":28854,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":193296,"subject":"U2H8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ebb08645a22c70c2ba793e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de4d"},"rt":12692,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":206119,"subject":"U2H8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ebb08645a22c70c2ba793e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de4e"},"rt":9309,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":215565,"subject":"U2H8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ebb08645a22c70c2ba793e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de4f"},"rt":10246,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":225958,"subject":"U2H8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ebb08645a22c70c2ba793e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de50"},"rt":17629,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":243722,"subject":"U2H8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ebb08645a22c70c2ba793e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de52"},"rt":7809,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":257190,"subject":"U2H8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ebb08645a22c70c2ba793e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de53"},"rt":38941,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":296259,"subject":"U2H8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ebb08645a22c70c2ba793e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de54"},"rt":61164,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":357555,"subject":"U2H8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ebb08645a22c70c2ba793e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"J C F F B B G C C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de55"},"rt":40877,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":399085,"subject":"U2H8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ebb08645a22c70c2ba793e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de56"},"rt":8634,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":407861,"subject":"U2H8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ebb08645a22c70c2ba793e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de57"},"rt":9664,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":417674,"subject":"U2H8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ebb08645a22c70c2ba793e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de58"},"rt":7152,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":424974,"subject":"U2H8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ebb08645a22c70c2ba793e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de59"},"rt":9302,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":434409,"subject":"U2H8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ebb08645a22c70c2ba793e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de5a"},"rt":8696,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":443249,"subject":"U2H8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ebb08645a22c70c2ba793e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de5b"},"rt":14501,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":457885,"subject":"U2H8G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ebb08645a22c70c2ba793e4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"3X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de6c"},"rt":11265,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":62966,"subject":"OP4AD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e029395b324b1a05508694","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de6d"},"rt":22140,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":85146,"subject":"OP4AD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e029395b324b1a05508694","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,E","hovered":"U H E J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de6e"},"rt":24787,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":109977,"subject":"OP4AD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e029395b324b1a05508694","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"A A C O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de6f"},"rt":55763,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":165780,"subject":"OP4AD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e029395b324b1a05508694","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"04 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM008 AM02 PM01 PM12 PM10 AM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de70"},"rt":11931,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":177741,"subject":"OP4AD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e029395b324b1a05508694","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de72"},"rt":12353,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":195737,"subject":"OP4AD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e029395b324b1a05508694","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de73"},"rt":11554,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":207327,"subject":"OP4AD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e029395b324b1a05508694","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de74"},"rt":16258,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":223624,"subject":"OP4AD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e029395b324b1a05508694","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de75"},"rt":12505,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":236161,"subject":"OP4AD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e029395b324b1a05508694","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de76"},"rt":11250,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":247441,"subject":"OP4AD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e029395b324b1a05508694","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F 5I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de77"},"rt":6043,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":253522,"subject":"OP4AD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e029395b324b1a05508694","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de78"},"rt":7093,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":260848,"subject":"OP4AD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e029395b324b1a05508694","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"09 AMB B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de79"},"rt":11007,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":271939,"subject":"OP4AD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e029395b324b1a05508694","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de7a"},"rt":9358,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":281347,"subject":"OP4AD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e029395b324b1a05508694","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"02 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de7b"},"rt":11533,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":292919,"subject":"OP4AD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e029395b324b1a05508694","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.33333333333333337,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G,X","hovered":"M X 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de8c"},"rt":16801,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":162007,"subject":"5D438","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a7f44ec8fe2dc000105c9b0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A A A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de8d"},"rt":10069,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":172319,"subject":"5D438","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a7f44ec8fe2dc000105c9b0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"0A A U E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de8e"},"rt":97236,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":270013,"subject":"5D438","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a7f44ec8fe2dc000105c9b0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C 10 AM10 AM08 PM07 PM06 PM05 PM05 PM04 PMZ O K 08 AM09 AMI I C C C A U 02 PM01 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM5C A C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de8f"},"rt":81355,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":352108,"subject":"5D438","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a7f44ec8fe2dc000105c9b0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"08 AM02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de90"},"rt":74863,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":427923,"subject":"5D438","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a7f44ec8fe2dc000105c9b0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de92"},"rt":9403,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":451053,"subject":"5D438","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a7f44ec8fe2dc000105c9b0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de93"},"rt":14304,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":465594,"subject":"5D438","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a7f44ec8fe2dc000105c9b0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de94"},"rt":44431,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":510258,"subject":"5D438","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a7f44ec8fe2dc000105c9b0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"1X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de95"},"rt":38152,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":548642,"subject":"5D438","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a7f44ec8fe2dc000105c9b0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de96"},"rt":13984,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":562857,"subject":"5D438","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a7f44ec8fe2dc000105c9b0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PMF Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de97"},"rt":9989,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":573082,"subject":"5D438","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a7f44ec8fe2dc000105c9b0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de98"},"rt":10680,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":583993,"subject":"5D438","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a7f44ec8fe2dc000105c9b0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"08 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de99"},"rt":23922,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":608145,"subject":"5D438","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a7f44ec8fe2dc000105c9b0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"11 AM12 PMZ 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de9a"},"rt":36713,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":645089,"subject":"5D438","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a7f44ec8fe2dc000105c9b0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"01 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972de9b"},"rt":25497,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":670817,"subject":"5D438","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a7f44ec8fe2dc000105c9b0","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"01 PM02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972deac"},"rt":58838,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":261297,"subject":"PGGF2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e6e9bffdcd02bee9c6ebbf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AM11 AMA A A A 11 AMA C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dead"},"rt":60495,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":322297,"subject":"PGGF2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e6e9bffdcd02bee9c6ebbf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D E E E J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972deae"},"rt":106000,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":430521,"subject":"PGGF2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e6e9bffdcd02bee9c6ebbf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"2210 AM11 AM12 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM11 AMC C A Z 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972deaf"},"rt":79148,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":510960,"subject":"PGGF2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e6e9bffdcd02bee9c6ebbf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"01 PM02 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM09 AM09 AM10 AM01 PM02 PMU "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972deb0"},"rt":36442,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":548659,"subject":"PGGF2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e6e9bffdcd02bee9c6ebbf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972deb2"},"rt":15894,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":588617,"subject":"PGGF2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e6e9bffdcd02bee9c6ebbf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972deb3"},"rt":69046,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":658005,"subject":"PGGF2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e6e9bffdcd02bee9c6ebbf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"I F F B B I F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972deb4"},"rt":186215,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":845856,"subject":"PGGF2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e6e9bffdcd02bee9c6ebbf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B X 08 PM07 PMX X O E E X X X X Z Z E E G G E E E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972deb5"},"rt":376422,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1226639,"subject":"PGGF2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e6e9bffdcd02bee9c6ebbf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J H H H H H K A A 12 PM11 AML P 7I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972deb6"},"rt":174609,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1403169,"subject":"PGGF2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e6e9bffdcd02bee9c6ebbf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"I B F B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972deb7"},"rt":16106,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1421810,"subject":"PGGF2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e6e9bffdcd02bee9c6ebbf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972deb8"},"rt":8884,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1431086,"subject":"PGGF2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e6e9bffdcd02bee9c6ebbf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972deb9"},"rt":102648,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1535594,"subject":"PGGF2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e6e9bffdcd02bee9c6ebbf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"B O Z X X X O F F Z 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972deba"},"rt":48430,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1585385,"subject":"PGGF2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e6e9bffdcd02bee9c6ebbf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM02 PM03 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972debb"},"rt":93835,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1679592,"subject":"PGGF2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62e6e9bffdcd02bee9c6ebbf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972decc"},"rt":15645,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":124224,"subject":"Y7FVM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5c12b0ba17e18d0001e7629e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972decd"},"rt":9369,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":133659,"subject":"Y7FVM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5c12b0ba17e18d0001e7629e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"K E 03 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dece"},"rt":61983,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":195683,"subject":"Y7FVM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5c12b0ba17e18d0001e7629e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X,U","hovered":"Z B B 09 AM11 AMC C C C C 02 PM01 PMU U 01 PM02 PM02 PMC 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972decf"},"rt":14513,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":210340,"subject":"Y7FVM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5c12b0ba17e18d0001e7629e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ded0"},"rt":74686,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":285085,"subject":"Y7FVM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5c12b0ba17e18d0001e7629e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"01 PM12 PM06 PM05 PM03 PM02 PMK B B U 12 PMO O I O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ded2"},"rt":213402,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":505905,"subject":"Y7FVM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5c12b0ba17e18d0001e7629e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"F M J J 09 AMM M 12 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM11 AMX K K K X 11 AM03 PM03 PMC C 01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM04 PMZ 04 PM04 PM05 PM05 PM04 PM04 PM05 PM05 PM05 PM05 PMZ Z 05 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ded3"},"rt":139715,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":645761,"subject":"Y7FVM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5c12b0ba17e18d0001e7629e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ded4"},"rt":141640,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":787555,"subject":"Y7FVM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5c12b0ba17e18d0001e7629e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"F G F B X X M 12 PM12 PMM M J B B 12 PM12 PMJ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ded5"},"rt":53333,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":841052,"subject":"Y7FVM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5c12b0ba17e18d0001e7629e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"2J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ded6"},"rt":42355,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":883458,"subject":"Y7FVM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5c12b0ba17e18d0001e7629e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ded7"},"rt":11278,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":894796,"subject":"Y7FVM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5c12b0ba17e18d0001e7629e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ded8"},"rt":14458,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":909330,"subject":"Y7FVM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5c12b0ba17e18d0001e7629e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972ded9"},"rt":128495,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1037868,"subject":"Y7FVM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5c12b0ba17e18d0001e7629e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"B F 05 PM04 PMZ F I 4791008 AM008 AM09 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972deda"},"rt":105749,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1143759,"subject":"Y7FVM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5c12b0ba17e18d0001e7629e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dedb"},"rt":59400,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1203286,"subject":"Y7FVM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5c12b0ba17e18d0001e7629e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972deec"},"rt":17276,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":84299,"subject":"K5DGU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6305b8d5ac4df0bfd1e5b335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"7F Z A A 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972deed"},"rt":10898,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":95275,"subject":"K5DGU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6305b8d5ac4df0bfd1e5b335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"C A 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972deee"},"rt":48841,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":144194,"subject":"K5DGU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6305b8d5ac4df0bfd1e5b335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"3C 02 PM02 PMA A C A A A A 111 AMC C 09 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972deef"},"rt":14159,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":158431,"subject":"K5DGU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6305b8d5ac4df0bfd1e5b335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PME E D E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972def0"},"rt":10691,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":169198,"subject":"K5DGU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6305b8d5ac4df0bfd1e5b335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"U I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972def2"},"rt":10583,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":185213,"subject":"K5DGU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6305b8d5ac4df0bfd1e5b335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972def3"},"rt":13035,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":198333,"subject":"K5DGU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6305b8d5ac4df0bfd1e5b335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F B B B B F 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972def4"},"rt":76267,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":274678,"subject":"K5DGU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6305b8d5ac4df0bfd1e5b335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E F F B B B B B O I 1M 01 PM04 PMJ J 02 PM10 AMG J J E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972def5"},"rt":21878,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":296783,"subject":"K5DGU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6305b8d5ac4df0bfd1e5b335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972def6"},"rt":26032,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":322892,"subject":"K5DGU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6305b8d5ac4df0bfd1e5b335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B B B B F F X 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972def7"},"rt":6320,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":329290,"subject":"K5DGU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6305b8d5ac4df0bfd1e5b335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M M 01 PM12 PMB F I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972def8"},"rt":6505,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":335872,"subject":"K5DGU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6305b8d5ac4df0bfd1e5b335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972def9"},"rt":71495,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":407444,"subject":"K5DGU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6305b8d5ac4df0bfd1e5b335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"Z Z Z 05 PM04 PMB O 1M Z Z H F F X 05 PM05 PMN N Z H H Z Z N N N N Z H 06 PM05 PM04 PM2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972defa"},"rt":17102,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":424766,"subject":"K5DGU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6305b8d5ac4df0bfd1e5b335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"10 AM11 AM12 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972defb"},"rt":18032,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":442872,"subject":"K5DGU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6305b8d5ac4df0bfd1e5b335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,M","hovered":"08 AM09 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM01 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df0c"},"rt":74725,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":268643,"subject":"5KL7Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614eb0a92921d8c1e64f4873","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df0d"},"rt":17126,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":286041,"subject":"5KL7Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614eb0a92921d8c1e64f4873","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df0e"},"rt":14811,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":300961,"subject":"5KL7Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614eb0a92921d8c1e64f4873","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df0f"},"rt":31061,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":332168,"subject":"5KL7Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614eb0a92921d8c1e64f4873","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df10"},"rt":55845,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":388130,"subject":"5KL7Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614eb0a92921d8c1e64f4873","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df12"},"rt":9329,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":408960,"subject":"5KL7Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614eb0a92921d8c1e64f4873","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df13"},"rt":18837,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":427911,"subject":"5KL7Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614eb0a92921d8c1e64f4873","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df14"},"rt":61078,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":489094,"subject":"5KL7Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614eb0a92921d8c1e64f4873","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df15"},"rt":22524,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":511933,"subject":"5KL7Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614eb0a92921d8c1e64f4873","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df16"},"rt":80616,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":592648,"subject":"5KL7Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614eb0a92921d8c1e64f4873","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df17"},"rt":18003,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":610897,"subject":"5KL7Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614eb0a92921d8c1e64f4873","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df18"},"rt":9158,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":620156,"subject":"5KL7Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614eb0a92921d8c1e64f4873","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df19"},"rt":34083,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":654341,"subject":"5KL7Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614eb0a92921d8c1e64f4873","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df1a"},"rt":36639,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":691091,"subject":"5KL7Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614eb0a92921d8c1e64f4873","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df1b"},"rt":55376,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":746583,"subject":"5KL7Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614eb0a92921d8c1e64f4873","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df2c"},"rt":11377,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":64860,"subject":"DBJU1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f4fd146ee39f70f490889c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df2d"},"rt":6852,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":71795,"subject":"DBJU1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f4fd146ee39f70f490889c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"08 AM11 AM02 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df2e"},"rt":28565,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":100435,"subject":"DBJU1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f4fd146ee39f70f490889c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"09 AMC C 10 AMC C A Z Z 09 AM10 AM10 AM10 AM10 AM10 AM10 AM10 AM10 AM12 PM12 PM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df2f"},"rt":30296,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":130795,"subject":"DBJU1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f4fd146ee39f70f490889c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"09 AMZ 02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMZ Z U U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df30"},"rt":33938,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":164811,"subject":"DBJU1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f4fd146ee39f70f490889c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I X I I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df32"},"rt":9952,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":178733,"subject":"DBJU1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f4fd146ee39f70f490889c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df33"},"rt":9098,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":187891,"subject":"DBJU1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f4fd146ee39f70f490889c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B B F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df34"},"rt":63066,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":251092,"subject":"DBJU1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f4fd146ee39f70f490889c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,E,G","hovered":"L E E E B B X X B B B B X X J J 04 PMG G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df35"},"rt":28145,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":279548,"subject":"DBJU1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f4fd146ee39f70f490889c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AMJ J J I I I J J I I I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df36"},"rt":21126,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":300732,"subject":"DBJU1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f4fd146ee39f70f490889c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F B B B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df37"},"rt":9428,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":310219,"subject":"DBJU1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f4fd146ee39f70f490889c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df38"},"rt":9502,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":319795,"subject":"DBJU1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f4fd146ee39f70f490889c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df39"},"rt":43094,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":365915,"subject":"DBJU1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f4fd146ee39f70f490889c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"Z F F I I B N N N F E G C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df3a"},"rt":75284,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":441259,"subject":"DBJU1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f4fd146ee39f70f490889c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM02 PMM X X X B B O I E E E 10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM10 AM12 PM01 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM02 PMM J B B F F F F E F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df3b"},"rt":25870,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":467451,"subject":"DBJU1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f4fd146ee39f70f490889c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"008 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM02 PMX X X B B F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df4c"},"rt":32212,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":115399,"subject":"1NHXQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62d85abed427caa15e2d6093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df4d"},"rt":12498,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":127991,"subject":"1NHXQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62d85abed427caa15e2d6093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df4e"},"rt":14324,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":142466,"subject":"1NHXQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62d85abed427caa15e2d6093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df4f"},"rt":20818,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":163399,"subject":"1NHXQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62d85abed427caa15e2d6093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"05 PM04 PM04 PM04 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df50"},"rt":46166,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":209638,"subject":"1NHXQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62d85abed427caa15e2d6093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,H","hovered":"O H H O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df52"},"rt":17356,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":235918,"subject":"1NHXQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62d85abed427caa15e2d6093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df53"},"rt":23591,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":259568,"subject":"1NHXQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62d85abed427caa15e2d6093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df54"},"rt":65224,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":324853,"subject":"1NHXQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62d85abed427caa15e2d6093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L","hovered":"O X G E G L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df55"},"rt":27377,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":352586,"subject":"1NHXQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62d85abed427caa15e2d6093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B B B F J J M J J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df56"},"rt":13243,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":365951,"subject":"1NHXQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62d85abed427caa15e2d6093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df57"},"rt":11362,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":377381,"subject":"1NHXQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62d85abed427caa15e2d6093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df58"},"rt":6693,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":384132,"subject":"1NHXQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62d85abed427caa15e2d6093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df59"},"rt":22001,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":406354,"subject":"1NHXQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62d85abed427caa15e2d6093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df5a"},"rt":17386,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":423855,"subject":"1NHXQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62d85abed427caa15e2d6093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"M 03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df5b"},"rt":15285,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":439265,"subject":"1NHXQ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62d85abed427caa15e2d6093","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df6c"},"rt":19722,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":49461,"subject":"3C1UG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"627e7b6d33e1df14160c05ba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df6d"},"rt":12876,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":62407,"subject":"3C1UG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"627e7b6d33e1df14160c05ba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"B B K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df6e"},"rt":21774,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":84250,"subject":"3C1UG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"627e7b6d33e1df14160c05ba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"U C 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df6f"},"rt":9830,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":94150,"subject":"3C1UG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"627e7b6d33e1df14160c05ba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"05 PM04 PM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df70"},"rt":19781,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":113999,"subject":"3C1UG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"627e7b6d33e1df14160c05ba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"10I O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df72"},"rt":17756,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":141074,"subject":"3C1UG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"627e7b6d33e1df14160c05ba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df73"},"rt":37058,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":178202,"subject":"3C1UG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"627e7b6d33e1df14160c05ba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C C F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df74"},"rt":42001,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":220281,"subject":"3C1UG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"627e7b6d33e1df14160c05ba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"G H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df75"},"rt":26900,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":247249,"subject":"3C1UG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"627e7b6d33e1df14160c05ba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df76"},"rt":20108,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":267428,"subject":"3C1UG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"627e7b6d33e1df14160c05ba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"H B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df77"},"rt":14424,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":281920,"subject":"3C1UG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"627e7b6d33e1df14160c05ba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df78"},"rt":12842,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":294830,"subject":"3C1UG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"627e7b6d33e1df14160c05ba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"M F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df79"},"rt":15517,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":310424,"subject":"3C1UG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"627e7b6d33e1df14160c05ba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df7a"},"rt":9651,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":320144,"subject":"3C1UG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"627e7b6d33e1df14160c05ba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df7b"},"rt":12224,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":332434,"subject":"3C1UG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"627e7b6d33e1df14160c05ba","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"06 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df8c"},"rt":18684,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":123508,"subject":"4AKA2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5e3244f5bac19521aee1a0de","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AM11 AMA A 608 AM011 AM11 AMA A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df8d"},"rt":25753,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":149359,"subject":"4AKA2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5e3244f5bac19521aee1a0de","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"09 AM11 AM11 AM6K D D D D 08 PME D J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df8e"},"rt":33825,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":183282,"subject":"4AKA2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5e3244f5bac19521aee1a0de","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"8C C 2C C C C D E E 04 PMO A C C C C A Z Z Z A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df8f"},"rt":107372,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":290749,"subject":"4AKA2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5e3244f5bac19521aee1a0de","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"03 PM04 PMX K K 03 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PMU U U A C C Z F G F F F F 01 PMH 01 PM01 PMH O O O O 11 AMZ 04 PM04 PM04 PMU U U U U Z 12 PMF F O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df90"},"rt":109923,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":401077,"subject":"4AKA2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5e3244f5bac19521aee1a0de","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"O F O I I I 11 AMI I 07 PM01 PM11 AM301 PM02 PM03 PM01 PMF F 03 PMU U 01 PM12 PM11 AM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df92"},"rt":11454,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":421342,"subject":"4AKA2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5e3244f5bac19521aee1a0de","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df93"},"rt":17420,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":438856,"subject":"4AKA2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5e3244f5bac19521aee1a0de","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"E E 11 AMF B B B B F F B B B B B B 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df94"},"rt":65506,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":504459,"subject":"4AKA2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5e3244f5bac19521aee1a0de","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B G G E F F E G 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df95"},"rt":14750,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":519518,"subject":"4AKA2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5e3244f5bac19521aee1a0de","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"77I B 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df96"},"rt":33134,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":552747,"subject":"4AKA2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5e3244f5bac19521aee1a0de","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F Z 04 PM04 PMO B B M 02 PM02 PMX X J X X F F F 11 AM11 AME E E I 09 AM09 AMJ J J 10 AMJ 12 PM12 PMB 6F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df97"},"rt":11536,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":564387,"subject":"4AKA2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5e3244f5bac19521aee1a0de","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B 10 AM09 AM12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df98"},"rt":5800,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":570284,"subject":"4AKA2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5e3244f5bac19521aee1a0de","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df99"},"rt":36899,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":607277,"subject":"4AKA2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5e3244f5bac19521aee1a0de","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z 04 PMZ Z H H G G F I I B B O F F C C C F F M X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df9a"},"rt":34957,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":642337,"subject":"4AKA2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5e3244f5bac19521aee1a0de","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"X 01 PM03 PMO G 5H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972df9b"},"rt":28873,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":671307,"subject":"4AKA2","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5e3244f5bac19521aee1a0de","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"03 PM11 AM12 PMX X 01 PM01 PM02 PMZ G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfac"},"rt":23071,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":134674,"subject":"FNUCO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a6fd0626923df0001ef977b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMA A 0A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfad"},"rt":11004,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":145786,"subject":"FNUCO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a6fd0626923df0001ef977b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"Z E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfae"},"rt":41830,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":187717,"subject":"FNUCO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a6fd0626923df0001ef977b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C C C 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfaf"},"rt":38970,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":226782,"subject":"FNUCO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a6fd0626923df0001ef977b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"03 PM04 PME 08 AM09 AM09 AMC C 02 PM03 PM04 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfb0"},"rt":28302,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":255193,"subject":"FNUCO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a6fd0626923df0001ef977b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AMI O O I O 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfb2"},"rt":13880,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":274841,"subject":"FNUCO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a6fd0626923df0001ef977b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"5E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfb3"},"rt":23958,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":298982,"subject":"FNUCO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a6fd0626923df0001ef977b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"I J X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfb4"},"rt":87703,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":386806,"subject":"FNUCO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a6fd0626923df0001ef977b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"J X N H B B B B B 11 AMX B B B E F F X 03 PMO C C G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfb5"},"rt":54449,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":441532,"subject":"FNUCO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a6fd0626923df0001ef977b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J B J E J J I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfb6"},"rt":11242,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":452865,"subject":"FNUCO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a6fd0626923df0001ef977b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfb7"},"rt":15704,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":468662,"subject":"FNUCO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a6fd0626923df0001ef977b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"01 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfb8"},"rt":7549,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":476304,"subject":"FNUCO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a6fd0626923df0001ef977b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"2F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfb9"},"rt":14257,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":490653,"subject":"FNUCO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a6fd0626923df0001ef977b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfba"},"rt":8593,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":499351,"subject":"FNUCO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a6fd0626923df0001ef977b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfbb"},"rt":10999,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":510441,"subject":"FNUCO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5a6fd0626923df0001ef977b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"11 AM02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfcc"},"rt":21490,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":104111,"subject":"9WKLV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d5b67ab9ad5a300181398dc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfcd"},"rt":36930,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":141131,"subject":"9WKLV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d5b67ab9ad5a300181398dc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfce"},"rt":21969,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":163189,"subject":"9WKLV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d5b67ab9ad5a300181398dc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfcf"},"rt":71765,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":235044,"subject":"9WKLV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d5b67ab9ad5a300181398dc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfd0"},"rt":137767,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":373131,"subject":"9WKLV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d5b67ab9ad5a300181398dc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfd2"},"rt":12745,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":392525,"subject":"9WKLV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d5b67ab9ad5a300181398dc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfd3"},"rt":31733,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":424361,"subject":"9WKLV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d5b67ab9ad5a300181398dc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfd4"},"rt":92490,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":516934,"subject":"9WKLV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d5b67ab9ad5a300181398dc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfd5"},"rt":47967,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":565244,"subject":"9WKLV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d5b67ab9ad5a300181398dc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"3J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfd6"},"rt":78434,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":643757,"subject":"9WKLV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d5b67ab9ad5a300181398dc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"08 AMB B 12 PMJ 10 AM11 AMB B M M G C C C C X X M X H L 06 PM05 PM06 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfd7"},"rt":7426,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":651511,"subject":"9WKLV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d5b67ab9ad5a300181398dc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfd8"},"rt":10023,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":661618,"subject":"9WKLV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d5b67ab9ad5a300181398dc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfd9"},"rt":26364,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":688066,"subject":"9WKLV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d5b67ab9ad5a300181398dc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfda"},"rt":82115,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":770269,"subject":"9WKLV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d5b67ab9ad5a300181398dc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"11 AM4I M M M G G A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfdb"},"rt":214089,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":984667,"subject":"9WKLV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d5b67ab9ad5a300181398dc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfec"},"rt":46080,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":256454,"subject":"7MO2B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f49f3262a3d07563d14a7f1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfed"},"rt":29254,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":285762,"subject":"7MO2B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f49f3262a3d07563d14a7f1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfee"},"rt":23295,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":309104,"subject":"7MO2B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f49f3262a3d07563d14a7f1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dfef"},"rt":70698,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":379869,"subject":"7MO2B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f49f3262a3d07563d14a7f1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dff0"},"rt":141805,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":521767,"subject":"7MO2B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f49f3262a3d07563d14a7f1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dff2"},"rt":31704,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":562527,"subject":"7MO2B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f49f3262a3d07563d14a7f1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dff3"},"rt":34743,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":597352,"subject":"7MO2B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f49f3262a3d07563d14a7f1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dff4"},"rt":110052,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":707485,"subject":"7MO2B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f49f3262a3d07563d14a7f1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"01 PM02 PME 12 PM03 PM04 PME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dff5"},"rt":42295,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":749901,"subject":"7MO2B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f49f3262a3d07563d14a7f1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dff6"},"rt":49652,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":799641,"subject":"7MO2B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f49f3262a3d07563d14a7f1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dff7"},"rt":16049,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":815777,"subject":"7MO2B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f49f3262a3d07563d14a7f1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dff8"},"rt":13385,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":829221,"subject":"7MO2B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f49f3262a3d07563d14a7f1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dff9"},"rt":27703,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":856976,"subject":"7MO2B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f49f3262a3d07563d14a7f1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dffa"},"rt":24000,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":881032,"subject":"7MO2B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f49f3262a3d07563d14a7f1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972dffb"},"rt":138275,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1019356,"subject":"7MO2B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f49f3262a3d07563d14a7f1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e00c"},"rt":17656,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":96871,"subject":"ZX26B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"628e51d27495cbf569ed1767","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"Z Z A A 5211 AM11 AMA 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e00d"},"rt":9325,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":106440,"subject":"ZX26B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"628e51d27495cbf569ed1767","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e00e"},"rt":92536,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":199020,"subject":"ZX26B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"628e51d27495cbf569ed1767","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"U U A C A B B Z C 12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM05 PM06 PM3C C A C 10 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM12 PMZ Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e00f"},"rt":63142,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":262288,"subject":"ZX26B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"628e51d27495cbf569ed1767","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"12 PMD D 04 PMH H H 04 PMH H B U U F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e010"},"rt":47701,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":310119,"subject":"ZX26B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"628e51d27495cbf569ed1767","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I I I O O I U U 02 PMA A A U U U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e012"},"rt":12012,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":328321,"subject":"ZX26B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"628e51d27495cbf569ed1767","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e013"},"rt":18204,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":346560,"subject":"ZX26B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"628e51d27495cbf569ed1767","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e014"},"rt":24340,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":370934,"subject":"ZX26B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"628e51d27495cbf569ed1767","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"7F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e015"},"rt":18470,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":389437,"subject":"ZX26B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"628e51d27495cbf569ed1767","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"4J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e016"},"rt":34245,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":423716,"subject":"ZX26B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"628e51d27495cbf569ed1767","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"C F Z M O Z F Z E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e017"},"rt":9240,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":432991,"subject":"ZX26B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"628e51d27495cbf569ed1767","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"03 PM02 PM11 AM12 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e018"},"rt":6112,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":439139,"subject":"ZX26B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"628e51d27495cbf569ed1767","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"J B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e019"},"rt":78365,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":517538,"subject":"ZX26B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"628e51d27495cbf569ed1767","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"H Z Z X X X H Z Z Z O Z Z B F F E G G G A G G B O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e01a"},"rt":48105,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":565775,"subject":"ZX26B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"628e51d27495cbf569ed1767","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PMX B B M B 03 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e01b"},"rt":86543,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":652345,"subject":"ZX26B","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"628e51d27495cbf569ed1767","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"X X B B B 12 PM01 PMI J X X X X B F Z M M 01 PM01 PMB B B B 12 PMX X 02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e02c"},"rt":10462,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":51300,"subject":"AU60S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"580d5d1f357e890001dd14ce","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"5J 12 PM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e02d"},"rt":12259,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":63615,"subject":"AU60S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"580d5d1f357e890001dd14ce","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e02e"},"rt":14780,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":78458,"subject":"AU60S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"580d5d1f357e890001dd14ce","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e02f"},"rt":18218,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":96720,"subject":"AU60S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"580d5d1f357e890001dd14ce","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"008 AM09 AM10 AM03 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e030"},"rt":11841,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":108609,"subject":"AU60S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"580d5d1f357e890001dd14ce","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"1C I H O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e032"},"rt":7026,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":118891,"subject":"AU60S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"580d5d1f357e890001dd14ce","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"2G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e033"},"rt":19743,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":138686,"subject":"AU60S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"580d5d1f357e890001dd14ce","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"08 AM09 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e034"},"rt":24250,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":162991,"subject":"AU60S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"580d5d1f357e890001dd14ce","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"E E J J J J J J I B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e035"},"rt":17414,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":180453,"subject":"AU60S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"580d5d1f357e890001dd14ce","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I I I I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e036"},"rt":12075,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":192585,"subject":"AU60S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"580d5d1f357e890001dd14ce","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e037"},"rt":14958,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":207593,"subject":"AU60S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"580d5d1f357e890001dd14ce","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F E B 01 PM12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e038"},"rt":9160,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":216802,"subject":"AU60S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"580d5d1f357e890001dd14ce","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"I F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e039"},"rt":10803,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":227655,"subject":"AU60S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"580d5d1f357e890001dd14ce","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"3I Z Z O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e03a"},"rt":7496,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":235198,"subject":"AU60S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"580d5d1f357e890001dd14ce","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e03b"},"rt":27639,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":262884,"subject":"AU60S","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"580d5d1f357e890001dd14ce","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"102 PMX X X 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e04c"},"rt":12824,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":205520,"subject":"7PBLW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d62886927a84f00010fbbb4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"211 AMA A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e04d"},"rt":11903,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":217461,"subject":"7PBLW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d62886927a84f00010fbbb4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"U E D E C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e04e"},"rt":20991,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":238488,"subject":"7PBLW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d62886927a84f00010fbbb4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"3C C A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e04f"},"rt":86039,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":324562,"subject":"7PBLW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d62886927a84f00010fbbb4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"U 04 PM04 PMU U U J U 2H H I I O O O O H U 04 PM04 PMK "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e050"},"rt":67842,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":392523,"subject":"7PBLW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d62886927a84f00010fbbb4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"G I O O Z Z F 03 PMU 2U F O O O O O K O C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e052"},"rt":11449,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":410046,"subject":"7PBLW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d62886927a84f00010fbbb4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e053"},"rt":20135,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":430218,"subject":"7PBLW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d62886927a84f00010fbbb4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4F C F 4B B 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e054"},"rt":39867,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":470122,"subject":"7PBLW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d62886927a84f00010fbbb4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E F F B B X X B B B E 6F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e055"},"rt":24062,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":494218,"subject":"7PBLW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d62886927a84f00010fbbb4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"4F J B B J J J B 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e056"},"rt":65589,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":559842,"subject":"7PBLW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d62886927a84f00010fbbb4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"O G G F F F B B B B M M O O C C G B F F F F I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e057"},"rt":8135,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":568170,"subject":"7PBLW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d62886927a84f00010fbbb4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"I 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e058"},"rt":6700,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":574904,"subject":"7PBLW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d62886927a84f00010fbbb4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"2J B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e059"},"rt":45394,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":620334,"subject":"7PBLW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d62886927a84f00010fbbb4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"F Z Z Z B O O C C G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e05a"},"rt":39924,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":660289,"subject":"7PBLW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d62886927a84f00010fbbb4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"5X C C C O O X F B 4X X I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e05b"},"rt":35048,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":695374,"subject":"7PBLW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5d62886927a84f00010fbbb4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X F F F X X X F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e06c"},"rt":15498,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":66284,"subject":"087ES","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5b15d20c444cef0001cb1153","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e06d"},"rt":13180,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":79554,"subject":"087ES","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5b15d20c444cef0001cb1153","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e06e"},"rt":12773,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":92356,"subject":"087ES","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5b15d20c444cef0001cb1153","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e06f"},"rt":12489,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":104870,"subject":"087ES","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5b15d20c444cef0001cb1153","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e070"},"rt":20683,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":125580,"subject":"087ES","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5b15d20c444cef0001cb1153","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e072"},"rt":29051,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":162132,"subject":"087ES","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5b15d20c444cef0001cb1153","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AM09 AMJ G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e073"},"rt":34740,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":197560,"subject":"087ES","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5b15d20c444cef0001cb1153","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e074"},"rt":29476,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":227060,"subject":"087ES","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5b15d20c444cef0001cb1153","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"B B 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e075"},"rt":45848,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":272934,"subject":"087ES","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5b15d20c444cef0001cb1153","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e076"},"rt":23309,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":296271,"subject":"087ES","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5b15d20c444cef0001cb1153","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e077"},"rt":12825,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":309124,"subject":"087ES","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5b15d20c444cef0001cb1153","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e078"},"rt":23814,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":332964,"subject":"087ES","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5b15d20c444cef0001cb1153","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"A C M 01 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e079"},"rt":41627,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":374617,"subject":"087ES","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5b15d20c444cef0001cb1153","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,P","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e07a"},"rt":37131,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":411780,"subject":"087ES","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5b15d20c444cef0001cb1153","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e07b"},"rt":15731,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":427537,"subject":"087ES","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5b15d20c444cef0001cb1153","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e08c"},"rt":10614,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":75117,"subject":"JYQBU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5654175604212700054a12b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e08d"},"rt":10810,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":85980,"subject":"JYQBU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5654175604212700054a12b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e08e"},"rt":14706,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":100737,"subject":"JYQBU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5654175604212700054a12b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e08f"},"rt":28238,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":129026,"subject":"JYQBU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5654175604212700054a12b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e090"},"rt":84411,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":213490,"subject":"JYQBU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5654175604212700054a12b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I 12 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM11 AMI O O I I 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e092"},"rt":7728,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":226191,"subject":"JYQBU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5654175604212700054a12b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e093"},"rt":16306,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":242545,"subject":"JYQBU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5654175604212700054a12b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e094"},"rt":106458,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":349053,"subject":"JYQBU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5654175604212700054a12b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e095"},"rt":28373,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":377602,"subject":"JYQBU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5654175604212700054a12b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J I 10 AM10 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e096"},"rt":70563,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":448211,"subject":"JYQBU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5654175604212700054a12b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"Z 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e097"},"rt":6103,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":454482,"subject":"JYQBU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5654175604212700054a12b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e098"},"rt":7178,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":461709,"subject":"JYQBU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5654175604212700054a12b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e099"},"rt":182,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":461947,"subject":"JYQBU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5654175604212700054a12b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e09a"},"rt":144,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":462148,"subject":"JYQBU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5654175604212700054a12b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e09b"},"rt":32141,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":494347,"subject":"JYQBU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5654175604212700054a12b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0ac"},"rt":9838,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":44246,"subject":"35BO6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"606492360e422d12dc63000e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0ad"},"rt":19972,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":64281,"subject":"35BO6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"606492360e422d12dc63000e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0ae"},"rt":11390,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":75733,"subject":"35BO6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"606492360e422d12dc63000e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0af"},"rt":31896,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":107693,"subject":"35BO6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"606492360e422d12dc63000e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C 04 PMC F F H O O 11 AM10 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0b0"},"rt":44624,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":152374,"subject":"35BO6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"606492360e422d12dc63000e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C I O O 12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0b2"},"rt":7326,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":166053,"subject":"35BO6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"606492360e422d12dc63000e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0b3"},"rt":14387,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":180502,"subject":"35BO6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"606492360e422d12dc63000e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0b4"},"rt":21726,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":202293,"subject":"35BO6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"606492360e422d12dc63000e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"1C B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0b5"},"rt":15702,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":218062,"subject":"35BO6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"606492360e422d12dc63000e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"M J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0b6"},"rt":39943,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":258070,"subject":"35BO6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"606492360e422d12dc63000e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"M F Z B O O F Z C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0b7"},"rt":4727,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":262862,"subject":"35BO6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"606492360e422d12dc63000e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0b8"},"rt":6880,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":269805,"subject":"35BO6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"606492360e422d12dc63000e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0b9"},"rt":22126,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":291990,"subject":"35BO6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"606492360e422d12dc63000e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z Z Z O X M X F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0ba"},"rt":26078,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":318143,"subject":"35BO6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"606492360e422d12dc63000e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0bb"},"rt":69147,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":387366,"subject":"35BO6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"606492360e422d12dc63000e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"2M 08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AMX X 02 PMB X X 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0cc"},"rt":21562,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":142066,"subject":"691MW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6234f3b76898c3f34402935c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"03 PMJ 09 AM11 AM11 AMA 11 AM11 AM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0cd"},"rt":13687,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":155866,"subject":"691MW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6234f3b76898c3f34402935c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A F K E 04 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0ce"},"rt":61331,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":217336,"subject":"691MW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6234f3b76898c3f34402935c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"1U C A U B C C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0cf"},"rt":78721,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":296417,"subject":"691MW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6234f3b76898c3f34402935c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"04 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMZ Z C C A U B B X 02 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0d0"},"rt":94029,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":390834,"subject":"691MW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6234f3b76898c3f34402935c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"1Z I I O O 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0d2"},"rt":19396,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":423144,"subject":"691MW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6234f3b76898c3f34402935c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"4E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0d3"},"rt":41489,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":464733,"subject":"691MW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6234f3b76898c3f34402935c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"6F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0d4"},"rt":122366,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":587198,"subject":"691MW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6234f3b76898c3f34402935c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0d5"},"rt":49601,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":637084,"subject":"691MW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6234f3b76898c3f34402935c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"0I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0d6"},"rt":62680,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":700622,"subject":"691MW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6234f3b76898c3f34402935c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0d7"},"rt":24202,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":725110,"subject":"691MW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6234f3b76898c3f34402935c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0d8"},"rt":25125,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":750344,"subject":"691MW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6234f3b76898c3f34402935c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0d9"},"rt":62343,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":812794,"subject":"691MW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6234f3b76898c3f34402935c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0da"},"rt":123584,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":936674,"subject":"691MW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6234f3b76898c3f34402935c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0db"},"rt":165333,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1102294,"subject":"691MW","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"6234f3b76898c3f34402935c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0ec"},"rt":26593,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":75275,"subject":"D3FZH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f24b0fc546c5a0c3c2e43b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"111 AM10 AM11 AMA A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0ed"},"rt":15975,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":91373,"subject":"D3FZH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f24b0fc546c5a0c3c2e43b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"O D D D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0ee"},"rt":14726,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":106146,"subject":"D3FZH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f24b0fc546c5a0c3c2e43b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"O A A C 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0ef"},"rt":27022,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":133203,"subject":"D3FZH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f24b0fc546c5a0c3c2e43b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0f0"},"rt":16797,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":150041,"subject":"D3FZH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f24b0fc546c5a0c3c2e43b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"3H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0f2"},"rt":8942,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":160888,"subject":"D3FZH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f24b0fc546c5a0c3c2e43b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0f3"},"rt":24423,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":185350,"subject":"D3FZH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f24b0fc546c5a0c3c2e43b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,H","hovered":"5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0f4"},"rt":30230,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":215623,"subject":"D3FZH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f24b0fc546c5a0c3c2e43b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J,M","hovered":"E B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0f5"},"rt":20117,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":235774,"subject":"D3FZH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f24b0fc546c5a0c3c2e43b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0f6"},"rt":26321,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":262131,"subject":"D3FZH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f24b0fc546c5a0c3c2e43b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0f7"},"rt":8909,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":271116,"subject":"D3FZH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f24b0fc546c5a0c3c2e43b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0f8"},"rt":15192,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":286344,"subject":"D3FZH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f24b0fc546c5a0c3c2e43b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0f9"},"rt":30682,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":317064,"subject":"D3FZH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f24b0fc546c5a0c3c2e43b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L","hovered":"J O X X Z Z Z Z H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0fa"},"rt":39948,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":357050,"subject":"D3FZH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f24b0fc546c5a0c3c2e43b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"03 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMX M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e0fb"},"rt":31706,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":388796,"subject":"D3FZH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f24b0fc546c5a0c3c2e43b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,X","hovered":"2J H F F M 01 PM02 PMX X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e10c"},"rt":19374,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":100843,"subject":"FKYE6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"611ae552f2b586def2c4d9c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e10d"},"rt":7346,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":108307,"subject":"FKYE6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"611ae552f2b586def2c4d9c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e10e"},"rt":11702,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":120125,"subject":"FKYE6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"611ae552f2b586def2c4d9c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"Z C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e10f"},"rt":44526,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":164774,"subject":"FKYE6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"611ae552f2b586def2c4d9c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PM01 PM01 PM01 PMF 12 PMZ 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e110"},"rt":64176,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":229072,"subject":"FKYE6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"611ae552f2b586def2c4d9c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"9O O 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM02 PMZ H H H H F A A O O K K 02 PM02 PMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e112"},"rt":12115,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":246325,"subject":"FKYE6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"611ae552f2b586def2c4d9c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"01 PM12 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e113"},"rt":16525,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":262971,"subject":"FKYE6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"611ae552f2b586def2c4d9c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e114"},"rt":48617,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":311703,"subject":"FKYE6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"611ae552f2b586def2c4d9c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e115"},"rt":26105,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":337920,"subject":"FKYE6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"611ae552f2b586def2c4d9c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e116"},"rt":33210,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":371251,"subject":"FKYE6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"611ae552f2b586def2c4d9c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"3I Z Z X M B O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e117"},"rt":6842,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":378235,"subject":"FKYE6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"611ae552f2b586def2c4d9c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e118"},"rt":4595,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":382950,"subject":"FKYE6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"611ae552f2b586def2c4d9c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e119"},"rt":41244,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":424317,"subject":"FKYE6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"611ae552f2b586def2c4d9c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e11a"},"rt":40959,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":465399,"subject":"FKYE6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"611ae552f2b586def2c4d9c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e11b"},"rt":40532,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":506048,"subject":"FKYE6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"611ae552f2b586def2c4d9c9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"F X 02 PMX X X G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e12c"},"rt":16037,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":196060,"subject":"YSHXL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"612d18cff20cd023bd839bde","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e12d"},"rt":8414,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":204512,"subject":"YSHXL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"612d18cff20cd023bd839bde","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e12e"},"rt":61976,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":266512,"subject":"YSHXL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"612d18cff20cd023bd839bde","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,G","hovered":"09 AMC C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e12f"},"rt":54663,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":321292,"subject":"YSHXL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"612d18cff20cd023bd839bde","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"04 PM04 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM09 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e130"},"rt":76715,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":398038,"subject":"YSHXL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"612d18cff20cd023bd839bde","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,K","hovered":"I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e132"},"rt":49571,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":457578,"subject":"YSHXL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"612d18cff20cd023bd839bde","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"J M 02 PM01 PM12 PMB O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e133"},"rt":17092,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":474717,"subject":"YSHXL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"612d18cff20cd023bd839bde","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,J","hovered":"01 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e134"},"rt":26182,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":500924,"subject":"YSHXL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"612d18cff20cd023bd839bde","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"B M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e135"},"rt":13374,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":514326,"subject":"YSHXL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"612d18cff20cd023bd839bde","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"10 AMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e136"},"rt":42248,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":556602,"subject":"YSHXL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"612d18cff20cd023bd839bde","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"P,Z","hovered":"B F F F 8Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e137"},"rt":10386,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":567018,"subject":"YSHXL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"612d18cff20cd023bd839bde","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e138"},"rt":18165,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":585212,"subject":"YSHXL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"612d18cff20cd023bd839bde","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"J B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e139"},"rt":13997,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":599234,"subject":"YSHXL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"612d18cff20cd023bd839bde","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"11 AMZ Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e13a"},"rt":23517,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":622790,"subject":"YSHXL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"612d18cff20cd023bd839bde","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,O","hovered":"09 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM10 AM09 AMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e13b"},"rt":18279,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":641098,"subject":"YSHXL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"612d18cff20cd023bd839bde","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e14c"},"rt":20311,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":408923,"subject":"UZ4K6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"59d8ae913e5ea00001e1d05f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C 11 AMA A 11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e14d"},"rt":14243,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":423280,"subject":"UZ4K6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"59d8ae913e5ea00001e1d05f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"C F K E 01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e14e"},"rt":15840,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":439235,"subject":"UZ4K6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"59d8ae913e5ea00001e1d05f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C Z 12 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e14f"},"rt":110404,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":549756,"subject":"UZ4K6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"59d8ae913e5ea00001e1d05f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e150"},"rt":87998,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":637934,"subject":"UZ4K6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"59d8ae913e5ea00001e1d05f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e152"},"rt":13944,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":661856,"subject":"UZ4K6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"59d8ae913e5ea00001e1d05f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e153"},"rt":25677,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":687584,"subject":"UZ4K6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"59d8ae913e5ea00001e1d05f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F B B B M M 01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e154"},"rt":234351,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":921982,"subject":"UZ4K6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"59d8ae913e5ea00001e1d05f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E E E E M X X O O O D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e155"},"rt":29835,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":951959,"subject":"UZ4K6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"59d8ae913e5ea00001e1d05f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e156"},"rt":88092,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1040098,"subject":"UZ4K6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"59d8ae913e5ea00001e1d05f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e157"},"rt":8592,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1048863,"subject":"UZ4K6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"59d8ae913e5ea00001e1d05f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"08 AM12 PM01 PM12 PMB B F F 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e158"},"rt":8997,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1057907,"subject":"UZ4K6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"59d8ae913e5ea00001e1d05f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e159"},"rt":21772,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1079727,"subject":"UZ4K6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"59d8ae913e5ea00001e1d05f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e15a"},"rt":54077,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1133850,"subject":"UZ4K6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"59d8ae913e5ea00001e1d05f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PMB B B F F B B X F J I J M M X M M 12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e15b"},"rt":46270,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1180173,"subject":"UZ4K6","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"59d8ae913e5ea00001e1d05f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"J 02 PM02 PMB I E E E E M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e16c"},"rt":28211,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":102904,"subject":"ZHGQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60fcdb6cf1d45f7a16312fc7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AMA A A A A 10 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e16d"},"rt":12866,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":115833,"subject":"ZHGQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60fcdb6cf1d45f7a16312fc7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"10 AM11 AMO U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e16e"},"rt":25804,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":141693,"subject":"ZHGQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60fcdb6cf1d45f7a16312fc7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"1C A Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e16f"},"rt":57787,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":199543,"subject":"ZHGQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60fcdb6cf1d45f7a16312fc7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,U","hovered":"U U Z H F F F O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e170"},"rt":114472,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":314074,"subject":"ZHGQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60fcdb6cf1d45f7a16312fc7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"O O 12 PM02 PMH I I 03 PM2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e172"},"rt":10443,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":328840,"subject":"ZHGQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60fcdb6cf1d45f7a16312fc7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"2E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e173"},"rt":15457,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":344353,"subject":"ZHGQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60fcdb6cf1d45f7a16312fc7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"2I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e174"},"rt":71276,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":415693,"subject":"ZHGQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60fcdb6cf1d45f7a16312fc7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"3G G B X F F E 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e175"},"rt":42285,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":458138,"subject":"ZHGQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60fcdb6cf1d45f7a16312fc7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J 08 AMI 10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e176"},"rt":48698,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":506898,"subject":"ZHGQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60fcdb6cf1d45f7a16312fc7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"Z O F B B X J J J B 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e177"},"rt":10038,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":516993,"subject":"ZHGQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60fcdb6cf1d45f7a16312fc7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"08 AM09 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e178"},"rt":7790,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":524831,"subject":"ZHGQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60fcdb6cf1d45f7a16312fc7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e179"},"rt":33420,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":558308,"subject":"ZHGQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60fcdb6cf1d45f7a16312fc7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"O O X F O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e17a"},"rt":17278,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":575639,"subject":"ZHGQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60fcdb6cf1d45f7a16312fc7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e17b"},"rt":58986,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":634683,"subject":"ZHGQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60fcdb6cf1d45f7a16312fc7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"3F C C M M M M B B F 11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e18c"},"rt":18976,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":138340,"subject":"7WX1G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"607ce9df61f8f44b9403edfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM10 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e18d"},"rt":21582,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":160141,"subject":"7WX1G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"607ce9df61f8f44b9403edfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"U A C D D D E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e18e"},"rt":32203,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":192547,"subject":"7WX1G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"607ce9df61f8f44b9403edfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"11 AMC C C C C A Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e18f"},"rt":100988,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":293770,"subject":"7WX1G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"607ce9df61f8f44b9403edfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"Z 03 PM04 PM06 PM04 PM04 PMU U J U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e190"},"rt":321129,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":615290,"subject":"7WX1G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"607ce9df61f8f44b9403edfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I O O H H I K O O 12 PM11 AMO O H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e192"},"rt":6485,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":631745,"subject":"7WX1G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"607ce9df61f8f44b9403edfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e193"},"rt":16341,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":648229,"subject":"7WX1G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"607ce9df61f8f44b9403edfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C F 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e194"},"rt":117675,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":766038,"subject":"7WX1G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"607ce9df61f8f44b9403edfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G F B X X X X 02 PM03 PMX X B B B F C F F B G E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e195"},"rt":52630,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":818868,"subject":"7WX1G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"607ce9df61f8f44b9403edfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"6B B X B O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e196"},"rt":51148,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":870347,"subject":"7WX1G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"607ce9df61f8f44b9403edfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F Z O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e197"},"rt":11762,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":882561,"subject":"7WX1G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"607ce9df61f8f44b9403edfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e198"},"rt":9488,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":892188,"subject":"7WX1G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"607ce9df61f8f44b9403edfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e199"},"rt":24250,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":916775,"subject":"7WX1G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"607ce9df61f8f44b9403edfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"O Z O X X X 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e19a"},"rt":37968,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":954887,"subject":"7WX1G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"607ce9df61f8f44b9403edfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PMX 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e19b"},"rt":74730,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1029834,"subject":"7WX1G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"607ce9df61f8f44b9403edfc","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PMX X 02 PMM M M B B B B B F F F F F E E E G F J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1ac"},"rt":31205,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":136335,"subject":"MV1AX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ba345bcf07414000106135e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1ad"},"rt":34177,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":170652,"subject":"MV1AX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ba345bcf07414000106135e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"08 AM09 AM11 AMO Z Z D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1ae"},"rt":68350,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":239224,"subject":"MV1AX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ba345bcf07414000106135e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"C Z C C C C C 08 AMA A C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1af"},"rt":62502,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":301979,"subject":"MV1AX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ba345bcf07414000106135e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"10 AM09 AM01 PM04 PM02 PM04 PM1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1b0"},"rt":50245,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":352409,"subject":"MV1AX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ba345bcf07414000106135e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"02 PMU 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1b2"},"rt":83247,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":474151,"subject":"MV1AX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ba345bcf07414000106135e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AM10 AM11 AM11 AMM M E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1b3"},"rt":33635,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":508978,"subject":"MV1AX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ba345bcf07414000106135e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F B B B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1b4"},"rt":52942,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":562268,"subject":"MV1AX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ba345bcf07414000106135e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I,J","hovered":"B F F B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1b5"},"rt":31536,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":593968,"subject":"MV1AX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ba345bcf07414000106135e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1b6"},"rt":85774,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":679859,"subject":"MV1AX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ba345bcf07414000106135e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"2F F 12 PMF B B F F B B B B B B 12 PM01 PM02 PM04 PM06 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1b7"},"rt":17316,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":697405,"subject":"MV1AX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ba345bcf07414000106135e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"11 AM12 PM01 PM12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1b8"},"rt":7706,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":705220,"subject":"MV1AX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ba345bcf07414000106135e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1b9"},"rt":37799,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":743093,"subject":"MV1AX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ba345bcf07414000106135e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M B O Z 04 PM04 PMZ Z Z B B F 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1ba"},"rt":23609,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":766918,"subject":"MV1AX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ba345bcf07414000106135e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"08 AMM N 03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1bb"},"rt":48103,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":815129,"subject":"MV1AX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ba345bcf07414000106135e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM01 PM02 PM02 PMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1cc"},"rt":40864,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":156807,"subject":"L5J42","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeb6839de2a6585202286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1cd"},"rt":14928,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":171861,"subject":"L5J42","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeb6839de2a6585202286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"5K E E G U A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1ce"},"rt":55047,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":227028,"subject":"L5J42","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeb6839de2a6585202286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"4C C A B Z A U B B C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1cf"},"rt":24967,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":252109,"subject":"L5J42","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeb6839de2a6585202286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"H E E D E E O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1d0"},"rt":56892,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":309112,"subject":"L5J42","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeb6839de2a6585202286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X,U","hovered":"A Z I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1d2"},"rt":70524,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":392672,"subject":"L5J42","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeb6839de2a6585202286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"J X O A E G 3C C H F F Z B F F F B B B B X N N N D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1d3"},"rt":46095,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":439016,"subject":"L5J42","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeb6839de2a6585202286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N,Z","hovered":"B 08 PM07 PM06 PM05 PM04 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1d4"},"rt":46246,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":485401,"subject":"L5J42","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeb6839de2a6585202286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I,J","hovered":"7X B J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1d5"},"rt":15199,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":500814,"subject":"L5J42","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeb6839de2a6585202286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1d6"},"rt":41525,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":542489,"subject":"L5J42","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeb6839de2a6585202286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1d7"},"rt":15411,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":557990,"subject":"L5J42","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeb6839de2a6585202286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1d8"},"rt":9472,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":567565,"subject":"L5J42","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeb6839de2a6585202286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1d9"},"rt":25979,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":593633,"subject":"L5J42","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeb6839de2a6585202286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1da"},"rt":29107,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":622846,"subject":"L5J42","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeb6839de2a6585202286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"02 PM03 PMI I B O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1db"},"rt":31757,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":654697,"subject":"L5J42","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeb6839de2a6585202286","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"M X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1ec"},"rt":33066,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":184399,"subject":"4CTP0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bac1d9dc1155b0001175e55","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM12 PM11 AM10 AM10 AM11 AMA A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1ed"},"rt":23745,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":208277,"subject":"4CTP0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bac1d9dc1155b0001175e55","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"01 PM01 PM02 PM02 PMZ K D E E E 04 PME K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1ee"},"rt":68048,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":276445,"subject":"4CTP0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bac1d9dc1155b0001175e55","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"Z C A C A C C A Z 10 AM09 AM08 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1ef"},"rt":65304,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":342126,"subject":"4CTP0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bac1d9dc1155b0001175e55","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"08 AM09 AM11 AM11 AM01 PM12 PM06 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM12 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM04 PM05 PM04 PM04 PM02 PM02 PMX X X H 03 PM04 PMU U 02 PMU 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1f0"},"rt":425346,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":767818,"subject":"4CTP0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bac1d9dc1155b0001175e55","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"O I O I O O U F 01 PMF F H H O O 11 AMO H H H H H 01 PMH O U U Z U 02 PMU U U F F A H H H I F 02 PM02 PM03 PM03 PMU U U U Z H J H H I O O O A A A A Z F F U U U 03 PM03 PMK J F F U U K 03 PMU Z H I O 02 PMU U G G G O O H C C Z U U 02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1f2"},"rt":19257,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":797702,"subject":"4CTP0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bac1d9dc1155b0001175e55","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1f3"},"rt":31505,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":829334,"subject":"4CTP0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bac1d9dc1155b0001175e55","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"3F F B B B B 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1f4"},"rt":75441,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":904903,"subject":"4CTP0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bac1d9dc1155b0001175e55","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"N N B B B E E I E E E J E X X 0E M M M G B B E J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1f5"},"rt":141282,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1046467,"subject":"4CTP0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bac1d9dc1155b0001175e55","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"X J G F B B I 11 AM12 PM12 PMM B F F F 01 PMM 10 AM11 AMB J 10 AMJ J I J J I I 10 AM10 AMI B B B B B F F F B E 11 AM11 AM10 AM10 AM09 AMI I I B B I I 09 AM01 PMM M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1f6"},"rt":109903,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1156635,"subject":"4CTP0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bac1d9dc1155b0001175e55","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"J J J F 12 PMB F 03 PM03 PM04 PMB B M B B B 12 PMM M 12 PMX X 01X 02 PM02 PM02 PMX X X O O 03 PMX C C C F F E 11 AM11 AME E E E E F I B B 12 PM12 PMB E G 01 PMG G X X X O O X X 02 PMX Z Z Z H A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1f7"},"rt":19025,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1176055,"subject":"4CTP0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bac1d9dc1155b0001175e55","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"E 12 PM12 PMB F 12 PMB F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1f8"},"rt":13585,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1189766,"subject":"4CTP0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bac1d9dc1155b0001175e55","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"J B B 0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1f9"},"rt":58542,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1248424,"subject":"4CTP0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bac1d9dc1155b0001175e55","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"X 12 PMO Z 04 PMZ F F 02 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM03 PM05 PM04 PM04 PM02 PMB B B M F E 11 AMO X 0008 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1fa"},"rt":75610,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1324169,"subject":"4CTP0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bac1d9dc1155b0001175e55","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"08 AM003 PMM 12 PMM M 03 PMB B 12 PMM F F E C C C C C C X X X X 02 PM02 PM02 PMX X X X B B 11 AM11 AMJ J J J I 09 AMM M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e1fb"},"rt":339892,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1664402,"subject":"4CTP0","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bac1d9dc1155b0001175e55","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,E","hovered":"X 02 PM02 PMJ J I I I 09 AM09 AMJ 10 AME E E J I E E 11 AM43F F F B 12 PMF F B B B 12 PM12 PMB B 12 PMB B B B B B 01 PMM M M X 02 PMM B 12 PM11 AM11 AMJ E E 11 AM10 AM12 PM01 PM01 PM12 PMX X X X C E E F F F B B X M M M X 02 PMJ J J I B B F F B I 11 AM11 AME 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e20c"},"rt":24283,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":169301,"subject":"S0HHG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62fb516e94e3e8aa31c1e0e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e20d"},"rt":64392,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":233837,"subject":"S0HHG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62fb516e94e3e8aa31c1e0e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"F 06 PM04 PME E E E E J J E E E E B B O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e20e"},"rt":21024,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":255369,"subject":"S0HHG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62fb516e94e3e8aa31c1e0e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"6C 02 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e20f"},"rt":15510,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":271027,"subject":"S0HHG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62fb516e94e3e8aa31c1e0e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"F 02 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e210"},"rt":116750,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":387917,"subject":"S0HHG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62fb516e94e3e8aa31c1e0e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"O C 11 AM08 AM09 AM08 AM10 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AMC C 10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM10 AMU U U Z 11 AM10 AM09 AMC 09 AM10 AM11 AM03 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM11 AM11 AMA A 10 AM10 AM11 AMA 09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e212"},"rt":100500,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":497416,"subject":"S0HHG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62fb516e94e3e8aa31c1e0e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"009 AM10 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM10 AM09 AM09 AM09 AMJ F 02 PMM F B 11 AM03 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PMM 01 PM02 PM03 PM06 PM07 PM07 PM07 PMX 01 PM12 PMX O H F F 10 AM09 AMA 05 PM04 PMM 10 AMB C C 10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM04 PMH 12 PM01 PM01 PMX O Z Z N 06 PM05 PMM 09 AMJ G J J J B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e213"},"rt":47007,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":544931,"subject":"S0HHG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62fb516e94e3e8aa31c1e0e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"12 PM09 AM08 AMJ 11 AM11 AM10 AM11 AMB B B 11 AM10 AM11 AM08 AM09 AMM M 01 PMX O X M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e214"},"rt":46083,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":591161,"subject":"S0HHG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62fb516e94e3e8aa31c1e0e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"7C B B B B B B B B C O B 10 AMB X X 04 PMC C G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e215"},"rt":33913,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":625210,"subject":"S0HHG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62fb516e94e3e8aa31c1e0e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"I B B B F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e216"},"rt":13412,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":638762,"subject":"S0HHG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62fb516e94e3e8aa31c1e0e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"C C B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e217"},"rt":16593,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":655495,"subject":"S0HHG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62fb516e94e3e8aa31c1e0e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"I 11 AM12 PM12 PMM M M 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e218"},"rt":18661,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":674295,"subject":"S0HHG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62fb516e94e3e8aa31c1e0e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F F G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e219"},"rt":16176,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":690613,"subject":"S0HHG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62fb516e94e3e8aa31c1e0e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":"F F M B N D D Z N N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e21a"},"rt":13834,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":704717,"subject":"S0HHG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62fb516e94e3e8aa31c1e0e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B 02 PM03 PMX X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e21b"},"rt":25900,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":730758,"subject":"S0HHG","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62fb516e94e3e8aa31c1e0e7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"5F F B 01 PM02 PM02 PMX X X X X X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e22c"},"rt":29357,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":681297,"subject":"K8UXV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62f3fd82d8bca81b9ba8842d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"05 PM04 PM03 PM10 AMA A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e22d"},"rt":25811,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":707175,"subject":"K8UXV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62f3fd82d8bca81b9ba8842d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"05 PMB K E E K E E G 11 AM06 PMB B G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e22e"},"rt":26310,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":733550,"subject":"K8UXV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62f3fd82d8bca81b9ba8842d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e22f"},"rt":31141,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":764757,"subject":"K8UXV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62f3fd82d8bca81b9ba8842d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"10 AM04 PM04 PME E 01 PM07 PM04 PM04 PMK "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e230"},"rt":23852,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":788674,"subject":"K8UXV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62f3fd82d8bca81b9ba8842d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e232"},"rt":15891,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":816993,"subject":"K8UXV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62f3fd82d8bca81b9ba8842d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e233"},"rt":34963,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":852015,"subject":"K8UXV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62f3fd82d8bca81b9ba8842d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e234"},"rt":53306,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":905383,"subject":"K8UXV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62f3fd82d8bca81b9ba8842d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"B B M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e235"},"rt":39669,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":945112,"subject":"K8UXV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62f3fd82d8bca81b9ba8842d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e236"},"rt":16252,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":961429,"subject":"K8UXV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62f3fd82d8bca81b9ba8842d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e237"},"rt":9268,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":970759,"subject":"K8UXV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62f3fd82d8bca81b9ba8842d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e238"},"rt":14255,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":985078,"subject":"K8UXV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62f3fd82d8bca81b9ba8842d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e239"},"rt":90626,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1075765,"subject":"K8UXV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62f3fd82d8bca81b9ba8842d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,P","hovered":"02 PMZ L L L Z O O Z Z H Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e23a"},"rt":100215,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1176176,"subject":"K8UXV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62f3fd82d8bca81b9ba8842d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"07 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMN O 03 PM03 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e23b"},"rt":116286,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1292657,"subject":"K8UXV","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62f3fd82d8bca81b9ba8842d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"12 PM01 PM03 PM04 PMM 12 PMB E E F X B B B B B F E F F F E F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e24c"},"rt":26126,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":135305,"subject":"2P7ZX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeca4922726b49ec42dc3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AMA K 510 AM11 AMX X 11 AM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e24d"},"rt":19099,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":154480,"subject":"2P7ZX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeca4922726b49ec42dc3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"U F K D E 04 PM03 PM02 PM1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e24e"},"rt":59437,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":213978,"subject":"2P7ZX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeca4922726b49ec42dc3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PMH E C C A A C C C C C C C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e24f"},"rt":119877,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":333934,"subject":"2P7ZX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeca4922726b49ec42dc3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"Z 04 PMB B B Z A A A 01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM08 AM05 PM04 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e250"},"rt":86183,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":420354,"subject":"2P7ZX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeca4922726b49ec42dc3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I 12 PM12 PMO I I I I A I I I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e252"},"rt":8257,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":438846,"subject":"2P7ZX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeca4922726b49ec42dc3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e253"},"rt":13420,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":452330,"subject":"2P7ZX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeca4922726b49ec42dc3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F B B F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e254"},"rt":79480,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":531922,"subject":"2P7ZX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeca4922726b49ec42dc3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"6E E E B B B B B M M B 12 PM12 PMB M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e255"},"rt":29001,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":561181,"subject":"2P7ZX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeca4922726b49ec42dc3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e256"},"rt":19628,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":580913,"subject":"2P7ZX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeca4922726b49ec42dc3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"M F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e257"},"rt":9008,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":590031,"subject":"2P7ZX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeca4922726b49ec42dc3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"09 AM11 AM12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e258"},"rt":18313,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":608426,"subject":"2P7ZX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeca4922726b49ec42dc3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"J F 12 PMB B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e259"},"rt":50950,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":659492,"subject":"2P7ZX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeca4922726b49ec42dc3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,X","hovered":"04 PM04 PM03 PMZ Z Z X X X X X M X O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e25a"},"rt":77074,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":736625,"subject":"2P7ZX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeca4922726b49ec42dc3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"08 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM02 PMX X X C G G M B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e25b"},"rt":44376,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":781194,"subject":"2P7ZX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"62bdeca4922726b49ec42dc3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"10 AM02 PM2B B M B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e26c"},"rt":31183,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":106975,"subject":"A41X5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5dd4a7c9c0823f494b158668","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"76609 AM10 AM11 AM11 AMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e26d"},"rt":9305,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":116398,"subject":"A41X5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5dd4a7c9c0823f494b158668","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"Z U U D D 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e26e"},"rt":83232,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":199743,"subject":"A41X5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5dd4a7c9c0823f494b158668","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"01 PMC C C C C C C C C C C C C O O J O O U 01 PM07 PM06 PM10 AMC C C C C A U B B 1C U 11 AM10 AM10 AMA B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e26f"},"rt":22254,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":222551,"subject":"A41X5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5dd4a7c9c0823f494b158668","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"O Z 01 PM06 PM07 PM05 PM04 PME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e270"},"rt":40049,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":262718,"subject":"A41X5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5dd4a7c9c0823f494b158668","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"U E I I I I I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e272"},"rt":35903,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":304872,"subject":"A41X5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5dd4a7c9c0823f494b158668","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"J 10 AMI E E 08 AM09 AM10 AMI E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e273"},"rt":28754,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":333742,"subject":"A41X5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5dd4a7c9c0823f494b158668","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"C C F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e274"},"rt":52231,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":386086,"subject":"A41X5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5dd4a7c9c0823f494b158668","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"E E B B X X X N J B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e275"},"rt":44830,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":431030,"subject":"A41X5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5dd4a7c9c0823f494b158668","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e276"},"rt":31568,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":462718,"subject":"A41X5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5dd4a7c9c0823f494b158668","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"L H H F F F B B 12 PMB B F F B B B B F F A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e277"},"rt":11516,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":474350,"subject":"A41X5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5dd4a7c9c0823f494b158668","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"02 PM12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e278"},"rt":6403,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":480870,"subject":"A41X5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5dd4a7c9c0823f494b158668","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e279"},"rt":61130,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":542110,"subject":"A41X5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5dd4a7c9c0823f494b158668","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,P","hovered":"Z M M Z Z Z J Z Z Z Z Z P P P "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e27a"},"rt":38308,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":580742,"subject":"A41X5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5dd4a7c9c0823f494b158668","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"04 PM03 PM02 PMH 02 PM03 PM01 PM01 PMX F 11 AM10 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e27b"},"rt":34121,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":614982,"subject":"A41X5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5dd4a7c9c0823f494b158668","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"E 11 AM04 PM03 PM02 PM11 AM10 AMF F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e28c"},"rt":20780,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":407879,"subject":"YX963","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ce747ed05a2e2001941e790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e28d"},"rt":20908,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":429107,"subject":"YX963","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ce747ed05a2e2001941e790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"11 AMA A A A O D D 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e28e"},"rt":90293,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":519714,"subject":"YX963","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ce747ed05a2e2001941e790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"3B A U B B B Z C B Z C A U B 06 PM06 PMB B B 01 PMC C C C C C 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e28f"},"rt":87285,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":607350,"subject":"YX963","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ce747ed05a2e2001941e790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"303 PM04 PM05 PM06 PM04 PM04 PME G 05 PM04 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM04 PM04 PME D 02 PM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM08 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e290"},"rt":43921,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":651604,"subject":"YX963","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ce747ed05a2e2001941e790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"1I O K 03 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e292"},"rt":82835,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":755069,"subject":"YX963","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ce747ed05a2e2001941e790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"J F M M X X C K I I M M M 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e293"},"rt":24823,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":780313,"subject":"YX963","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ce747ed05a2e2001941e790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"10 AM09 AMI O F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e294"},"rt":88323,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":869022,"subject":"YX963","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ce747ed05a2e2001941e790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"6B B E G F F B B B E J F I B O O B J E G G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e295"},"rt":20837,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":890202,"subject":"YX963","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ce747ed05a2e2001941e790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e296"},"rt":20079,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":910608,"subject":"YX963","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ce747ed05a2e2001941e790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"2F B 12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e297"},"rt":14058,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":924961,"subject":"YX963","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ce747ed05a2e2001941e790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PMB F F F B 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e298"},"rt":27552,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":952815,"subject":"YX963","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ce747ed05a2e2001941e790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"3I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e299"},"rt":96060,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1049349,"subject":"YX963","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ce747ed05a2e2001941e790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,H","hovered":"Z F Z Z F Z F F 04 PMP P P Z Z H H H H H C H C H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e29a"},"rt":134496,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1184261,"subject":"YX963","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ce747ed05a2e2001941e790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"1L 23I B O O B I I B O O 03 PM03 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM12 PMM M B O O 03 PM03 PMO J J B B O O 03 PMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e29b"},"rt":54916,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1239627,"subject":"YX963","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5ce747ed05a2e2001941e790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"B X 12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMJ 10 AM05 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM01 PMI 02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM02 PMX X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2ac"},"rt":11764,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":68388,"subject":"X2J7T","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61081aed7c3142ce4e945d81","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2ad"},"rt":7477,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":76058,"subject":"X2J7T","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61081aed7c3142ce4e945d81","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2ae"},"rt":14188,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":90445,"subject":"X2J7T","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61081aed7c3142ce4e945d81","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2af"},"rt":34742,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":125473,"subject":"X2J7T","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61081aed7c3142ce4e945d81","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"05 PM04 PMU K K A K I F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2b0"},"rt":28144,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":153802,"subject":"X2J7T","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61081aed7c3142ce4e945d81","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"I U F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2b2"},"rt":8858,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":167684,"subject":"X2J7T","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61081aed7c3142ce4e945d81","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2b3"},"rt":18014,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":185803,"subject":"X2J7T","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61081aed7c3142ce4e945d81","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2b4"},"rt":29518,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":215429,"subject":"X2J7T","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61081aed7c3142ce4e945d81","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E G G F N F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2b5"},"rt":28867,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":244401,"subject":"X2J7T","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61081aed7c3142ce4e945d81","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J J B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2b6"},"rt":20156,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":264665,"subject":"X2J7T","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61081aed7c3142ce4e945d81","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"7F Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2b7"},"rt":9830,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":274603,"subject":"X2J7T","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61081aed7c3142ce4e945d81","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2b8"},"rt":3591,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":278305,"subject":"X2J7T","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61081aed7c3142ce4e945d81","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2b9"},"rt":21059,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":299477,"subject":"X2J7T","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61081aed7c3142ce4e945d81","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"C H O X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2ba"},"rt":14707,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":314290,"subject":"X2J7T","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61081aed7c3142ce4e945d81","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"05 PM04 PM03 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2bb"},"rt":14294,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":328690,"subject":"X2J7T","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61081aed7c3142ce4e945d81","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"01 PM02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2cc"},"rt":29311,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":485966,"subject":"6N7FZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f6f738fef894f0dbf9839f8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"J 05 PMC A Z 12 PM11 AMA A A 08 AMA A A A A X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2cd"},"rt":19811,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":505873,"subject":"6N7FZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f6f738fef894f0dbf9839f8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"01 PMD "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2ce"},"rt":147824,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":653784,"subject":"6N7FZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f6f738fef894f0dbf9839f8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"08 PMC A A 11 AMC C Z Z 01 PMZ Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2cf"},"rt":85285,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":739411,"subject":"6N7FZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f6f738fef894f0dbf9839f8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"G G G B U 12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PME U U U U U U 02 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2d0"},"rt":62941,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":802706,"subject":"6N7FZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f6f738fef894f0dbf9839f8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"C A K I A 11 AMA 10 AM11 AMA 12 PMO O 12 PM11 AM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PMK K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2d2"},"rt":13620,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":821682,"subject":"6N7FZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f6f738fef894f0dbf9839f8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2d3"},"rt":14766,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":836540,"subject":"6N7FZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f6f738fef894f0dbf9839f8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"3C C B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2d4"},"rt":62582,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":899217,"subject":"6N7FZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f6f738fef894f0dbf9839f8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2d5"},"rt":32473,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":932024,"subject":"6N7FZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f6f738fef894f0dbf9839f8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2d6"},"rt":43377,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":975484,"subject":"6N7FZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f6f738fef894f0dbf9839f8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"G B F B B 12 PM12 PMM M B B F F B B B B B F F F X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2d7"},"rt":11077,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":986648,"subject":"6N7FZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f6f738fef894f0dbf9839f8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"309 AM10 AM11 AM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2d8"},"rt":4304,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":991047,"subject":"6N7FZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f6f738fef894f0dbf9839f8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2d9"},"rt":35692,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1026827,"subject":"6N7FZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f6f738fef894f0dbf9839f8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"01 PM02 PM03 PMB J J E F J M X J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2da"},"rt":25014,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1051931,"subject":"6N7FZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f6f738fef894f0dbf9839f8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"212 PMM X B 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2db"},"rt":27815,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1079839,"subject":"6N7FZ","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5f6f738fef894f0dbf9839f8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"O X 03 PM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2ec"},"rt":11773,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":148968,"subject":"JNM09","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bacc9bc42a1d1000187669b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2ed"},"rt":13800,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":162846,"subject":"JNM09","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bacc9bc42a1d1000187669b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2ee"},"rt":24340,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":187261,"subject":"JNM09","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bacc9bc42a1d1000187669b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2ef"},"rt":43295,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":230652,"subject":"JNM09","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bacc9bc42a1d1000187669b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,F,U","hovered":"1Z A C C C C 04 PMK O O K F U H Z Z Z 0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2f0"},"rt":120886,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":351611,"subject":"JNM09","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bacc9bc42a1d1000187669b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I I I I F Z Z Z U U F O H A A K K H E F O K K A A C B B U U A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2f2"},"rt":9301,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":368594,"subject":"JNM09","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bacc9bc42a1d1000187669b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"09 AMI X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2f3"},"rt":17585,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":386264,"subject":"JNM09","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bacc9bc42a1d1000187669b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2f4"},"rt":30922,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":417264,"subject":"JNM09","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bacc9bc42a1d1000187669b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"1J J B M M M 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2f5"},"rt":15900,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":433248,"subject":"JNM09","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bacc9bc42a1d1000187669b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I I B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2f6"},"rt":31185,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":464511,"subject":"JNM09","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bacc9bc42a1d1000187669b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F Z Z Z Z Z C Z L G H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2f7"},"rt":14552,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":479150,"subject":"JNM09","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bacc9bc42a1d1000187669b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"04 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM02 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2f8"},"rt":7548,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":486782,"subject":"JNM09","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bacc9bc42a1d1000187669b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2f9"},"rt":32002,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":518870,"subject":"JNM09","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bacc9bc42a1d1000187669b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"M O O Z C E G H H F X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2fa"},"rt":33072,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":552021,"subject":"JNM09","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bacc9bc42a1d1000187669b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"03 PM03 PMG G M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e2fb"},"rt":28021,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":580125,"subject":"JNM09","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5bacc9bc42a1d1000187669b","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"1M X X G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e30c"},"rt":14534,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":50847,"subject":"GOHER","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61002d0b8920b51da825d9d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,O,I","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AMA C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e30d"},"rt":5863,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":56842,"subject":"GOHER","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61002d0b8920b51da825d9d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"10 AM11 AMA E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e30e"},"rt":14515,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":71487,"subject":"GOHER","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61002d0b8920b51da825d9d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"5O C C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e30f"},"rt":21292,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":93236,"subject":"GOHER","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61002d0b8920b51da825d9d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"03 PM04 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e310"},"rt":16222,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":109678,"subject":"GOHER","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61002d0b8920b51da825d9d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e312"},"rt":5824,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":119131,"subject":"GOHER","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61002d0b8920b51da825d9d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e313"},"rt":21305,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":140572,"subject":"GOHER","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61002d0b8920b51da825d9d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"3I I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e314"},"rt":17459,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":158181,"subject":"GOHER","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61002d0b8920b51da825d9d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"B B F E A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e315"},"rt":21697,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":180286,"subject":"GOHER","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61002d0b8920b51da825d9d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e316"},"rt":5506,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":185921,"subject":"GOHER","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61002d0b8920b51da825d9d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e317"},"rt":4303,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":190361,"subject":"GOHER","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61002d0b8920b51da825d9d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e318"},"rt":6503,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":196917,"subject":"GOHER","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61002d0b8920b51da825d9d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e319"},"rt":15608,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":212660,"subject":"GOHER","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61002d0b8920b51da825d9d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"K L H M M F E E G Z Z Z 02 PM02 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e31a"},"rt":15280,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":228120,"subject":"GOHER","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61002d0b8920b51da825d9d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PMO O O 03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e31b"},"rt":11670,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":240100,"subject":"GOHER","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"61002d0b8920b51da825d9d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e32c"},"rt":74921,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":969027,"subject":"BMT62","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614d465852620924f85603c8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"09 AM09 AM10 AM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM12 PM11 AM11 AMA A 11 AM11 AMA U U U 12 PM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e32d"},"rt":29984,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":999265,"subject":"BMT62","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614d465852620924f85603c8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D D 04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e32e"},"rt":32378,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1031832,"subject":"BMT62","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614d465852620924f85603c8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"K 02 PM01 PM12 PMC C C C 10 AMC C 10 AMC 12 PM12 PM12 PM12 PMZ Z A 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e32f"},"rt":82831,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1114884,"subject":"BMT62","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614d465852620924f85603c8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"02 PM12 PM04 PMU U 12 PM12 PM12 PM12 PMZ Z Z 09 AM008 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM11 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM01 PM01 PM01 PM01 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM05 PM04 PM02 PM03 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e330"},"rt":252463,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1367592,"subject":"BMT62","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614d465852620924f85603c8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I I O O O O O O H 01 PM01 PM01 PM01 PMU 03 PM03 PMK A 11 AM11 AMO O Z 12 PM12 PMZ Z O 11 AMZ O O O O O O 12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMU 12 PM12 PMO O 11 AM11 AMO 12 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM02 PMU Z 02 PMU 02 PM02 PM03 PM05 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM01 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM05 PM04 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e332"},"rt":33819,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1425629,"subject":"BMT62","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614d465852620924f85603c8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"11 AM11 AME E E 3G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e333"},"rt":42055,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1467753,"subject":"BMT62","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614d465852620924f85603c8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"H F F O F J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e334"},"rt":80324,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1548147,"subject":"BMT62","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614d465852620924f85603c8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"C A L F E E G 05 PM05 PM02 PM03 PM40J I J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e335"},"rt":75568,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1623946,"subject":"BMT62","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614d465852620924f85603c8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"E J J I I I J J J J J J J J I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e336"},"rt":93523,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1717730,"subject":"BMT62","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614d465852620924f85603c8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"X X J B B 12 PM12 PM01 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PMX B 12 PM12 PMB B O M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e337"},"rt":24189,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1742167,"subject":"BMT62","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614d465852620924f85603c8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"M 01 PM12 PM12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e338"},"rt":16578,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1758813,"subject":"BMT62","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614d465852620924f85603c8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"10 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e339"},"rt":43591,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1802486,"subject":"BMT62","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614d465852620924f85603c8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z Z Z 04 PM04 PM05 PM04 PMZ X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e33a"},"rt":26556,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1829109,"subject":"BMT62","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614d465852620924f85603c8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"12 PMJ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e33b"},"rt":116679,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1945855,"subject":"BMT62","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"614d465852620924f85603c8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"J J M 02 PM03 PM02 PM01 PMX X 02 PM01 PM03 PM02 PMX 12 PMB B F F F B B 01 PM01 PM02 PM11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM03 PM03 PMJ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e34c"},"rt":13166,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":107456,"subject":"H3NDL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6157503061aaecc87964d076","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e34d"},"rt":7832,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":115373,"subject":"H3NDL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6157503061aaecc87964d076","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e34e"},"rt":33805,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":149253,"subject":"H3NDL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6157503061aaecc87964d076","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"3C C C 09 AM10 AMC A A C C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e34f"},"rt":10525,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":159862,"subject":"H3NDL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6157503061aaecc87964d076","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"F U 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e350"},"rt":42480,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":202425,"subject":"H3NDL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6157503061aaecc87964d076","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"I I I 01 PM01 PM02 PM05 PM06 PMU "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e352"},"rt":8103,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":215880,"subject":"H3NDL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6157503061aaecc87964d076","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e353"},"rt":11061,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":227020,"subject":"H3NDL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6157503061aaecc87964d076","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"2J F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e354"},"rt":31238,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":258338,"subject":"H3NDL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6157503061aaecc87964d076","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e355"},"rt":16718,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":275136,"subject":"H3NDL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6157503061aaecc87964d076","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e356"},"rt":14772,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":289988,"subject":"H3NDL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6157503061aaecc87964d076","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"H F F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e357"},"rt":8612,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":298684,"subject":"H3NDL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6157503061aaecc87964d076","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"10 AM11 AMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e358"},"rt":12069,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":310836,"subject":"H3NDL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6157503061aaecc87964d076","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e359"},"rt":20725,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":331643,"subject":"H3NDL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6157503061aaecc87964d076","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"H Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e35a"},"rt":57204,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":388930,"subject":"H3NDL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6157503061aaecc87964d076","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PMH 04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e35b"},"rt":44516,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":433519,"subject":"H3NDL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6157503061aaecc87964d076","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"03 PM02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e36c"},"rt":129552,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":228496,"subject":"CZNHA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6104b1c50f6057c1d8a6e3a6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e36d"},"rt":46463,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":275060,"subject":"CZNHA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6104b1c50f6057c1d8a6e3a6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"09 AM10 AM12 PMD D K E D D D K K K K K K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e36e"},"rt":23026,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":298114,"subject":"CZNHA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6104b1c50f6057c1d8a6e3a6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"08 AMC C C 11 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e36f"},"rt":36173,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":334319,"subject":"CZNHA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6104b1c50f6057c1d8a6e3a6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"04 PM04 PM04 PM5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e370"},"rt":46325,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":380673,"subject":"CZNHA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6104b1c50f6057c1d8a6e3a6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A I I I F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e372"},"rt":17415,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":409925,"subject":"CZNHA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6104b1c50f6057c1d8a6e3a6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"14E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e373"},"rt":50713,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":460668,"subject":"CZNHA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6104b1c50f6057c1d8a6e3a6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F F B I J J X X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e374"},"rt":75124,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":535824,"subject":"CZNHA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6104b1c50f6057c1d8a6e3a6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B X X J E E E J G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e375"},"rt":23765,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":559705,"subject":"CZNHA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6104b1c50f6057c1d8a6e3a6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"E 2J J I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e376"},"rt":14336,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":574073,"subject":"CZNHA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6104b1c50f6057c1d8a6e3a6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e377"},"rt":22031,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":596135,"subject":"CZNHA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6104b1c50f6057c1d8a6e3a6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PM12 PM12 PMM M M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e378"},"rt":11244,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":607409,"subject":"CZNHA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6104b1c50f6057c1d8a6e3a6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e379"},"rt":14518,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":621951,"subject":"CZNHA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6104b1c50f6057c1d8a6e3a6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e37a"},"rt":16798,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":638776,"subject":"CZNHA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6104b1c50f6057c1d8a6e3a6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM03 PMX X X B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e37b"},"rt":31305,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":670109,"subject":"CZNHA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6104b1c50f6057c1d8a6e3a6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PM02 PMK K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e38c"},"rt":17391,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1630510,"subject":"6BK5K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60d13d406f3b34d6791c8831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e38d"},"rt":16622,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1647225,"subject":"6BK5K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60d13d406f3b34d6791c8831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"008 AM09 AME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e38e"},"rt":29094,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1676409,"subject":"6BK5K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60d13d406f3b34d6791c8831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"Z C Z Z Z A C C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e38f"},"rt":65294,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1741795,"subject":"6BK5K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60d13d406f3b34d6791c8831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"01 PMZ Z U U 02 PMU 01 PMZ O O O O O U U H 01 PMF F 12 PM11 AM12 PM01 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e390"},"rt":97087,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":1839214,"subject":"6BK5K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60d13d406f3b34d6791c8831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I I O O O A F F F H H F F O F 01 PMU U U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e392"},"rt":12646,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1863800,"subject":"6BK5K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60d13d406f3b34d6791c8831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"O E E E G G E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e393"},"rt":23375,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1887263,"subject":"6BK5K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60d13d406f3b34d6791c8831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F B F B B B B F F F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e394"},"rt":54562,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1941915,"subject":"6BK5K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60d13d406f3b34d6791c8831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G B B J J J E E 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e395"},"rt":56941,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1998950,"subject":"6BK5K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60d13d406f3b34d6791c8831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"C B B B I I I B J J J B J 10 AMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e396"},"rt":55042,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2054084,"subject":"6BK5K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60d13d406f3b34d6791c8831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B B B F F F F B B M X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e397"},"rt":12928,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2067101,"subject":"6BK5K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60d13d406f3b34d6791c8831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"212 PM12 PMB B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e398"},"rt":12763,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2079953,"subject":"6BK5K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60d13d406f3b34d6791c8831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F 12 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e399"},"rt":41460,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":2121504,"subject":"6BK5K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60d13d406f3b34d6791c8831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"X Z 04 PMX X X X F X B F Z F 12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e39a"},"rt":72659,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2194255,"subject":"6BK5K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60d13d406f3b34d6791c8831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"X M M M M B B B B B B B M F F 12 PM11 AME B G G G G C C O O X X M X O H Z Z X X B B M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e39b"},"rt":48685,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":2243189,"subject":"6BK5K","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"60d13d406f3b34d6791c8831","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X M M B B B B B F F 12 PM12 PMX F B F F F E J J B B G 01 PMF F F B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3ac"},"rt":64989,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":185069,"subject":"RR0NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5de6cf8c601a8f035e47b907","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3ad"},"rt":10871,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":196292,"subject":"RR0NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5de6cf8c601a8f035e47b907","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3ae"},"rt":27275,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":223708,"subject":"RR0NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5de6cf8c601a8f035e47b907","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3af"},"rt":87883,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":311855,"subject":"RR0NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5de6cf8c601a8f035e47b907","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3b0"},"rt":111201,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":423387,"subject":"RR0NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5de6cf8c601a8f035e47b907","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3b2"},"rt":14036,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":444282,"subject":"RR0NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5de6cf8c601a8f035e47b907","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"55"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3b3"},"rt":34557,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":478996,"subject":"RR0NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5de6cf8c601a8f035e47b907","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3b4"},"rt":148444,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":627590,"subject":"RR0NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5de6cf8c601a8f035e47b907","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"B B X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3b5"},"rt":35146,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":663368,"subject":"RR0NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5de6cf8c601a8f035e47b907","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I","hovered":"J J B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3b6"},"rt":143884,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":807662,"subject":"RR0NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5de6cf8c601a8f035e47b907","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J B F Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3b7"},"rt":19337,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":827354,"subject":"RR0NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5de6cf8c601a8f035e47b907","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3b8"},"rt":9624,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":837233,"subject":"RR0NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5de6cf8c601a8f035e47b907","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3b9"},"rt":110027,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":947834,"subject":"RR0NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5de6cf8c601a8f035e47b907","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"C Z Z F Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3ba"},"rt":126386,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1074565,"subject":"RR0NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5de6cf8c601a8f035e47b907","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3bb"},"rt":172350,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1247299,"subject":"RR0NP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5de6cf8c601a8f035e47b907","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PM03 PM1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3cc"},"rt":16366,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":108515,"subject":"J7ZQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"610016a0ab72f8793ea043e5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"6511 AMA C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3cd"},"rt":29726,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":138299,"subject":"J7ZQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"610016a0ab72f8793ea043e5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"D E E 04 PME D 5E E G 05 PMD E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3ce"},"rt":21495,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":159859,"subject":"J7ZQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"610016a0ab72f8793ea043e5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3cf"},"rt":66139,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":226059,"subject":"J7ZQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"610016a0ab72f8793ea043e5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"U U A C U U U U Z F H H H H J H H 01 PMI O O O A A A Z Z Z Z Z F F F F 01 PM02 PMA F U U U 03 PM03 PM03 PMJ H H H 01 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3d0"},"rt":93351,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":319592,"subject":"J7ZQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"610016a0ab72f8793ea043e5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I I O O O O I O O O O O O O 03 PM03 PMU U U 03 PMF F H 01 PMH H O O C C C K U U H H J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3d2"},"rt":7910,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":333148,"subject":"J7ZQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"610016a0ab72f8793ea043e5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"2E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3d3"},"rt":21679,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":354889,"subject":"J7ZQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"610016a0ab72f8793ea043e5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C H H C C F B B B F F F B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3d4"},"rt":107625,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":462582,"subject":"J7ZQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"610016a0ab72f8793ea043e5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"7L G B 12 PM12 PMB B F M M X 04 PM05 PM05 PMI I I J J B E E E G E E X X X E E B X X E G G G F F J 2J J J J I I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3d5"},"rt":50280,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":513046,"subject":"J7ZQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"610016a0ab72f8793ea043e5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J I B I I 10 AMI B 12 PMI B F J J J J J 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3d6"},"rt":56762,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":569874,"subject":"J7ZQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"610016a0ab72f8793ea043e5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B F F B B F F Z I 09 AMJ 11 AMM M M B F E 11 AME G G G C X X X X X O K K K K K P P H N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3d7"},"rt":10790,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":580731,"subject":"J7ZQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"610016a0ab72f8793ea043e5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"06 PM05 PM12 PMB B 12 PME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3d8"},"rt":10162,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":590959,"subject":"J7ZQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"610016a0ab72f8793ea043e5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3d9"},"rt":44186,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":635205,"subject":"J7ZQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"610016a0ab72f8793ea043e5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z 04 PM04 PMZ O O H M X M M C C H Z C G G G E F B B M M 04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3da"},"rt":37387,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":672645,"subject":"J7ZQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"610016a0ab72f8793ea043e5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"O X M M B A E O B J J I E B B F B B B M M M C C G G A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3db"},"rt":77809,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":750514,"subject":"J7ZQM","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"610016a0ab72f8793ea043e5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"11 AM02 PM12 PMM M M B 12 PMB B F B B B F J 10 AMJ J J I X X X C E 11 AMH C E 11 AME G 01 PMF B B B 12 PMB B F B F X X M M 12 PMM M C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3ec"},"rt":20468,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":57457,"subject":"350NF","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"630633e8b2adbf1157f42b22","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3ed"},"rt":8211,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":65741,"subject":"350NF","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"630633e8b2adbf1157f42b22","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"Z K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3ee"},"rt":13051,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":78864,"subject":"350NF","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"630633e8b2adbf1157f42b22","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3ef"},"rt":29008,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":107927,"subject":"350NF","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"630633e8b2adbf1157f42b22","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"08 PM07 PM06 PM04 PM03 PM02 PMA C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3f0"},"rt":57312,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":165292,"subject":"350NF","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"630633e8b2adbf1157f42b22","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"I I I O O C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3f2"},"rt":6577,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":178019,"subject":"350NF","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"630633e8b2adbf1157f42b22","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3f3"},"rt":20216,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":198296,"subject":"350NF","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"630633e8b2adbf1157f42b22","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3f4"},"rt":38675,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":237026,"subject":"350NF","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"630633e8b2adbf1157f42b22","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"F F B B J J J B E E F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3f5"},"rt":19068,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":256152,"subject":"350NF","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"630633e8b2adbf1157f42b22","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"1X J I J I B B I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3f6"},"rt":78696,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":334904,"subject":"350NF","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"630633e8b2adbf1157f42b22","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J F F B B Z 8F Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3f7"},"rt":8898,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":346988,"subject":"350NF","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"630633e8b2adbf1157f42b22","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3f8"},"rt":6039,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":353093,"subject":"350NF","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"630633e8b2adbf1157f42b22","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3f9"},"rt":46910,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":400074,"subject":"350NF","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"630633e8b2adbf1157f42b22","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z F Z Z E G Z Z Z Z C H O X J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3fa"},"rt":64697,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":464838,"subject":"350NF","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"630633e8b2adbf1157f42b22","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"X M M X X B B O O B 02 PM02 PMB E E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e3fb"},"rt":83302,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":548299,"subject":"350NF","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"630633e8b2adbf1157f42b22","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"12 PM02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e40c"},"rt":40689,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":122305,"subject":"M0PPP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5f878ac24e7e5f1ba4237c09","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AM11 AM11 AMA A A 02 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMB C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e40d"},"rt":7495,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":129901,"subject":"M0PPP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5f878ac24e7e5f1ba4237c09","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e40e"},"rt":12098,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":142093,"subject":"M0PPP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5f878ac24e7e5f1ba4237c09","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e40f"},"rt":37311,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":179500,"subject":"M0PPP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5f878ac24e7e5f1ba4237c09","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"Z 04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e410"},"rt":77873,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":257468,"subject":"M0PPP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5f878ac24e7e5f1ba4237c09","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"U I I 12 PMO O I K K 03 PMK K H C A A Z F F F O I U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e412"},"rt":7380,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":269737,"subject":"M0PPP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5f878ac24e7e5f1ba4237c09","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e413"},"rt":16094,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":285926,"subject":"M0PPP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5f878ac24e7e5f1ba4237c09","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"10 AM11 AM1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e414"},"rt":103701,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":389720,"subject":"M0PPP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5f878ac24e7e5f1ba4237c09","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E 05 PMX M M M B B F F I X X E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e415"},"rt":17802,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":407825,"subject":"M0PPP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5f878ac24e7e5f1ba4237c09","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e416"},"rt":43917,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":451838,"subject":"M0PPP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5f878ac24e7e5f1ba4237c09","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"04 PMX N X X X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e417"},"rt":6755,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":458691,"subject":"M0PPP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5f878ac24e7e5f1ba4237c09","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e418"},"rt":8236,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":467022,"subject":"M0PPP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5f878ac24e7e5f1ba4237c09","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e419"},"rt":90759,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":557876,"subject":"M0PPP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5f878ac24e7e5f1ba4237c09","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"08 AM09 AMM X Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z X X X Z Z X X X X X X X X X F E I E A A G G X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e41a"},"rt":32749,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":590938,"subject":"M0PPP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5f878ac24e7e5f1ba4237c09","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"103 PM12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e41b"},"rt":36511,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":627541,"subject":"M0PPP","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5f878ac24e7e5f1ba4237c09","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"M X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e42c"},"rt":38638,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":113820,"subject":"LJTQR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d29346269a747001acdb205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"122C C 11 AMA A 11 AM11 AMA 11 AMC C 08 AMI I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e42d"},"rt":8365,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":122280,"subject":"LJTQR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d29346269a747001acdb205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e42e"},"rt":8645,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":131015,"subject":"LJTQR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d29346269a747001acdb205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e42f"},"rt":6867,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":137972,"subject":"LJTQR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d29346269a747001acdb205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e430"},"rt":13715,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":151779,"subject":"LJTQR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d29346269a747001acdb205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"O O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e432"},"rt":6699,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":163140,"subject":"LJTQR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d29346269a747001acdb205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e433"},"rt":30389,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":193618,"subject":"LJTQR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d29346269a747001acdb205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"B O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e434"},"rt":39534,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":233249,"subject":"LJTQR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d29346269a747001acdb205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"3B 36E G G J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e435"},"rt":52049,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":285388,"subject":"LJTQR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d29346269a747001acdb205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J E J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e436"},"rt":8331,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":293812,"subject":"LJTQR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d29346269a747001acdb205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e437"},"rt":11869,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":305772,"subject":"LJTQR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d29346269a747001acdb205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e438"},"rt":7336,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":313197,"subject":"LJTQR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d29346269a747001acdb205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e439"},"rt":15222,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":328510,"subject":"LJTQR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d29346269a747001acdb205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"N Z Z 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e43a"},"rt":7128,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":335729,"subject":"LJTQR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d29346269a747001acdb205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e43b"},"rt":13231,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":349051,"subject":"LJTQR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d29346269a747001acdb205","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e44c"},"rt":21063,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":120575,"subject":"WDQ37","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fdfe436bebd218b540b54f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AM11 AMA 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e44d"},"rt":25037,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":145658,"subject":"WDQ37","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fdfe436bebd218b540b54f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e44e"},"rt":86090,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":231792,"subject":"WDQ37","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fdfe436bebd218b540b54f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e44f"},"rt":83126,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":315027,"subject":"WDQ37","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fdfe436bebd218b540b54f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,U","hovered":"O O O 7I I I C C H 11 AMZ Z Z Z Z F F F F 03 PMO H F F O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e450"},"rt":209014,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":524147,"subject":"WDQ37","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fdfe436bebd218b540b54f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e452"},"rt":11045,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":540385,"subject":"WDQ37","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fdfe436bebd218b540b54f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e453"},"rt":26288,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":566711,"subject":"WDQ37","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fdfe436bebd218b540b54f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e454"},"rt":99758,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":666509,"subject":"WDQ37","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fdfe436bebd218b540b54f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E E 6E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e455"},"rt":51060,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":717679,"subject":"WDQ37","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fdfe436bebd218b540b54f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e456"},"rt":60403,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":778119,"subject":"WDQ37","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fdfe436bebd218b540b54f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e457"},"rt":16452,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":794688,"subject":"WDQ37","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fdfe436bebd218b540b54f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e458"},"rt":11677,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":806403,"subject":"WDQ37","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fdfe436bebd218b540b54f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e459"},"rt":21156,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":827595,"subject":"WDQ37","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fdfe436bebd218b540b54f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e45a"},"rt":43831,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":871466,"subject":"WDQ37","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fdfe436bebd218b540b54f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e45b"},"rt":173941,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1045438,"subject":"WDQ37","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fdfe436bebd218b540b54f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e46c"},"rt":31152,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":352487,"subject":"0VG7G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62696bb2397d5c5496064e56","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"510 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM08 PM08 PM03 PM12 PM11 AM11 AMA C A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e46d"},"rt":14962,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":367508,"subject":"0VG7G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62696bb2397d5c5496064e56","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"12 PME 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e46e"},"rt":79806,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":447369,"subject":"0VG7G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62696bb2397d5c5496064e56","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PMC C O O O C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e46f"},"rt":49492,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":497074,"subject":"0VG7G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62696bb2397d5c5496064e56","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e470"},"rt":51920,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":549064,"subject":"0VG7G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62696bb2397d5c5496064e56","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"7I 12 PM12 PMI 101112X I I 12F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e472"},"rt":36294,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":594188,"subject":"0VG7G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62696bb2397d5c5496064e56","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,M","hovered":"I E E J J A E F F G G G B C L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e473"},"rt":70453,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":664712,"subject":"0VG7G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62696bb2397d5c5496064e56","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,O","hovered":"09 AM09 AMJ X N J I B O I E J F B B C P I B O H O B C F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e474"},"rt":71124,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":736092,"subject":"0VG7G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62696bb2397d5c5496064e56","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I","hovered":"54I B B B J A A J B F F B B B E 7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e475"},"rt":46207,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":782548,"subject":"0VG7G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62696bb2397d5c5496064e56","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I I J J J I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e476"},"rt":18830,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":801451,"subject":"0VG7G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62696bb2397d5c5496064e56","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"F F F B F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e477"},"rt":13674,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":815180,"subject":"0VG7G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62696bb2397d5c5496064e56","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e478"},"rt":16277,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":831518,"subject":"0VG7G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62696bb2397d5c5496064e56","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e479"},"rt":58625,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":890211,"subject":"0VG7G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62696bb2397d5c5496064e56","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,P","hovered":"5Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e47a"},"rt":59635,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":949979,"subject":"0VG7G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62696bb2397d5c5496064e56","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"M 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e47b"},"rt":33776,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":983830,"subject":"0VG7G","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62696bb2397d5c5496064e56","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"02 PMX X I K X 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e48c"},"rt":49439,"condition":"11111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":184401,"subject":"MP5P5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5658000ca9872d0011e1ba26","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"211 AMA A A A A A C B Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e48d"},"rt":20827,"condition":"11111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":205350,"subject":"MP5P5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5658000ca9872d0011e1ba26","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"4E E D G G G G E E D D D E E E E E E K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e48e"},"rt":67295,"condition":"11111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":272764,"subject":"MP5P5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5658000ca9872d0011e1ba26","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"4A 10 AMC A 10 AMC 10 AM10 AM11 AMC 10 AMA A C 11 AMZ Z Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e48f"},"rt":79852,"condition":"11111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":352984,"subject":"MP5P5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5658000ca9872d0011e1ba26","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"F F U U Z 01 PMU G U U K K H O O U U U Z Z G B B B B G G G G G G K K K X F F O A 0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e490"},"rt":400927,"condition":"11111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":754265,"subject":"MP5P5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5658000ca9872d0011e1ba26","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"09 AMZ I I O A 11 AM11 AMI 03 PMH U U F A C 65I U B B B G G K K F F F F Z Z 08 AM11 AMU U F U K H O A A C C O I 5H H H J K K O O O F F I U U F O O I I O O I I O O I H F F A Z Z F U U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e492"},"rt":9464,"condition":"11111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":774187,"subject":"MP5P5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5658000ca9872d0011e1ba26","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"5G E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e493"},"rt":26946,"condition":"11111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":801300,"subject":"MP5P5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5658000ca9872d0011e1ba26","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"1F F F B B B F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e494"},"rt":55525,"condition":"11111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":856967,"subject":"MP5P5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5658000ca9872d0011e1ba26","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"4E E E B B B B B B F A E E 11 AMB B F F E X X J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e495"},"rt":57416,"condition":"11111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":914517,"subject":"MP5P5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5658000ca9872d0011e1ba26","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I I 10 AM11 AM12 PM11 AMJ J J I E B M M D M 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e496"},"rt":58422,"condition":"11111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":973074,"subject":"MP5P5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5658000ca9872d0011e1ba26","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F 04 PMX 09 AM10 AM03 PM02 PMX N D N O B B B B B M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e497"},"rt":9201,"condition":"11111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":982436,"subject":"MP5P5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5658000ca9872d0011e1ba26","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM01 PM12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e498"},"rt":19645,"condition":"11111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1002199,"subject":"MP5P5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5658000ca9872d0011e1ba26","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F B B B F F F B B 12 PM12 PMB B F F 12 PM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e499"},"rt":51410,"condition":"11111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1053774,"subject":"MP5P5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5658000ca9872d0011e1ba26","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"X N N Z B X 12 PM01 PMO X J J B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e49a"},"rt":53966,"condition":"11111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1107873,"subject":"MP5P5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5658000ca9872d0011e1ba26","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AMM M B B B B J J J I I X O O O X X 02 PMM M X N X B B B B B J 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e49b"},"rt":186697,"condition":"11111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1294987,"subject":"MP5P5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305bc183e587c9c646d5f33","sona_id":"5658000ca9872d0011e1ba26","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,J","hovered":"10 AM10 AM11 AM10 AMI B F B B B M M B J C C C E E G C C C G E B B 12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4ac"},"rt":18149,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":111231,"subject":"M8XM5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ff1e2a6e2955fdf4315335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4ad"},"rt":13288,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":124678,"subject":"M8XM5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ff1e2a6e2955fdf4315335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"4D D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4ae"},"rt":19151,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":143945,"subject":"M8XM5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ff1e2a6e2955fdf4315335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4af"},"rt":29355,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":173860,"subject":"M8XM5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ff1e2a6e2955fdf4315335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A Z 12 PMZ F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4b0"},"rt":72823,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":246827,"subject":"M8XM5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ff1e2a6e2955fdf4315335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4b2"},"rt":13298,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":267622,"subject":"M8XM5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ff1e2a6e2955fdf4315335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4b3"},"rt":27444,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":295193,"subject":"M8XM5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ff1e2a6e2955fdf4315335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4B F B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4b4"},"rt":84143,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":379409,"subject":"M8XM5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ff1e2a6e2955fdf4315335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E B B B F F B B B B B B B B F F E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4b5"},"rt":73370,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":453042,"subject":"M8XM5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ff1e2a6e2955fdf4315335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"O O O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4b6"},"rt":39809,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":493208,"subject":"M8XM5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ff1e2a6e2955fdf4315335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4b7"},"rt":21857,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":515191,"subject":"M8XM5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ff1e2a6e2955fdf4315335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4b8"},"rt":16214,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":531475,"subject":"M8XM5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ff1e2a6e2955fdf4315335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4b9"},"rt":52430,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":584374,"subject":"M8XM5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ff1e2a6e2955fdf4315335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"H Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4ba"},"rt":42480,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":626924,"subject":"M8XM5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ff1e2a6e2955fdf4315335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4bb"},"rt":49397,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":676391,"subject":"M8XM5","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ff1e2a6e2955fdf4315335","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,E,F","hovered":"E B I 12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PMX X 02 PM02 PMX F 02 PMX X B C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4cc"},"rt":56977,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":123433,"subject":"G75FS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62f45af2edd9fe55b26f4ec7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A A A C 08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4cd"},"rt":11684,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":135195,"subject":"G75FS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62f45af2edd9fe55b26f4ec7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4ce"},"rt":40798,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":176071,"subject":"G75FS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62f45af2edd9fe55b26f4ec7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4cf"},"rt":55056,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":231197,"subject":"G75FS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62f45af2edd9fe55b26f4ec7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"O 3C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4d0"},"rt":62679,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":293963,"subject":"G75FS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62f45af2edd9fe55b26f4ec7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4d2"},"rt":18229,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":318356,"subject":"G75FS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62f45af2edd9fe55b26f4ec7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4d3"},"rt":57151,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":375589,"subject":"G75FS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62f45af2edd9fe55b26f4ec7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4d4"},"rt":59792,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":435455,"subject":"G75FS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62f45af2edd9fe55b26f4ec7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"11 AM12 PMB B X E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4d5"},"rt":56327,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":491863,"subject":"G75FS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62f45af2edd9fe55b26f4ec7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4d6"},"rt":42832,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":534784,"subject":"G75FS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62f45af2edd9fe55b26f4ec7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"M M 12 PM2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4d7"},"rt":209,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":535080,"subject":"G75FS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62f45af2edd9fe55b26f4ec7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4d8"},"rt":16381,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":551542,"subject":"G75FS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62f45af2edd9fe55b26f4ec7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4d9"},"rt":17174,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":568802,"subject":"G75FS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62f45af2edd9fe55b26f4ec7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4da"},"rt":31580,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":600469,"subject":"G75FS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62f45af2edd9fe55b26f4ec7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"08 AM02 PM03 PMO G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4db"},"rt":101359,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":701909,"subject":"G75FS","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62f45af2edd9fe55b26f4ec7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,M","hovered":"M M B B B M B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4ec"},"rt":12573,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":63112,"subject":"SYW8Y","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5c49484a6d9ae80001a1aa72","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"211 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4ed"},"rt":13179,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":76972,"subject":"SYW8Y","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5c49484a6d9ae80001a1aa72","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D E E Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4ee"},"rt":15782,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":93430,"subject":"SYW8Y","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5c49484a6d9ae80001a1aa72","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4ef"},"rt":61624,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":155256,"subject":"SYW8Y","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5c49484a6d9ae80001a1aa72","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM02 PMH H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4f0"},"rt":18725,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":174476,"subject":"SYW8Y","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5c49484a6d9ae80001a1aa72","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4f2"},"rt":9312,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":188593,"subject":"SYW8Y","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5c49484a6d9ae80001a1aa72","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4f3"},"rt":20093,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":209547,"subject":"SYW8Y","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5c49484a6d9ae80001a1aa72","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4f4"},"rt":63220,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":273541,"subject":"SYW8Y","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5c49484a6d9ae80001a1aa72","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J G C C O O F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4f5"},"rt":26093,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":300067,"subject":"SYW8Y","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5c49484a6d9ae80001a1aa72","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I J 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4f6"},"rt":11841,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":312420,"subject":"SYW8Y","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5c49484a6d9ae80001a1aa72","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"O F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4f7"},"rt":7663,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":321324,"subject":"SYW8Y","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5c49484a6d9ae80001a1aa72","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4f8"},"rt":9024,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":330756,"subject":"SYW8Y","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5c49484a6d9ae80001a1aa72","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"08 AM09 AMF F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4f9"},"rt":26259,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":359488,"subject":"SYW8Y","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5c49484a6d9ae80001a1aa72","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,O","hovered":"23N Z O I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4fa"},"rt":7265,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":367023,"subject":"SYW8Y","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5c49484a6d9ae80001a1aa72","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e4fb"},"rt":31936,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":399416,"subject":"SYW8Y","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5c49484a6d9ae80001a1aa72","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,Z","hovered":"01 PM01 PM02 PM02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e50c"},"rt":38420,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":104989,"subject":"G7V3A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fd7ee255d0c660dfafff5a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"10 AM11 AMA 12 PMA F Z Z F F F 02 PMC F F F 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e50d"},"rt":6518,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":111540,"subject":"G7V3A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fd7ee255d0c660dfafff5a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e50e"},"rt":8399,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":119974,"subject":"G7V3A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fd7ee255d0c660dfafff5a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e50f"},"rt":5354,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":125357,"subject":"G7V3A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fd7ee255d0c660dfafff5a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e510"},"rt":33477,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":158864,"subject":"G7V3A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fd7ee255d0c660dfafff5a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"O O O U U 09 AMI 02 PM03 PMH "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e512"},"rt":10261,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":174300,"subject":"G7V3A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fd7ee255d0c660dfafff5a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"I I F E 6E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e513"},"rt":21184,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":195508,"subject":"G7V3A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fd7ee255d0c660dfafff5a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"J F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e514"},"rt":35564,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":231096,"subject":"G7V3A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fd7ee255d0c660dfafff5a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E E E B B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e515"},"rt":22254,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":253449,"subject":"G7V3A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fd7ee255d0c660dfafff5a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F J J B B 11 AM11 AMJ 6B 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e516"},"rt":6524,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":260000,"subject":"G7V3A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fd7ee255d0c660dfafff5a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e517"},"rt":6690,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":266719,"subject":"G7V3A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fd7ee255d0c660dfafff5a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"10 AM12 PM01 PMM M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e518"},"rt":11357,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":278104,"subject":"G7V3A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fd7ee255d0c660dfafff5a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e519"},"rt":24130,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":302258,"subject":"G7V3A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fd7ee255d0c660dfafff5a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"C A A X Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e51a"},"rt":5154,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":307443,"subject":"G7V3A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fd7ee255d0c660dfafff5a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e51b"},"rt":16174,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":323647,"subject":"G7V3A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fd7ee255d0c660dfafff5a","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"C 02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e52c"},"rt":39522,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":76784,"subject":"MY0UR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"J J J 11 AM12 PM01 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e52d"},"rt":15649,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":92748,"subject":"MY0UR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"01 PM02 PM01 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e52e"},"rt":18051,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":111162,"subject":"MY0UR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e52f"},"rt":2643,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":114119,"subject":"MY0UR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e530"},"rt":2340,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":116838,"subject":"MY0UR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e532"},"rt":3829,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":122930,"subject":"MY0UR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e533"},"rt":2831,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":126075,"subject":"MY0UR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e534"},"rt":2395,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":128787,"subject":"MY0UR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e535"},"rt":3738,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":132837,"subject":"MY0UR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e536"},"rt":4948,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":138101,"subject":"MY0UR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e537"},"rt":6013,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":144489,"subject":"MY0UR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e538"},"rt":2642,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":147467,"subject":"MY0UR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e539"},"rt":2164,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":149944,"subject":"MY0UR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e53a"},"rt":2409,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":152665,"subject":"MY0UR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e53b"},"rt":2578,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":155594,"subject":"MY0UR","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e54c"},"rt":40479,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":164512,"subject":"22FPD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"622a426e8900cf2b495353e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e54d"},"rt":14923,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":181523,"subject":"22FPD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"622a426e8900cf2b495353e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e54e"},"rt":37132,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":223534,"subject":"22FPD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"622a426e8900cf2b495353e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"01 PM12 PM11 AM1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e54f"},"rt":63290,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":286901,"subject":"22FPD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"622a426e8900cf2b495353e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e550"},"rt":64816,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":357796,"subject":"22FPD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"622a426e8900cf2b495353e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"5I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e552"},"rt":19558,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":381449,"subject":"22FPD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"622a426e8900cf2b495353e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e553"},"rt":34114,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":415643,"subject":"22FPD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"622a426e8900cf2b495353e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e554"},"rt":43022,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":461683,"subject":"22FPD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"622a426e8900cf2b495353e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e555"},"rt":34784,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":497507,"subject":"22FPD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"622a426e8900cf2b495353e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e556"},"rt":33974,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":531578,"subject":"22FPD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"622a426e8900cf2b495353e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B B B B F B B 04 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e557"},"rt":20020,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":552403,"subject":"22FPD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"622a426e8900cf2b495353e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e558"},"rt":21109,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":573674,"subject":"22FPD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"622a426e8900cf2b495353e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e559"},"rt":54300,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":629042,"subject":"22FPD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"622a426e8900cf2b495353e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e55a"},"rt":131765,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":764666,"subject":"22FPD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"622a426e8900cf2b495353e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"202 PM03 PMH B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e55b"},"rt":3729,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":768551,"subject":"22FPD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"622a426e8900cf2b495353e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e56c"},"rt":3291,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":34819,"subject":"KVZT7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e56d"},"rt":2686,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":37815,"subject":"KVZT7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e56e"},"rt":2630,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":40753,"subject":"KVZT7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e56f"},"rt":2574,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":43646,"subject":"KVZT7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e570"},"rt":2796,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":46750,"subject":"KVZT7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e572"},"rt":2721,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":51796,"subject":"KVZT7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e573"},"rt":3197,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":55300,"subject":"KVZT7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e574"},"rt":2862,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":58472,"subject":"KVZT7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e575"},"rt":3335,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":62112,"subject":"KVZT7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e576"},"rt":4399,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":66794,"subject":"KVZT7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e577"},"rt":2767,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":69866,"subject":"KVZT7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e578"},"rt":2694,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":72868,"subject":"KVZT7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e579"},"rt":2112,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":75287,"subject":"KVZT7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e57a"},"rt":2978,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":78578,"subject":"KVZT7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e57b"},"rt":2923,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":81811,"subject":"KVZT7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d9fa04cd8034b0016b65d79","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e58c"},"rt":11829,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":70481,"subject":"63CND","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fba37f3560a85b4eb94aac","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e58d"},"rt":9246,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":79836,"subject":"63CND","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fba37f3560a85b4eb94aac","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e58e"},"rt":27359,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":107306,"subject":"63CND","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fba37f3560a85b4eb94aac","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e58f"},"rt":46883,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":154305,"subject":"63CND","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fba37f3560a85b4eb94aac","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e590"},"rt":123670,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":278095,"subject":"63CND","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fba37f3560a85b4eb94aac","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"O O I I 08 PM07 PM06 PM05 PM04 PMK K K 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e592"},"rt":16725,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":304235,"subject":"63CND","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fba37f3560a85b4eb94aac","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e593"},"rt":21640,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":325992,"subject":"63CND","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fba37f3560a85b4eb94aac","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e594"},"rt":156702,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":482809,"subject":"63CND","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fba37f3560a85b4eb94aac","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"3B 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e595"},"rt":39523,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":522880,"subject":"63CND","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fba37f3560a85b4eb94aac","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I I I J E E B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e596"},"rt":41888,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":564891,"subject":"63CND","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fba37f3560a85b4eb94aac","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F X M M X F 04 PM04 PMO X X M J J E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e597"},"rt":8992,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":574003,"subject":"63CND","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fba37f3560a85b4eb94aac","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e598"},"rt":12935,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":587045,"subject":"63CND","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fba37f3560a85b4eb94aac","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e599"},"rt":106313,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":693465,"subject":"63CND","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fba37f3560a85b4eb94aac","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"B X X Z Z H 08 PM08 PM08 PM08 PM07 PM06 PM03 PM01 PM09 AM11 AM11 AML M M M A K K K A A A H H O C C C G Z Z 2F X M M M M M F 2X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e59a"},"rt":48566,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":742460,"subject":"63CND","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fba37f3560a85b4eb94aac","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"12 PMX M J I 05 PM04 PM04 PM10 AME E E E E J A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e59b"},"rt":36328,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":778909,"subject":"63CND","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fba37f3560a85b4eb94aac","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"B B 2F F X X X X X X X 6E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5ac"},"rt":20597,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":121123,"subject":"9JE0Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"628409abe8772d1f138b7f14","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5ad"},"rt":10862,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":132083,"subject":"9JE0Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"628409abe8772d1f138b7f14","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A K E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5ae"},"rt":58092,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":190283,"subject":"9JE0Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"628409abe8772d1f138b7f14","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"C 09 AM10 AM11 AMA 10 AM11 AMF F Z C 09 AMO C O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5af"},"rt":11814,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":202196,"subject":"9JE0Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"628409abe8772d1f138b7f14","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5b0"},"rt":30219,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":232512,"subject":"9JE0Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"628409abe8772d1f138b7f14","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"11 AM12 PM01 PMI I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5b2"},"rt":17132,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":259125,"subject":"9JE0Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"628409abe8772d1f138b7f14","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"09 AMG "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5b3"},"rt":37134,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":296360,"subject":"9JE0Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"628409abe8772d1f138b7f14","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5b4"},"rt":57968,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":354431,"subject":"9JE0Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"628409abe8772d1f138b7f14","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5b5"},"rt":28982,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":383514,"subject":"9JE0Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"628409abe8772d1f138b7f14","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5b6"},"rt":7887,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":391507,"subject":"9JE0Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"628409abe8772d1f138b7f14","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5b7"},"rt":11927,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":403541,"subject":"9JE0Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"628409abe8772d1f138b7f14","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PM01 PM01 PMM M M L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5b8"},"rt":6787,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":410430,"subject":"9JE0Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"628409abe8772d1f138b7f14","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"1F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5b9"},"rt":27258,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":437793,"subject":"9JE0Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"628409abe8772d1f138b7f14","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":"1Z Z Z 02 PMZ Z Z Z Z H N N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5ba"},"rt":9616,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":447514,"subject":"9JE0Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"628409abe8772d1f138b7f14","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X 04 PM03 PMX X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5bb"},"rt":17562,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":465189,"subject":"9JE0Q","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"628409abe8772d1f138b7f14","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5cc"},"rt":10792,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":66328,"subject":"VO1X9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5eb7c006b839846ea7a24178","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5cd"},"rt":7148,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":73528,"subject":"VO1X9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5eb7c006b839846ea7a24178","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5ce"},"rt":10118,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":83703,"subject":"VO1X9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5eb7c006b839846ea7a24178","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PMC A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5cf"},"rt":12822,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":96577,"subject":"VO1X9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5eb7c006b839846ea7a24178","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PMF E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5d0"},"rt":63198,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":159822,"subject":"VO1X9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5eb7c006b839846ea7a24178","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"O I O O I I I F H H U U U C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5d2"},"rt":23191,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":186895,"subject":"VO1X9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5eb7c006b839846ea7a24178","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"08 AME E E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5d3"},"rt":14711,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":201679,"subject":"VO1X9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5eb7c006b839846ea7a24178","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5d4"},"rt":18693,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":220421,"subject":"VO1X9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5eb7c006b839846ea7a24178","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"12 PMM B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5d5"},"rt":11363,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":231837,"subject":"VO1X9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5eb7c006b839846ea7a24178","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"01 PM02 PM11 AMJ J I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5d6"},"rt":12194,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":244080,"subject":"VO1X9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5eb7c006b839846ea7a24178","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"O Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5d7"},"rt":8274,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":252408,"subject":"VO1X9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5eb7c006b839846ea7a24178","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"02 PM11 AM12 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5d8"},"rt":4957,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":257429,"subject":"VO1X9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5eb7c006b839846ea7a24178","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5d9"},"rt":23437,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":280912,"subject":"VO1X9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5eb7c006b839846ea7a24178","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,F","hovered":"Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5da"},"rt":21361,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":302322,"subject":"VO1X9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5eb7c006b839846ea7a24178","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5db"},"rt":64229,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":366607,"subject":"VO1X9","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5eb7c006b839846ea7a24178","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"09 AM12 PMA X X X X X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5ec"},"rt":13039,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":49828,"subject":"57Y8A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fe17a7fbe55f58560251a3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PM11 AM11 AM08 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5ed"},"rt":10262,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":60144,"subject":"57Y8A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fe17a7fbe55f58560251a3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F E E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5ee"},"rt":14274,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":74467,"subject":"57Y8A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fe17a7fbe55f58560251a3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"A C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5ef"},"rt":10751,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":85267,"subject":"57Y8A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fe17a7fbe55f58560251a3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"A Z U U U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5f0"},"rt":40486,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":125802,"subject":"57Y8A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fe17a7fbe55f58560251a3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I I O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5f2"},"rt":9496,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":139338,"subject":"57Y8A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fe17a7fbe55f58560251a3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5f3"},"rt":10095,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":149485,"subject":"57Y8A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fe17a7fbe55f58560251a3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5f4"},"rt":21767,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":171298,"subject":"57Y8A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fe17a7fbe55f58560251a3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5f5"},"rt":12495,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":183843,"subject":"57Y8A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fe17a7fbe55f58560251a3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"E I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5f6"},"rt":22564,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":206456,"subject":"57Y8A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fe17a7fbe55f58560251a3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F 12 PM09 AME J 10 AME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5f7"},"rt":5597,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":212104,"subject":"57Y8A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fe17a7fbe55f58560251a3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"J 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5f8"},"rt":7232,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":219383,"subject":"57Y8A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fe17a7fbe55f58560251a3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"7F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5f9"},"rt":41534,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":260965,"subject":"57Y8A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fe17a7fbe55f58560251a3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,X","hovered":"H X X X C M M G E E M 12 PM12 PMB 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5fa"},"rt":24489,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":285502,"subject":"57Y8A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fe17a7fbe55f58560251a3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"A 801 PMM M J X X 08 AMJ M B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e5fb"},"rt":7514,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":293062,"subject":"57Y8A","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60fe17a7fbe55f58560251a3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e60c"},"rt":46476,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":121624,"subject":"W8HY1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62c805770a334345890d18b9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AM12 PM12 PM11 AMA A 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e60d"},"rt":6374,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":128057,"subject":"W8HY1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62c805770a334345890d18b9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"6D E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e60e"},"rt":25927,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":154049,"subject":"W8HY1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62c805770a334345890d18b9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C C C C C A A A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e60f"},"rt":51277,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":205373,"subject":"W8HY1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62c805770a334345890d18b9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"U 04 PMU 04 PMU E E E E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e610"},"rt":29182,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":234781,"subject":"W8HY1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62c805770a334345890d18b9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e612"},"rt":11322,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":249422,"subject":"W8HY1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62c805770a334345890d18b9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AM11E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e613"},"rt":9004,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":258464,"subject":"W8HY1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62c805770a334345890d18b9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"E B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e614"},"rt":22322,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":280968,"subject":"W8HY1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62c805770a334345890d18b9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"G E E E G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e615"},"rt":33239,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":314339,"subject":"W8HY1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62c805770a334345890d18b9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e616"},"rt":23924,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":338313,"subject":"W8HY1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62c805770a334345890d18b9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I 3Z O Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e617"},"rt":10361,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":348728,"subject":"W8HY1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62c805770a334345890d18b9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM12 PMB B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e618"},"rt":4353,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":353151,"subject":"W8HY1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62c805770a334345890d18b9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"I O F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e619"},"rt":34855,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":388082,"subject":"W8HY1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62c805770a334345890d18b9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"I I B B O Z Z 04 PMZ Z F Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e61a"},"rt":43037,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":431171,"subject":"W8HY1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62c805770a334345890d18b9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"03 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e61b"},"rt":78392,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":509610,"subject":"W8HY1","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62c805770a334345890d18b9","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"F 02 PMX X 02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e62c"},"rt":32997,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":169529,"subject":"KG1XD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dbdb8628c86b2a3824da16","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AMA A 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e62d"},"rt":10165,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":179744,"subject":"KG1XD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dbdb8628c86b2a3824da16","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e62e"},"rt":133190,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":312972,"subject":"KG1XD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dbdb8628c86b2a3824da16","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C 10 AM06 PM06 PM05 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM11 AM10 AM10 AM10 AM06 PM06 PM06 PM06 PM12 PM12 PM10 AM08 PMG Z F U C U Z A J E D F Z A U B B B F F K A H A A A A C C C C C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e62f"},"rt":79214,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":392327,"subject":"KG1XD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dbdb8628c86b2a3824da16","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"2Z 04 PME E E E E E E 04 PM05 PM08 PM07 PMK 03 PM04 PMU "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e630"},"rt":50586,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":443203,"subject":"KG1XD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dbdb8628c86b2a3824da16","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"I H I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e632"},"rt":13973,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":471803,"subject":"KG1XD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dbdb8628c86b2a3824da16","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e633"},"rt":24931,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":496771,"subject":"KG1XD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dbdb8628c86b2a3824da16","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e634"},"rt":13479,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":510402,"subject":"KG1XD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dbdb8628c86b2a3824da16","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I,J","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e635"},"rt":17918,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":528444,"subject":"KG1XD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dbdb8628c86b2a3824da16","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e636"},"rt":28897,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":557379,"subject":"KG1XD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dbdb8628c86b2a3824da16","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z,X","hovered":"Z Z O O O C E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e637"},"rt":12563,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":570077,"subject":"KG1XD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dbdb8628c86b2a3824da16","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM01 PM12 PM12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e638"},"rt":12189,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":583021,"subject":"KG1XD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dbdb8628c86b2a3824da16","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e639"},"rt":48060,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":639244,"subject":"KG1XD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dbdb8628c86b2a3824da16","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"12 PM09 AM08 AM1Z Z Z O B 5B B O H Z X X X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e63a"},"rt":58345,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":697719,"subject":"KG1XD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dbdb8628c86b2a3824da16","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM03 PM3J 01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM211 AM12 PM03 PM503 PM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e63b"},"rt":27650,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":725628,"subject":"KG1XD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dbdb8628c86b2a3824da16","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"J M 02 PMX X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e64c"},"rt":21078,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":165395,"subject":"X6HV7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"56e72067c89073000be77fdf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"C 12 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM06 PM07 PM08 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM09 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e64d"},"rt":20106,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":185565,"subject":"X6HV7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"56e72067c89073000be77fdf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"F B D K K K Z 12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e64e"},"rt":19173,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":204832,"subject":"X6HV7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"56e72067c89073000be77fdf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"K H C C C C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e64f"},"rt":59969,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":264878,"subject":"X6HV7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"56e72067c89073000be77fdf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"3305 PM06 PM05 PM04 PM03 PMC 5I O O O I I 08 AM08 AM08 AM09 AMH H H 10 AM10 AM11 AM403 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e650"},"rt":49508,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":314456,"subject":"X6HV7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"56e72067c89073000be77fdf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I I 03 PM03 PMI I I C C O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e652"},"rt":7054,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":325218,"subject":"X6HV7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"56e72067c89073000be77fdf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e653"},"rt":25034,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":350314,"subject":"X6HV7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"56e72067c89073000be77fdf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e654"},"rt":36868,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":387245,"subject":"X6HV7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"56e72067c89073000be77fdf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"56E E I I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e655"},"rt":16960,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":404268,"subject":"X6HV7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"56e72067c89073000be77fdf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e656"},"rt":8152,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":412483,"subject":"X6HV7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"56e72067c89073000be77fdf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"X X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e657"},"rt":11539,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":424083,"subject":"X6HV7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"56e72067c89073000be77fdf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"I 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e658"},"rt":6437,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":430580,"subject":"X6HV7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"56e72067c89073000be77fdf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e659"},"rt":8837,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":439478,"subject":"X6HV7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"56e72067c89073000be77fdf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e65a"},"rt":7709,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":447249,"subject":"X6HV7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"56e72067c89073000be77fdf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e65b"},"rt":14687,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":461998,"subject":"X6HV7","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"56e72067c89073000be77fdf","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e66c"},"rt":9965,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":191814,"subject":"KGOFH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62a378da05bc514b69023189","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e66d"},"rt":36301,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":228173,"subject":"KGOFH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62a378da05bc514b69023189","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e66e"},"rt":42152,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":270386,"subject":"KGOFH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62a378da05bc514b69023189","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"09 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e66f"},"rt":15118,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":285844,"subject":"KGOFH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62a378da05bc514b69023189","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e670"},"rt":46563,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":332467,"subject":"KGOFH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62a378da05bc514b69023189","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"B B B K I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e672"},"rt":8146,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":343720,"subject":"KGOFH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62a378da05bc514b69023189","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"09 AME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e673"},"rt":55686,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":399463,"subject":"KGOFH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62a378da05bc514b69023189","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,O","hovered":"F C F F 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e674"},"rt":35817,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":435341,"subject":"KGOFH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62a378da05bc514b69023189","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"108 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e675"},"rt":18118,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":453522,"subject":"KGOFH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62a378da05bc514b69023189","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e676"},"rt":7960,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":461544,"subject":"KGOFH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62a378da05bc514b69023189","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"08 AMB F E E E F F J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e677"},"rt":4837,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":466440,"subject":"KGOFH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62a378da05bc514b69023189","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e678"},"rt":6338,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":472840,"subject":"KGOFH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62a378da05bc514b69023189","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e679"},"rt":14943,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":487848,"subject":"KGOFH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62a378da05bc514b69023189","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e67a"},"rt":6023,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":493929,"subject":"KGOFH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62a378da05bc514b69023189","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e67b"},"rt":26294,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":520283,"subject":"KGOFH","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62a378da05bc514b69023189","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e68c"},"rt":50665,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":147434,"subject":"0B9KO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"577f70d1454e5400015f1845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e68d"},"rt":22446,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":169977,"subject":"0B9KO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"577f70d1454e5400015f1845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e68e"},"rt":16957,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":187030,"subject":"0B9KO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"577f70d1454e5400015f1845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"08 AM03 PMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e68f"},"rt":57837,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":244971,"subject":"0B9KO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"577f70d1454e5400015f1845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,U","hovered":"Z U Z Z A K K 09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e690"},"rt":53612,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":298680,"subject":"0B9KO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"577f70d1454e5400015f1845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"1I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e692"},"rt":15087,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":321684,"subject":"0B9KO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"577f70d1454e5400015f1845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e693"},"rt":24298,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":346082,"subject":"0B9KO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"577f70d1454e5400015f1845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"4F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e694"},"rt":38965,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":385149,"subject":"0B9KO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"577f70d1454e5400015f1845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e695"},"rt":18880,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":404130,"subject":"0B9KO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"577f70d1454e5400015f1845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"M M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e696"},"rt":57674,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":461902,"subject":"0B9KO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"577f70d1454e5400015f1845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"C M M M X X B B E 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e697"},"rt":9257,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":471256,"subject":"0B9KO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"577f70d1454e5400015f1845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e698"},"rt":8408,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":479759,"subject":"0B9KO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"577f70d1454e5400015f1845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"I J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e699"},"rt":77563,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":557421,"subject":"0B9KO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"577f70d1454e5400015f1845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"01 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e69a"},"rt":73168,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":630895,"subject":"0B9KO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"577f70d1454e5400015f1845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"X X M M B F C X O G A A A H B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e69b"},"rt":38281,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":669487,"subject":"0B9KO","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"577f70d1454e5400015f1845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"12 PM01 PMM M J B B I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6ac"},"rt":14507,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":56386,"subject":"5GRSD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5e149c03864020aa6e1cf04d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6ad"},"rt":14606,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":71055,"subject":"5GRSD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5e149c03864020aa6e1cf04d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6ae"},"rt":9130,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":80279,"subject":"5GRSD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5e149c03864020aa6e1cf04d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"Z A C 10 AM11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6af"},"rt":29209,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":109579,"subject":"5GRSD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5e149c03864020aa6e1cf04d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"Z U U U 02 PM01 PMU U H H J H 02 PM05 PM01 PM12 PMO O O A O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6b0"},"rt":29226,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":138863,"subject":"5GRSD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5e149c03864020aa6e1cf04d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"I I I O O 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6b2"},"rt":6247,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":151239,"subject":"5GRSD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5e149c03864020aa6e1cf04d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"H C E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6b3"},"rt":11177,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":162470,"subject":"5GRSD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5e149c03864020aa6e1cf04d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6b4"},"rt":41698,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":204227,"subject":"5GRSD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5e149c03864020aa6e1cf04d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"1X B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6b5"},"rt":17063,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":221414,"subject":"5GRSD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5e149c03864020aa6e1cf04d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6b6"},"rt":11464,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":232935,"subject":"5GRSD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5e149c03864020aa6e1cf04d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"08 AM11 AMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6b7"},"rt":7369,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":240358,"subject":"5GRSD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5e149c03864020aa6e1cf04d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6b8"},"rt":7027,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":247472,"subject":"5GRSD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5e149c03864020aa6e1cf04d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6b9"},"rt":24131,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":271663,"subject":"5GRSD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5e149c03864020aa6e1cf04d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"08 AMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6ba"},"rt":45482,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":317233,"subject":"5GRSD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5e149c03864020aa6e1cf04d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"12 PMB N N X J F I B B F B B 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6bb"},"rt":37649,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":354938,"subject":"5GRSD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5e149c03864020aa6e1cf04d","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"B B E B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6cc"},"rt":9059,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":78319,"subject":"PUPNU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62bdcbd1a1792d25af8c4e96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6cd"},"rt":11226,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":89614,"subject":"PUPNU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62bdcbd1a1792d25af8c4e96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6ce"},"rt":15856,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":105534,"subject":"PUPNU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62bdcbd1a1792d25af8c4e96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6cf"},"rt":22578,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":128176,"subject":"PUPNU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62bdcbd1a1792d25af8c4e96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6d0"},"rt":31266,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":159528,"subject":"PUPNU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62bdcbd1a1792d25af8c4e96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"11 AM11 AM01 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM08 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6d2"},"rt":12557,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":176423,"subject":"PUPNU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62bdcbd1a1792d25af8c4e96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"7"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6d3"},"rt":17285,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":193768,"subject":"PUPNU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62bdcbd1a1792d25af8c4e96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6d4"},"rt":29423,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":223257,"subject":"PUPNU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62bdcbd1a1792d25af8c4e96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"M 10 AM11 AM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6d5"},"rt":15127,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":238450,"subject":"PUPNU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62bdcbd1a1792d25af8c4e96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6d6"},"rt":20241,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":258754,"subject":"PUPNU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62bdcbd1a1792d25af8c4e96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"Z Z Z 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6d7"},"rt":6183,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":265251,"subject":"PUPNU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62bdcbd1a1792d25af8c4e96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6d8"},"rt":5344,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":270658,"subject":"PUPNU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62bdcbd1a1792d25af8c4e96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6d9"},"rt":15507,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":286226,"subject":"PUPNU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62bdcbd1a1792d25af8c4e96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"O Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6da"},"rt":27651,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":313952,"subject":"PUPNU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62bdcbd1a1792d25af8c4e96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B X 04 PM12 PM11 AM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6db"},"rt":47252,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":361266,"subject":"PUPNU","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62bdcbd1a1792d25af8c4e96","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"07 PMB B 6G E 11 AM12 PM01 PM01 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6ec"},"rt":10934,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":63279,"subject":"S1RTD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5589cd58fdf99b18be3203af","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"303 PM06 PM07 PM06 PM04 PM02 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6ed"},"rt":11063,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":74407,"subject":"S1RTD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5589cd58fdf99b18be3203af","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"05 PM02 PMD J D D D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6ee"},"rt":15629,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":90127,"subject":"S1RTD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5589cd58fdf99b18be3203af","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM03 PMZ Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6ef"},"rt":26575,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":116778,"subject":"S1RTD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5589cd58fdf99b18be3203af","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"10 AME G G E 04 PM04 PM04 PME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6f0"},"rt":36502,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":153344,"subject":"S1RTD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5589cd58fdf99b18be3203af","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I 11 AM11 AM10 AM09 AMO 4"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6f2"},"rt":6086,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":165383,"subject":"S1RTD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5589cd58fdf99b18be3203af","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6f3"},"rt":26996,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":192439,"subject":"S1RTD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5589cd58fdf99b18be3203af","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6f4"},"rt":157033,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":349535,"subject":"S1RTD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5589cd58fdf99b18be3203af","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,O","hovered":"X L B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6f5"},"rt":17630,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":367335,"subject":"S1RTD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5589cd58fdf99b18be3203af","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J I I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6f6"},"rt":14455,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":381847,"subject":"S1RTD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5589cd58fdf99b18be3203af","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6f7"},"rt":10228,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":392175,"subject":"S1RTD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5589cd58fdf99b18be3203af","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"08 AMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6f8"},"rt":7913,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":400143,"subject":"S1RTD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5589cd58fdf99b18be3203af","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"08 AMO F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6f9"},"rt":12187,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":412439,"subject":"S1RTD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5589cd58fdf99b18be3203af","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,P","hovered":"Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6fa"},"rt":20302,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":432798,"subject":"S1RTD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5589cd58fdf99b18be3203af","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"05 PM04 PM1204 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e6fb"},"rt":19297,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":452159,"subject":"S1RTD","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5589cd58fdf99b18be3203af","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"05 PM05 PM04 PM04 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e70c"},"rt":10715,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":58409,"subject":"MVXS8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fdda76250ace9232630851","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e70d"},"rt":7136,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":65670,"subject":"MVXS8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fdda76250ace9232630851","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e70e"},"rt":20508,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":86299,"subject":"MVXS8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fdda76250ace9232630851","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,I","hovered":"2C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e70f"},"rt":34739,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":121154,"subject":"MVXS8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fdda76250ace9232630851","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"Z Z Z C F F O O H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e710"},"rt":62159,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":183435,"subject":"MVXS8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fdda76250ace9232630851","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"I O O O O I O O F F Z F F F 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e712"},"rt":9668,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":197553,"subject":"MVXS8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fdda76250ace9232630851","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e713"},"rt":11924,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":209594,"subject":"MVXS8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fdda76250ace9232630851","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e714"},"rt":19496,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":229214,"subject":"MVXS8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fdda76250ace9232630851","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e715"},"rt":33884,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":263223,"subject":"MVXS8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fdda76250ace9232630851","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"401 PM02 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e716"},"rt":18986,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":282322,"subject":"MVXS8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fdda76250ace9232630851","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e717"},"rt":13104,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":295547,"subject":"MVXS8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fdda76250ace9232630851","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"K K M 01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e718"},"rt":4075,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":299744,"subject":"MVXS8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fdda76250ace9232630851","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e719"},"rt":28170,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":328035,"subject":"MVXS8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fdda76250ace9232630851","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"X X X M M M B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e71a"},"rt":14345,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":342497,"subject":"MVXS8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fdda76250ace9232630851","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e71b"},"rt":14088,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":356707,"subject":"MVXS8","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62fdda76250ace9232630851","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e72c"},"rt":20243,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":203874,"subject":"MSY24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dc2f588e2518753d3e0e12","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMA 11 AMA A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e72d"},"rt":10582,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":219561,"subject":"MSY24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dc2f588e2518753d3e0e12","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e72e"},"rt":9363,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":231486,"subject":"MSY24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dc2f588e2518753d3e0e12","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e72f"},"rt":19217,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":260823,"subject":"MSY24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dc2f588e2518753d3e0e12","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"04 PM04 PM04 PME D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e730"},"rt":61551,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":324543,"subject":"MSY24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dc2f588e2518753d3e0e12","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,E","hovered":"K J I 10I 456O 3911X X X I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e732"},"rt":8488,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":340880,"subject":"MSY24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dc2f588e2518753d3e0e12","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e733"},"rt":31873,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":374864,"subject":"MSY24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dc2f588e2518753d3e0e12","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"3C C C F B B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e734"},"rt":105103,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":488520,"subject":"MSY24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dc2f588e2518753d3e0e12","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.41666666666666663,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":5,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,H,N,O,Z","hovered":"F E E E E E E E O O O F O L X X X O Z Z H H N B H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e735"},"rt":38941,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":529493,"subject":"MSY24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dc2f588e2518753d3e0e12","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J J J B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e736"},"rt":11106,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":542786,"subject":"MSY24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dc2f588e2518753d3e0e12","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e737"},"rt":10732,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":556023,"subject":"MSY24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dc2f588e2518753d3e0e12","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PMB 11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e738"},"rt":12138,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":570557,"subject":"MSY24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dc2f588e2518753d3e0e12","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"4F F 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e739"},"rt":98359,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":671991,"subject":"MSY24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dc2f588e2518753d3e0e12","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,L","hovered":"C Z 05 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e73a"},"rt":14693,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":688927,"subject":"MSY24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dc2f588e2518753d3e0e12","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"08 AM09 AM02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e73b"},"rt":31884,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":722992,"subject":"MSY24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62dc2f588e2518753d3e0e12","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"01 PM02 PMX X 09 AM08 AM01 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e74c"},"rt":18941,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":96578,"subject":"1GLWL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"611c0228cb6bd61a906c8845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"05 PM11 AM10 AM11 AMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e74d"},"rt":31296,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":127938,"subject":"1GLWL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"611c0228cb6bd61a906c8845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F D D D D E E E 04 PM04 PM04 PMU "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e74e"},"rt":21847,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":149848,"subject":"1GLWL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"611c0228cb6bd61a906c8845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e74f"},"rt":61689,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":211605,"subject":"1GLWL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"611c0228cb6bd61a906c8845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"04 PM3K 04 PMD 05 PM04 PMU U 05 PMU A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e750"},"rt":116216,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":327981,"subject":"1GLWL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"611c0228cb6bd61a906c8845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,Z","hovered":"I I O O O I I O O O 04 PMI Z 3Z 11 AMO 12 PM11 AM12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e752"},"rt":19342,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":354865,"subject":"1GLWL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"611c0228cb6bd61a906c8845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"03 PMF Z H G E E 11 AME G G 01 PM01 PMG E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e753"},"rt":18489,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":373449,"subject":"1GLWL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"611c0228cb6bd61a906c8845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"J B B F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e754"},"rt":21214,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":394728,"subject":"1GLWL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"611c0228cb6bd61a906c8845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G","hovered":"07 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e755"},"rt":18917,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":413708,"subject":"1GLWL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"611c0228cb6bd61a906c8845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e756"},"rt":6870,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":420650,"subject":"1GLWL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"611c0228cb6bd61a906c8845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"06 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e757"},"rt":8619,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":429333,"subject":"1GLWL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"611c0228cb6bd61a906c8845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e758"},"rt":6638,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":436040,"subject":"1GLWL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"611c0228cb6bd61a906c8845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e759"},"rt":68015,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":504120,"subject":"1GLWL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"611c0228cb6bd61a906c8845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"N O F F B B 12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM05 PM04 PM04 PMM 04 PM04 PM04 PMO 06 PM06 PM112 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e75a"},"rt":23542,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":527817,"subject":"1GLWL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"611c0228cb6bd61a906c8845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"06 PM05 PM04 PMB M 12 PM01 PM03 PM02 PMM B B F X X M 01 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e75b"},"rt":33913,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":561828,"subject":"1GLWL","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"611c0228cb6bd61a906c8845","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM02 PM03 PMX X X X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e76c"},"rt":28529,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":571422,"subject":"FBHZA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ef4d541f9d5122ffad5d48","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"05 PM10 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e76d"},"rt":19219,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":592322,"subject":"FBHZA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ef4d541f9d5122ffad5d48","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"10 AM10 AMZ F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e76e"},"rt":30740,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":624949,"subject":"FBHZA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ef4d541f9d5122ffad5d48","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"03 PMZ C C 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e76f"},"rt":150234,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":776716,"subject":"FBHZA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ef4d541f9d5122ffad5d48","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,U","hovered":"03 PM04 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PME E E 01 PMU U F C A A U U 11 AMU F 04 PM04 PMF F F O K O 5"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e770"},"rt":88427,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":866716,"subject":"FBHZA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ef4d541f9d5122ffad5d48","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"O I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e772"},"rt":23965,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":904227,"subject":"FBHZA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ef4d541f9d5122ffad5d48","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"10 AMF E E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e773"},"rt":36467,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":942171,"subject":"FBHZA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ef4d541f9d5122ffad5d48","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e774"},"rt":50147,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":996234,"subject":"FBHZA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ef4d541f9d5122ffad5d48","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F C C G G B 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e775"},"rt":26625,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1024575,"subject":"FBHZA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ef4d541f9d5122ffad5d48","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I I 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e776"},"rt":68440,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1094362,"subject":"FBHZA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ef4d541f9d5122ffad5d48","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F B F Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e777"},"rt":16986,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1112864,"subject":"FBHZA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ef4d541f9d5122ffad5d48","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"02 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e778"},"rt":20885,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1135142,"subject":"FBHZA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ef4d541f9d5122ffad5d48","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e779"},"rt":64664,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1201168,"subject":"FBHZA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ef4d541f9d5122ffad5d48","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"D O Z Z Z Z Z Z Z O Z Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e77a"},"rt":104322,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1306962,"subject":"FBHZA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ef4d541f9d5122ffad5d48","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"11 AM03 PM03 PMO O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e77b"},"rt":118825,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1427543,"subject":"FBHZA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"60ef4d541f9d5122ffad5d48","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PM02 PMX X 02 PM02 PMX B J 02 PM02 PMG C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e78c"},"rt":21689,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":72008,"subject":"56OL3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d7dcf8f366c9e001bd6ed73","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e78d"},"rt":10600,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":82681,"subject":"56OL3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d7dcf8f366c9e001bd6ed73","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e78e"},"rt":14300,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":97041,"subject":"56OL3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d7dcf8f366c9e001bd6ed73","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e78f"},"rt":25137,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":122246,"subject":"56OL3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d7dcf8f366c9e001bd6ed73","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e790"},"rt":57742,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":180052,"subject":"56OL3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d7dcf8f366c9e001bd6ed73","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e792"},"rt":9238,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":193226,"subject":"56OL3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d7dcf8f366c9e001bd6ed73","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e793"},"rt":9652,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":202944,"subject":"56OL3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d7dcf8f366c9e001bd6ed73","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e794"},"rt":17375,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":220388,"subject":"56OL3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d7dcf8f366c9e001bd6ed73","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e795"},"rt":16075,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":236530,"subject":"56OL3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d7dcf8f366c9e001bd6ed73","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e796"},"rt":21809,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":258406,"subject":"56OL3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d7dcf8f366c9e001bd6ed73","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e797"},"rt":7352,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":265828,"subject":"56OL3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d7dcf8f366c9e001bd6ed73","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e798"},"rt":6085,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":271981,"subject":"56OL3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d7dcf8f366c9e001bd6ed73","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e799"},"rt":37121,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":309169,"subject":"56OL3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d7dcf8f366c9e001bd6ed73","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e79a"},"rt":26204,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":335447,"subject":"56OL3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d7dcf8f366c9e001bd6ed73","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e79b"},"rt":35921,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":371433,"subject":"56OL3","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5d7dcf8f366c9e001bd6ed73","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7ac"},"rt":14179,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":170103,"subject":"2OPH4","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5aedfba176b763000132f7fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7ad"},"rt":15203,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":185370,"subject":"2OPH4","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5aedfba176b763000132f7fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7ae"},"rt":86792,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":272222,"subject":"2OPH4","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5aedfba176b763000132f7fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7af"},"rt":50646,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":323076,"subject":"2OPH4","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5aedfba176b763000132f7fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7b0"},"rt":62456,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":385589,"subject":"2OPH4","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5aedfba176b763000132f7fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7b2"},"rt":14685,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":406369,"subject":"2OPH4","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5aedfba176b763000132f7fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7b3"},"rt":14263,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":420689,"subject":"2OPH4","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5aedfba176b763000132f7fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7b4"},"rt":27181,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":447925,"subject":"2OPH4","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5aedfba176b763000132f7fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7b5"},"rt":17835,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":465815,"subject":"2OPH4","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5aedfba176b763000132f7fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7b6"},"rt":48829,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":514702,"subject":"2OPH4","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5aedfba176b763000132f7fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7b7"},"rt":6336,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":521094,"subject":"2OPH4","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5aedfba176b763000132f7fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7b8"},"rt":5728,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":526879,"subject":"2OPH4","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5aedfba176b763000132f7fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7b9"},"rt":17146,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":544082,"subject":"2OPH4","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5aedfba176b763000132f7fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7ba"},"rt":25971,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":570109,"subject":"2OPH4","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5aedfba176b763000132f7fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7bb"},"rt":32039,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":602202,"subject":"2OPH4","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5aedfba176b763000132f7fe","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7cc"},"rt":28238,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":78278,"subject":"AHBSX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6153262ce40377b67913ca13","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7cd"},"rt":10886,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":89219,"subject":"AHBSX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6153262ce40377b67913ca13","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7ce"},"rt":6691,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":96021,"subject":"AHBSX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6153262ce40377b67913ca13","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"10 AMC C 11 AMZ F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7cf"},"rt":7984,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":104079,"subject":"AHBSX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6153262ce40377b67913ca13","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"04 PM04 PMZ C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7d0"},"rt":51438,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":155581,"subject":"AHBSX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6153262ce40377b67913ca13","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,O","hovered":"08 AMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7d2"},"rt":20066,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":180906,"subject":"AHBSX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6153262ce40377b67913ca13","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"10 AM10 AME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7d3"},"rt":36156,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":217119,"subject":"AHBSX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6153262ce40377b67913ca13","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"09 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7d4"},"rt":56411,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":273606,"subject":"AHBSX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6153262ce40377b67913ca13","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"02 PMF F B B B F E E E E 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7d5"},"rt":16291,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":290068,"subject":"AHBSX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6153262ce40377b67913ca13","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7d6"},"rt":6982,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":297186,"subject":"AHBSX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6153262ce40377b67913ca13","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7d7"},"rt":8002,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":305259,"subject":"AHBSX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6153262ce40377b67913ca13","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7d8"},"rt":7790,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":313117,"subject":"AHBSX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6153262ce40377b67913ca13","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7d9"},"rt":13951,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":327120,"subject":"AHBSX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6153262ce40377b67913ca13","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"05 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7da"},"rt":8248,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":335424,"subject":"AHBSX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6153262ce40377b67913ca13","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7db"},"rt":17379,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":352883,"subject":"AHBSX","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"6153262ce40377b67913ca13","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7ec"},"rt":21974,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":94437,"subject":"09NKA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"589fcf7a9b4be40001fdcff5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7ed"},"rt":10624,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":105174,"subject":"09NKA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"589fcf7a9b4be40001fdcff5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"06 PMD D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7ee"},"rt":85985,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":191288,"subject":"09NKA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"589fcf7a9b4be40001fdcff5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"09 AM10 AM11 AMC 10 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM11 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7ef"},"rt":63782,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":255426,"subject":"09NKA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"589fcf7a9b4be40001fdcff5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PMD D K H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7f0"},"rt":53631,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":309426,"subject":"09NKA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"589fcf7a9b4be40001fdcff5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,E","hovered":"05 PMI I O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7f2"},"rt":8553,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":324413,"subject":"09NKA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"589fcf7a9b4be40001fdcff5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"X E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7f3"},"rt":33369,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":357890,"subject":"09NKA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"589fcf7a9b4be40001fdcff5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"09 AM10 AM02 PM11 AMJ 11 AM01 PMM M F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7f4"},"rt":40819,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":398812,"subject":"09NKA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"589fcf7a9b4be40001fdcff5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"02 PM12 PMM 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7f5"},"rt":24316,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":423250,"subject":"09NKA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"589fcf7a9b4be40001fdcff5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"10 AM10 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7f6"},"rt":58557,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":482004,"subject":"09NKA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"589fcf7a9b4be40001fdcff5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"3J F F F 04 PM04 PM09 AMI J E F B B B M M M X X O O G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7f7"},"rt":8427,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":490546,"subject":"09NKA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"589fcf7a9b4be40001fdcff5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM12 PM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7f8"},"rt":6215,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":496862,"subject":"09NKA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"589fcf7a9b4be40001fdcff5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"01 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7f9"},"rt":54517,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":551485,"subject":"09NKA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"589fcf7a9b4be40001fdcff5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"09 AM10 AM06 PMD Z Z Z 04 PM03 PM12 PM09 AM09 AM09 AM10 AM10 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM11 AM12 PM01 PMB O B B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7fa"},"rt":27832,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":579422,"subject":"09NKA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"589fcf7a9b4be40001fdcff5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM03 PM11 AMF B B B F 03 PM04 PMO X X C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e7fb"},"rt":40640,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":620166,"subject":"09NKA","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"589fcf7a9b4be40001fdcff5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,E","hovered":"02 PM02 PMI J 02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e80c"},"rt":33064,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":302824,"subject":"WGD06","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62e31a9ce71b2e2da6fafbd4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"109 AM10 AM11 AM09 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e80d"},"rt":28091,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":332125,"subject":"WGD06","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62e31a9ce71b2e2da6fafbd4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"08 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e80e"},"rt":27310,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":360186,"subject":"WGD06","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62e31a9ce71b2e2da6fafbd4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"01 PM12 PM02 PM12 PMZ C C A A C C A C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e80f"},"rt":20731,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":381584,"subject":"WGD06","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62e31a9ce71b2e2da6fafbd4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"08 AM09 AM12 PM01 PM03 PM04 PM04 PME E E E H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e810"},"rt":62517,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":444718,"subject":"WGD06","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62e31a9ce71b2e2da6fafbd4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"O I I I 01 PMF F 12 PM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e812"},"rt":105364,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":588014,"subject":"WGD06","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62e31a9ce71b2e2da6fafbd4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"301 PM10 AMI M 10 AM10 AMI 403 PM04 PM05 PM06 PM07 PM07 PM06 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PMO X 12 PM12 PM01 PM10 AMJ 11 AM12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PMC C X X J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e813"},"rt":200576,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":789335,"subject":"WGD06","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62e31a9ce71b2e2da6fafbd4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,H","hovered":"F B M H N P A A F J E J B M G K K K E E M M G 01 PMC H H F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e814"},"rt":34990,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":825252,"subject":"WGD06","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62e31a9ce71b2e2da6fafbd4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":"G X N N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e815"},"rt":84944,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":911169,"subject":"WGD06","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62e31a9ce71b2e2da6fafbd4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J M J 22I I 09 AMI B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e816"},"rt":16709,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":928873,"subject":"WGD06","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62e31a9ce71b2e2da6fafbd4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM10 AMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e817"},"rt":35749,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":965306,"subject":"WGD06","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62e31a9ce71b2e2da6fafbd4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e818"},"rt":5927,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":971876,"subject":"WGD06","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62e31a9ce71b2e2da6fafbd4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"4J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e819"},"rt":165188,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1137330,"subject":"WGD06","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62e31a9ce71b2e2da6fafbd4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"J Z Z Z Z Z Z O I J Z F 5Z Z Z Z Z Z Z B Z Z Z Z H Z Z H H L H H C H H H H 01 PM01 PMJ O B B Z Z Z Z Z Z Z 04 PMZ Z Z Z Z Z P Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e81a"},"rt":45381,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1183674,"subject":"WGD06","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62e31a9ce71b2e2da6fafbd4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"12 PM11 AM08 AM04 PM03 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e81b"},"rt":24873,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1209293,"subject":"WGD06","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62e31a9ce71b2e2da6fafbd4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"X X K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e82c"},"rt":21432,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":73960,"subject":"WFH24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5998ffe005a0e30001f1ff54","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMA A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e82d"},"rt":35045,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":109128,"subject":"WFH24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5998ffe005a0e30001f1ff54","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"12 PMK D D D E E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e82e"},"rt":36117,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":145342,"subject":"WFH24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5998ffe005a0e30001f1ff54","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"H H H C C C C 10 AM11 AM12 PMC C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e82f"},"rt":12461,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":157904,"subject":"WFH24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5998ffe005a0e30001f1ff54","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"K 04 PME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e830"},"rt":49965,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":207982,"subject":"WFH24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5998ffe005a0e30001f1ff54","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I I I I O O I O O O O O I I O O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e832"},"rt":56453,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":276215,"subject":"WFH24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5998ffe005a0e30001f1ff54","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"108 AM5E E E E 11 AME E E E E G G E G G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e833"},"rt":26656,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":302972,"subject":"WFH24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5998ffe005a0e30001f1ff54","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C C F B F F B B B F F B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e834"},"rt":136859,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":439933,"subject":"WFH24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5998ffe005a0e30001f1ff54","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"A A A B B F F F G E G L B 12 PM12 PMM 01 PM02 PMO "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e835"},"rt":117031,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":557293,"subject":"WFH24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5998ffe005a0e30001f1ff54","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J 10 AM10 AMJ J J J J J J J J J J J 10 AMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e836"},"rt":95526,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":653127,"subject":"WFH24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5998ffe005a0e30001f1ff54","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"B F F B F F F F F F F F B Z Z O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e837"},"rt":20628,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":674060,"subject":"WFH24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5998ffe005a0e30001f1ff54","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PMB B F F F 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e838"},"rt":20392,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":694567,"subject":"WFH24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5998ffe005a0e30001f1ff54","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"H C B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e839"},"rt":318051,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":1012720,"subject":"WFH24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5998ffe005a0e30001f1ff54","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"E 11 AMJ I E B B 02 PMD 06 PM10H O Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z 04 PMZ Z Z 04 PM04 PMZ Z Z 04 PMZ Z Z Z 04 PMO O O X X X X Z Z Z 09 AM10 AMX X B B O B B B B B F 12 PMF Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e83a"},"rt":201316,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1214322,"subject":"WFH24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5998ffe005a0e30001f1ff54","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"203 PM03 PMM M M X X X X O B B B B 12 PMB B B B F F E E E I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e83b"},"rt":130237,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1344876,"subject":"WFH24","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"5998ffe005a0e30001f1ff54","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"P 1202 PMX X K K X X X 02 PM02 PMX X B I 12 PMB F F B B B B M M M M J B E B F F F X X F B M M M M M M M M 01 PMJ J M G G G 01 PM01 PMG 01 PMG C C 01 PMC C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e84c"},"rt":57875,"condition":"11311112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":153339,"subject":"FGO1E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62957302ad8c1756b553a298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e84d"},"rt":32023,"condition":"11311112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":185478,"subject":"FGO1E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62957302ad8c1756b553a298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e84e"},"rt":61193,"condition":"11311112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":246786,"subject":"FGO1E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62957302ad8c1756b553a298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e84f"},"rt":43922,"condition":"11311112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":291004,"subject":"FGO1E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62957302ad8c1756b553a298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e850"},"rt":74055,"condition":"11311112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":365182,"subject":"FGO1E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62957302ad8c1756b553a298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e852"},"rt":74543,"condition":"11311112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":449568,"subject":"FGO1E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62957302ad8c1756b553a298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e853"},"rt":28564,"condition":"11311112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":478418,"subject":"FGO1E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62957302ad8c1756b553a298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e854"},"rt":106079,"condition":"11311112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":584606,"subject":"FGO1E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62957302ad8c1756b553a298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B O B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e855"},"rt":42405,"condition":"11311112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":627312,"subject":"FGO1E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62957302ad8c1756b553a298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"B B B I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e856"},"rt":40876,"condition":"11311112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":668310,"subject":"FGO1E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62957302ad8c1756b553a298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e857"},"rt":10292,"condition":"11311112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":678727,"subject":"FGO1E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62957302ad8c1756b553a298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e858"},"rt":11335,"condition":"11311112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":690181,"subject":"FGO1E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62957302ad8c1756b553a298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e859"},"rt":107768,"condition":"11311112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":798053,"subject":"FGO1E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62957302ad8c1756b553a298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e85a"},"rt":11070,"condition":"11311112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":809403,"subject":"FGO1E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62957302ad8c1756b553a298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"6306850ed2ebe8c09972e85b"},"rt":31117,"condition":"11311112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","arotation":"1","lrotation":"1","shape":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":840634,"subject":"FGO1E","study":"SGC4D","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"6305c006f42920bf5e5e3336","sona_id":"62957302ad8c1756b553a298","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""}]
